{
  "name": "JPDB 5K",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "吐息",
      "answer": "といき",
      "meaning": "sigh, long breath"
    },
    {
      "question": "身長",
      "answer": "しんちょう",
      "meaning": "height (of body), stature"
    },
    {
      "question": "転移",
      "answer": "てんい",
      "meaning": "moving (location, with the times, etc.), change, transition, metastasis, spread, transition (e.g. ph"
    },
    {
      "question": "指す",
      "answer": "さす",
      "meaning": "to point, to nominate, to select someone, to specify some person, to identify, to indicate, to point"
    },
    {
      "question": "本音",
      "answer": "ほんね",
      "meaning": "real intention, motive, true opinion, what one really thinks"
    },
    {
      "question": "生じる",
      "answer": "しょうじる",
      "meaning": "to produce, to yield, to cause, to result from, to arise, to be generated"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護",
      "answer": "ほご",
      "meaning": "protection, safeguard, guardianship, custody, patronage, preservation, conservation"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏",
      "answer": "うじ,し",
      "meaning": "family name, lineage, birth, clan, Mr, Mrs, Ms, Miss, he, him, counter for people"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛情",
      "answer": "あいじょう",
      "meaning": "love, affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "収める",
      "answer": "おさめる",
      "meaning": "to dedicate, to make an offering, to pay (fees), to supply, to store, to finish, to bring to a close"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍い",
      "answer": "おそい,にぶい,のろい",
      "meaning": "slow, time-consuming, sluggish, dull, stupid, dull (e.g. a knife), blunt, thickheaded, obtuse, dull"
    },
    {
      "question": "教わる",
      "answer": "おそわる",
      "meaning": "to be taught, to learn, to take lessons in"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪える",
      "answer": "たえる,こらえる,こたえる",
      "meaning": "to bear, to stand, to endure, to put up with, to support, to withstand, to resist, to brave, to be f"
    },
    {
      "question": "何回",
      "answer": "なんかい",
      "meaning": "how many times?"
    },
    {
      "question": "団",
      "answer": "だん",
      "meaning": "body, group, party, company, troupe"
    },
    {
      "question": "器用",
      "answer": "きよう",
      "meaning": "skillful, skilful, adroit, dexterous, dextrous, deft, nimble, handy, clever, shrewd, ingenious"
    },
    {
      "question": "力になる",
      "answer": "ちからになる",
      "meaning": "to be helpful, to be dependable, to stand by (someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "作り出す",
      "answer": "つくりだす",
      "meaning": "to manufacture, to produce, to raise (crops), to invent, to dream up, to create"
    },
    {
      "question": "部活",
      "answer": "ぶかつ",
      "meaning": "club activities, extracurricular activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "数える",
      "answer": "かぞえる",
      "meaning": "to count, to enumerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "代わり",
      "answer": "かわり,がわり",
      "meaning": "substitute, replacement, substituting, replacing, stand-in, proxy, alternate, deputy, relief, succes"
    },
    {
      "question": "驚愕",
      "answer": "きょうがく",
      "meaning": "astonishment, amazement, surprise, fright, shock"
    },
    {
      "question": "対する",
      "answer": "たいする",
      "meaning": "to face (each other), to be facing, to be directed toward (the future, etc.), to be in response to,"
    },
    {
      "question": "金色",
      "answer": "きんいろ,こんじき,きんしょく",
      "meaning": "golden (colour, color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲望",
      "answer": "よくぼう",
      "meaning": "desire, appetite, lust"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕える",
      "answer": "つかえる",
      "meaning": "to serve, to work for, to attend"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊か",
      "answer": "ゆたか",
      "meaning": "abundant, wealthy, plentiful, rich, affluent, very, extremely, full of, great"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え込む",
      "answer": "かんがえこむ",
      "meaning": "to ponder, to brood"
    },
    {
      "question": "探索",
      "answer": "たんさく",
      "meaning": "search, lookup, hunt, (item of) research, exploration, investigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち込む",
      "answer": "もちこむ",
      "meaning": "to take something into ..., to bring in, to carry in, to lodge (a complaint), to file (a plan), to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "要素",
      "answer": "ようそ",
      "meaning": "component, factor, item (e.g. in list), element (e.g. in array), member (e.g. data structure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "積極的",
      "answer": "せっきょくてき",
      "meaning": "positive, assertive, active, proactive, aggressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "関係者",
      "answer": "かんけいしゃ",
      "meaning": "person concerned, people involved (in an event), those concerned, staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "針",
      "answer": "はり",
      "meaning": "needle, pin, hook, stinger, thorn, hand (e.g. clock, etc.), pointer, staple (for a stapler), needlew"
    },
    {
      "question": "溜まる",
      "answer": "たまる",
      "meaning": "to collect, to gather, to save, to accumulate, to pile up"
    },
    {
      "question": "地位",
      "answer": "ちい",
      "meaning": "(social) position, status"
    },
    {
      "question": "服装",
      "answer": "ふくそう",
      "meaning": "garments, attire"
    },
    {
      "question": "本格的",
      "answer": "ほんかくてき",
      "meaning": "genuine, real, regular, normal, typical, standard, orthodox, full-scale, full-blown, all-out, full-f"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔う",
      "answer": "よう,えう",
      "meaning": "to get drunk, to become intoxicated, to feel sick (e.g. in a vehicle), to become nauseated, to be el"
    },
    {
      "question": "変わり",
      "answer": "かわり",
      "meaning": "change, alteration, difference, distinction, something wrong, abnormality, unusual event, accident,"
    },
    {
      "question": "出会い",
      "answer": "であい",
      "meaning": "meeting, rendezvous, encounter, confluence"
    },
    {
      "question": "排除",
      "answer": "はいじょ",
      "meaning": "exclusion, removal, rejection, elimination, abatement, lifting (sanctions, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪の毛",
      "answer": "かみのけ",
      "meaning": "hair (of the head)"
    },
    {
      "question": "成績",
      "answer": "せいせき",
      "meaning": "results, record, grades, marks"
    },
    {
      "question": "金属",
      "answer": "きんぞく",
      "meaning": "metal"
    },
    {
      "question": "特定",
      "answer": "とくてい",
      "meaning": "specific, particular, designated, special, specifying, designating, identifying, pinpointing"
    },
    {
      "question": "小説",
      "answer": "しょうせつ",
      "meaning": "novel, (short) story"
    },
    {
      "question": "捧げる",
      "answer": "ささげる",
      "meaning": "to lift up, to hold up, to hold above eye level, to give, to offer, to consecrate, to devote, to sac"
    },
    {
      "question": "美",
      "answer": "び,み",
      "meaning": "beauty, august, beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "姉妹",
      "answer": "しまい,きょうだい",
      "meaning": "sisters"
    },
    {
      "question": "前後",
      "answer": "ぜんご,まえしりえ",
      "meaning": "front and rear, front and back, before and behind, back and forth, before and after, around, about,"
    },
    {
      "question": "時折",
      "answer": "ときおり,ときより",
      "meaning": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "実行",
      "answer": "じっこう",
      "meaning": "execution (e.g. of a plan), carrying out, practice, action, implementation, fulfillment, realization"
    },
    {
      "question": "一族",
      "answer": "いちぞく",
      "meaning": "family, relatives, dependents, household"
    },
    {
      "question": "姿を消す",
      "answer": "すがたをけす",
      "meaning": "to disappear, to vanish"
    },
    {
      "question": "散々",
      "answer": "さんざん",
      "meaning": "thoroughly, completely, utterly, severely, harshly, terribly, miserably, wretchedly, badly, scattere"
    },
    {
      "question": "微笑み",
      "answer": "ほほえみ,ほおえみ",
      "meaning": "smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "危うい",
      "answer": "あやうい",
      "meaning": "dangerous, in danger, facing imminent danger, precarious (situation), perilous (state, balance, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "世",
      "answer": "よ,せい",
      "meaning": "world, society, public, life, lifetime, age, era, period, epoch, generation, reign, rule, the times,"
    },
    {
      "question": "場面",
      "answer": "ばめん",
      "meaning": "scene, setting, place (where something happens), scenario, case, scene (in a movie, play), shot, sta"
    },
    {
      "question": "手渡す",
      "answer": "てわたす",
      "meaning": "to hand over, to surrender"
    },
    {
      "question": "明確",
      "answer": "めいかく",
      "meaning": "clear, precise, definite, distinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "倉庫",
      "answer": "そうこ",
      "meaning": "storehouse, warehouse, godown"
    },
    {
      "question": "種族",
      "answer": "しゅぞく",
      "meaning": "race, tribe, ethnic group, species, genus, family, stellar population (i.e. population I, II and III"
    },
    {
      "question": "上空",
      "answer": "じょうくう",
      "meaning": "sky, the skies, high-altitude sky, upper air"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐",
      "answer": "ふところ",
      "meaning": "inside the breast of one's clothing (esp. kimono), bosom, (breast) pocket, space between one's chest"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆様",
      "answer": "みなさま",
      "meaning": "everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "対抗",
      "answer": "たいこう",
      "meaning": "opposition, rivalry, competition, antagonism"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝心",
      "answer": "かんじん",
      "meaning": "essential, important, crucial, vital, main"
    },
    {
      "question": "美少女",
      "answer": "びしょうじょ",
      "meaning": "beautiful girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋",
      "answer": "とき,あき",
      "meaning": "time, hour, moment, autumn, fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を引く",
      "answer": "てをひく",
      "meaning": "to withdraw from (a deal), to wash one's hands of, to lead by the hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "個人的",
      "answer": "こじんてき",
      "meaning": "personal, individual, private"
    },
    {
      "question": "父上",
      "answer": "ちちうえ",
      "meaning": "father (esp. used in samurai families prior to the Meiji period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "封じる",
      "answer": "ふうじる,ほうじる",
      "meaning": "to seal (letter), to prevent, to forbid, to block, to enfeoff"
    },
    {
      "question": "時刻",
      "answer": "じこく",
      "meaning": "time, (the) hour, favourable time, opportunity, chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "凄まじい",
      "answer": "すさまじい",
      "meaning": "terrific, fierce, terrible, tremendous, dreadful, awful, amazing, absurd, cutthroat, intense"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲しむ",
      "answer": "かなしむ",
      "meaning": "to be sad, to mourn for, to regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "両",
      "answer": "りょう,もろ,りゃん",
      "meaning": "both (hands, parents, sides, etc.), counter for carriages (e.g. in a train), counter for vehicles, r"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲がる",
      "answer": "まがる",
      "meaning": "to bend, to curve, to warp, to wind, to twist, to turn, to be awry, to be askew, to be crooked"
    },
    {
      "question": "想う",
      "answer": "おもう",
      "meaning": "to think, to consider, to believe, to reckon, to think (of doing), to plan (to do), to judge, to ass"
    },
    {
      "question": "液体",
      "answer": "えきたい",
      "meaning": "liquid"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み物",
      "answer": "のみもの",
      "meaning": "drink, beverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩り",
      "answer": "かり",
      "meaning": "hunting, harvesting (e.g. berries, fruit), picking, gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "分かれる",
      "answer": "わかれる",
      "meaning": "to branch, to fork, to diverge, to separate, to split, to divide, to disperse, to scatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "要る",
      "answer": "いる",
      "meaning": "to be needed, to be wanted"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き抜く",
      "answer": "ひきぬく",
      "meaning": "to extract, to pull out, to draw out, to uproot, to headhunt, to lure away, to poach, to entice"
    },
    {
      "question": "叫び",
      "answer": "さけび",
      "meaning": "shout, scream, outcry"
    },
    {
      "question": "落下",
      "answer": "らっか",
      "meaning": "fall, drop, descent, coming down"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れる",
      "answer": "うれる",
      "meaning": "to sell (well), to be well known, to be popular, to be famous"
    },
    {
      "question": "見慣れる",
      "answer": "みなれる",
      "meaning": "to become used to seeing, to be familiar with"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭から",
      "answer": "あたまから",
      "meaning": "from the beginning, without hesitation, flatly (e.g. refusing), entirely, completely"
    },
    {
      "question": "騒がしい",
      "answer": "さわがしい",
      "meaning": "noisy, boisterous, turbulent (era, etc.), troubled"
    },
    {
      "question": "処分",
      "answer": "しょぶん",
      "meaning": "disposal, throwing away, selling off, dealing with (a problem), measure, punishment, penalty, puttin"
    },
    {
      "question": "棚",
      "answer": "たな",
      "meaning": "shelf, ledge, rack, trellis"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪文",
      "answer": "じゅもん",
      "meaning": "spell, charm, incantation, magic word"
    },
    {
      "question": "早め",
      "answer": "はやめ",
      "meaning": "early, a little earlier than usual, a little faster than usual, slightly quicker"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽霊",
      "answer": "ゆうれい",
      "meaning": "ghost, specter, spectre, apparition, phantom"
    },
    {
      "question": "真の",
      "answer": "しんの",
      "meaning": "true, real, genuine, proper, utter"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮",
      "answer": "かわ",
      "meaning": "skin, hide, pelt, fur, rind, peel, husk, bark, shell, sheath, wrapping, mask (hiding one's true natu"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖かい",
      "answer": "あたたかい,あったかい",
      "meaning": "warm, mild, (pleasantly) hot, warm (of a colour), mellow, having enough money"
    },
    {
      "question": "侍女",
      "answer": "じじょ",
      "meaning": "lady attendant, lady's maid, waiting maid"
    },
    {
      "question": "次第に",
      "answer": "しだいに",
      "meaning": "gradually (progress into a state), in sequence, in order, in turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "向き直る",
      "answer": "むきなおる",
      "meaning": "to turn round, to face about, to turn about"
    },
    {
      "question": "風景",
      "answer": "ふうけい",
      "meaning": "scenery, scene, landscape, view, sight, scene (e.g. of a crime)"
    },
    {
      "question": "現象",
      "answer": "げんしょう",
      "meaning": "phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "question": "感じ取る",
      "answer": "かんじとる",
      "meaning": "to perceive, to sense, to take in, to grasp, to feel"
    },
    {
      "question": "指差す",
      "answer": "ゆびさす",
      "meaning": "to point at"
    },
    {
      "question": "詳細",
      "answer": "しょうさい",
      "meaning": "details, particulars, specifics, detailed, specific, minute, close-up view (of a digitally displayed"
    },
    {
      "question": "微か",
      "answer": "かすか",
      "meaning": "faint, dim, weak, slight, vague, indistinct, hazy, poor, wretched, meagre, meager, scanty"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉",
      "answer": "は,よう",
      "meaning": "leaf, blade (of grass), (pine) needle, counter for leaves, pieces of paper, etc., counter for boats"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸",
      "answer": "はだか",
      "meaning": "nakedness, nudity, bareness, baldness, being uncovered, being penniless, concealing nothing, opennes"
    },
    {
      "question": "付き合い",
      "answer": "つきあい",
      "meaning": "association, socializing, socialising, fellowship"
    },
    {
      "question": "自宅",
      "answer": "じたく",
      "meaning": "one's home, one's house"
    },
    {
      "question": "頼み",
      "answer": "たのみ,だのみ",
      "meaning": "request, favor, favour, reliance, dependence, trust, hope, depending on, dependent upon, relying on"
    },
    {
      "question": "包み込む",
      "answer": "つつみこむ",
      "meaning": "to wrap up"
    },
    {
      "question": "気絶",
      "answer": "きぜつ",
      "meaning": "faint, swoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "足取り",
      "answer": "あしどり,あしとり",
      "meaning": "gait, walk, stride, pace, step, manner of walking, trace (e.g. of route taken by hunted criminal), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "本心",
      "answer": "ほんしん",
      "meaning": "true feelings, real intention, one's heart, one's right mind, one's senses, one's conscience"
    },
    {
      "question": "被る",
      "answer": "かぶる,かむる,こうむる",
      "meaning": "to put on (one's head), to wear, to have on, to pull over (one's head), to crown (oneself), to be co"
    },
    {
      "question": "器",
      "answer": "うつわ,き",
      "meaning": "bowl, vessel, container, ability, capacity, calibre, caliber, device, instrument"
    },
    {
      "question": "世間",
      "answer": "せけん",
      "meaning": "world, society, people, the public"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰める",
      "answer": "なぐさめる",
      "meaning": "to comfort, to console, to amuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "一口",
      "answer": "ひとくち",
      "meaning": "mouthful, morsel, bite, gulp, sip, draft, draught, one word, in short, one share, one contribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵器",
      "answer": "へいき",
      "meaning": "arms, weapon, ordnance"
    },
    {
      "question": "出迎える",
      "answer": "でむかえる",
      "meaning": "to meet, to greet"
    },
    {
      "question": "見据える",
      "answer": "みすえる",
      "meaning": "to stare fixedly at, to fix one's gaze on, to make sure of, to set one's eyes on (e.g. the future),"
    },
    {
      "question": "出入り",
      "answer": "でいり,ではいり",
      "meaning": "going in and out, entering and exiting, visiting regularly, frequenting, having regular dealings wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "幸運",
      "answer": "こううん",
      "meaning": "good luck, fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "憎む",
      "answer": "にくむ",
      "meaning": "to hate, to detest"
    },
    {
      "question": "異様",
      "answer": "いよう",
      "meaning": "bizarre, strange, eccentric, odd, queer"
    },
    {
      "question": "裾",
      "answer": "すそ",
      "meaning": "hem, (trouser) cuff, shirttail, bottom (of a kimono), train (of a dress), bottom part, bottom edge,"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅ぼす",
      "answer": "ほろぼす",
      "meaning": "to destroy, to overthrow, to wreck, to ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "内緒",
      "answer": "ないしょ",
      "meaning": "secrecy, confidentiality, privacy, secret, one's circumstances (esp. fiscal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅行",
      "answer": "りょこう",
      "meaning": "travel, trip, journey, excursion, tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "好む",
      "answer": "このむ",
      "meaning": "to like, to prefer"
    },
    {
      "question": "拒絶",
      "answer": "きょぜつ",
      "meaning": "refusal, rejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "住人",
      "answer": "じゅうにん",
      "meaning": "dweller, inhabitant, resident, user (of a website)"
    },
    {
      "question": "数字",
      "answer": "すうじ",
      "meaning": "numeral, figure, digit, numeric character"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠ける",
      "answer": "かける",
      "meaning": "to be chipped, to be damaged, to be broken, to be lacking, to be missing, to be insufficient, to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "評判",
      "answer": "ひょうばん",
      "meaning": "fame, reputation, popularity, rumour (rumor), talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "等",
      "answer": "など,とう,ら",
      "meaning": "et cetera, etc., and the like, and so forth, or something, the likes of, class, order, rank, equal,"
    },
    {
      "question": "手放す",
      "answer": "てばなす",
      "meaning": "to let go of, to release, to drop, to part with (e.g. a possession), to relinquish, to spare, to sel"
    },
    {
      "question": "滲む",
      "answer": "にじむ",
      "meaning": "to run (of liquid), to spread, to blur, to blot, to be blurred, to ooze, to well up (of tears, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏休み",
      "answer": "なつやすみ",
      "meaning": "summer vacation, summer holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "購入",
      "answer": "こうにゅう",
      "meaning": "purchase, buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "備える",
      "answer": "そなえる",
      "meaning": "to furnish with, to equip with, to provide, to install, to prepare for, to make preparations for, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "主人公",
      "answer": "しゅじんこう",
      "meaning": "protagonist, main character, hero(ine) (of a story), head of household"
    },
    {
      "question": "新鮮",
      "answer": "しんせん",
      "meaning": "fresh"
    },
    {
      "question": "着替え",
      "answer": "きがえ",
      "meaning": "changing clothes, change of clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "同行",
      "answer": "どうぎょう,どうこう",
      "meaning": "fellow pilgrim, fellow practicer of austerities, accompanying, travelling together, traveling togeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "経過",
      "answer": "けいか",
      "meaning": "passage (of time), elapsing, lapse, progress, development, course (of events), transit"
    },
    {
      "question": "餌",
      "answer": "えさ,え",
      "meaning": "(animal) feed, fodder, pet food, bait, lure, enticement"
    },
    {
      "question": "大半",
      "answer": "たいはん",
      "meaning": "majority, more than half, most (of), mostly, largely, mainly, predominately, nearly"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜",
      "answer": "さくら",
      "meaning": "cherry tree, cherry blossom, fake buyer, paid audience, shill, seat filler, hired applauder, horse m"
    },
    {
      "question": "不足",
      "answer": "ふそく",
      "meaning": "insufficiency, deficiency, shortage, lack, scarcity, deficit, dissatisfaction, discontent, complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "反撃",
      "answer": "はんげき",
      "meaning": "counterattack, counteroffensive, counterblow"
    },
    {
      "question": "電車",
      "answer": "でんしゃ",
      "meaning": "train, electric train"
    },
    {
      "question": "義務",
      "answer": "ぎむ",
      "meaning": "duty, obligation, responsibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛かる",
      "answer": "かかる",
      "meaning": "to take (a resource, e.g. time or money), to hang, to come into view, to arrive, to come under (a co"
    },
    {
      "question": "修行",
      "answer": "しゅぎょう,すぎょう",
      "meaning": "ascetic practices, training, practice, discipline, study"
    },
    {
      "question": "載る",
      "answer": "のる",
      "meaning": "to be placed on, to be set on, to be piled on, to be loaded on, to appear (in print), to be mentione"
    },
    {
      "question": "数人",
      "answer": "すうにん",
      "meaning": "several people, a few people"
    },
    {
      "question": "校舎",
      "answer": "こうしゃ",
      "meaning": "school building, schoolhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "意地悪",
      "answer": "いじわる",
      "meaning": "malicious, ill-tempered, unkind"
    },
    {
      "question": "述べる",
      "answer": "のべる",
      "meaning": "to state, to express, to mention"
    },
    {
      "question": "両腕",
      "answer": "りょううで,もろうで",
      "meaning": "both arms"
    },
    {
      "question": "晒す",
      "answer": "さらす",
      "meaning": "to expose (to the sun, public, danger, etc.), to bleach, to refine, to rinse (vegetables), to soak,"
    },
    {
      "question": "罰",
      "answer": "ばち,ばつ",
      "meaning": "(divine) punishment, curse, retribution, punishment, penalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸を張る",
      "answer": "むねをはる",
      "meaning": "to throw out one's chest, to be puffed up with pride"
    },
    {
      "question": "犯罪",
      "answer": "はんざい",
      "meaning": "crime, offence, offense"
    },
    {
      "question": "早々",
      "answer": "そうそう,はやはや,はやばや",
      "meaning": "as soon as..., just after..., immediately after..., hurriedly, in haste, quickly, promptly, early"
    },
    {
      "question": "響き渡る",
      "answer": "ひびきわたる",
      "meaning": "to resound, to echo, to reverberate"
    },
    {
      "question": "王妃",
      "answer": "おうひ",
      "meaning": "queen"
    },
    {
      "question": "食材",
      "answer": "しょくざい",
      "meaning": "ingredient, foodstuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "断言",
      "answer": "だんげん",
      "meaning": "assertion, declaration, affirmation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出口",
      "answer": "でぐち",
      "meaning": "exit, gateway, way out, outlet, vent, leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "上位",
      "answer": "じょうい",
      "meaning": "superior (in rank), top, ranking, higher order (e.g. byte), host computer (of connected device)"
    },
    {
      "question": "親子",
      "answer": "おやこ,しんし",
      "meaning": "parent and child"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰色",
      "answer": "はいいろ,かいしょく",
      "meaning": "grey, gray, ashen"
    },
    {
      "question": "心底",
      "answer": "しんそこ,しんてい",
      "meaning": "bottom of one's heart, depths of one's mind, innermost thoughts, completely (from the bottom of one'"
    },
    {
      "question": "固める",
      "answer": "かためる",
      "meaning": "to harden, to freeze, to strengthen, to solidify, to make (a fist), to tramp down (snow, dirt), to p"
    },
    {
      "question": "食料",
      "answer": "しょくりょう",
      "meaning": "food"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭ける",
      "answer": "かける",
      "meaning": "to wager, to bet, to risk, to stake, to gamble"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄暗い",
      "answer": "うすぐらい",
      "meaning": "dim, gloomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "見抜く",
      "answer": "みぬく",
      "meaning": "to see through, to see into (someone's heart, mind, etc.), to perceive, to find out, to detect"
    },
    {
      "question": "負担",
      "answer": "ふたん",
      "meaning": "burden, load, responsibility, bearing (a cost, responsibility, etc.), shouldering"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪う",
      "answer": "のろう,まじなう",
      "meaning": "to curse, to put a curse on, to detest intensely, to pray that one avoids disaster or illness, to pr"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定",
      "answer": "こてい",
      "meaning": "fixing (in place), being fixed (in place), securing, anchoring, fastening down, fixing (e.g. salary,"
    },
    {
      "question": "下る",
      "answer": "さがる,くだる",
      "meaning": "to come down, to go down, to fall, to drop, to sink, to get lower, to hang, to dangle, to move back,"
    },
    {
      "question": "一見",
      "answer": "いっけん,いちげん",
      "meaning": "look, glimpse, glance, apparently, seemingly, first meeting, first visit to inn, restaurant, etc. wi"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖",
      "answer": "そで",
      "meaning": "sleeve, wing (of a stage, desk, gate, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "提供",
      "answer": "ていきょう",
      "meaning": "offer, tender, providing, supplying, making available, donating (blood, organs, etc.), sponsoring (a"
    },
    {
      "question": "右腕",
      "answer": "みぎうで,うわん",
      "meaning": "right arm, right-hand man, right hand, right-hand person, right-handed pitcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "木々",
      "answer": "きぎ",
      "meaning": "(many) trees, every tree, all kinds of trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "容姿",
      "answer": "ようし",
      "meaning": "(physical) appearance (of a person), one's face and figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "沢山",
      "answer": "たくさん,だくさん",
      "meaning": "a lot, lots, plenty, many, a large number, much, a great deal, a good deal, enough, sufficient, too"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔術師",
      "answer": "まじゅつし",
      "meaning": "magician, conjurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "第三",
      "answer": "だいさん",
      "meaning": "the third"
    },
    {
      "question": "単語",
      "answer": "たんご",
      "meaning": "word, vocabulary, (usually) single-character word"
    },
    {
      "question": "所詮",
      "answer": "しょせん,そせん",
      "meaning": "after all, in the end, anyway, (cannot) possibly, (not) at all, (not) by any means, (not) ever"
    },
    {
      "question": "世話",
      "answer": "せわ",
      "meaning": "looking after, help, aid, assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "確率",
      "answer": "かくりつ",
      "meaning": "probability, likelihood, chances"
    },
    {
      "question": "困難",
      "answer": "こんなん",
      "meaning": "difficulty, hardship, trouble, distress, infeasibility, inability (to carry out)"
    },
    {
      "question": "折る",
      "answer": "おる",
      "meaning": "to break, to fracture, to break off, to snap off, to pick (e.g. flowers), to fold, to bend, to make"
    },
    {
      "question": "筈",
      "answer": "はず",
      "meaning": "should (be), bound (to be), expected (to be), must (be), nock (of a bow), nock (of an arrow), nock-s"
    },
    {
      "question": "這う",
      "answer": "はう",
      "meaning": "to creep, to crawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚す",
      "answer": "よごす,けがす",
      "meaning": "to pollute, to contaminate, to soil, to make dirty, to stain, to disgrace, to dishonour, to dishonor"
    },
    {
      "question": "見知る",
      "answer": "みしる",
      "meaning": "to recognise, to recognize, to know by sight, to become acquainted with"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗る",
      "answer": "ぬる",
      "meaning": "to paint, to plaster, to lacquer, to varnish, to spread, to smear, to put up (wallpaper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "領主",
      "answer": "りょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "feudal lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "深呼吸",
      "answer": "しんこきゅう",
      "meaning": "deep breath"
    },
    {
      "question": "勿論",
      "answer": "もちろん",
      "meaning": "of course, certainly, naturally"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞る",
      "answer": "しぼる",
      "meaning": "to wring (towel, rag), to squeeze, to squeeze (fruit to extract juice), to press, to extract, to mil"
    },
    {
      "question": "旦那",
      "answer": "だんな",
      "meaning": "master (of a house, shop, etc.), husband, sir, boss, master, governor, patron of a mistress, geisha,"
    },
    {
      "question": "漫画",
      "answer": "まんが",
      "meaning": "cartoon, comic, comic strip, manga"
    },
    {
      "question": "二度",
      "answer": "ふたたび,にど",
      "meaning": "again, once more, a second time, two times, twice, two degrees"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘い",
      "answer": "さそい,いざない",
      "meaning": "invitation, introduction, temptation"
    },
    {
      "question": "興味深い",
      "answer": "きょうみぶかい",
      "meaning": "very interesting, of great interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "理性",
      "answer": "りせい",
      "meaning": "reason, reasoning power, (one's) sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "魅力的",
      "answer": "みりょくてき",
      "meaning": "charming, fascinating, attractive"
    },
    {
      "question": "成立",
      "answer": "せいりつ",
      "meaning": "formation, establishment, materialization, coming into existence, conclusion (e.g. of a deal), reach"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋",
      "answer": "すじ,きん",
      "meaning": "muscle, tendon, sinew, vein, artery, fiber, fibre, string, line, stripe, streak, reason, logic, plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理矢理",
      "answer": "むりやり",
      "meaning": "forcibly, against one's will"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘導",
      "answer": "ゆうどう",
      "meaning": "guidance, leading, induction, introduction, incitement, inducement"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠告",
      "answer": "ちゅうこく",
      "meaning": "advice, warning"
    },
    {
      "question": "憧れ",
      "answer": "あこがれ",
      "meaning": "yearning, longing, aspiration, adoration, admiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "一般",
      "answer": "いっぱん",
      "meaning": "general, universal, ordinary, average, common, non-celebrity, the same, no different, (just) as if"
    },
    {
      "question": "済み",
      "answer": "ずみ,すみ",
      "meaning": "arranged, taken care of, settled, completed, finished"
    },
    {
      "question": "肯定",
      "answer": "こうてい",
      "meaning": "affirmation, affirmative (logic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一匹",
      "answer": "いっぴき",
      "meaning": "one animal (small), two-tan bolt of cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴く",
      "answer": "なく",
      "meaning": "to make sound (of an animal), to call, to cry, to whine, to sing, to chirp, to make a meld call (e.g"
    },
    {
      "question": "無論",
      "answer": "むろん",
      "meaning": "of course, certainly, naturally"
    },
    {
      "question": "混ぜる",
      "answer": "まぜる",
      "meaning": "to mix, to stir, to blend"
    },
    {
      "question": "出身",
      "answer": "しゅっしん",
      "meaning": "person's origin (e.g. city, country, parentage, school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "類",
      "answer": "るい,たぐい",
      "meaning": "kind, sort, type, class, genus, order, family, similar example, parallel, the like, equal, match, pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙げる",
      "answer": "あげる",
      "meaning": "to raise, to elevate, to do up (one's hair), to fly (a kite, etc.), to launch (fireworks, etc.), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "予測",
      "answer": "よそく",
      "meaning": "prediction, estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "見当たる",
      "answer": "みあたる",
      "meaning": "to be found"
    },
    {
      "question": "指導",
      "answer": "しどう",
      "meaning": "guidance, leadership, instruction, direction, coaching, shido (disciplinary action for a minor infri"
    },
    {
      "question": "再度",
      "answer": "さいど",
      "meaning": "twice, again, second time"
    },
    {
      "question": "後輩",
      "answer": "こうはい",
      "meaning": "junior (at work, school, etc.), younger people, younger student"
    },
    {
      "question": "一面",
      "answer": "いちめん",
      "meaning": "one face, one surface, the whole surface, one aspect, one side, (on) the other hand, one broad, flat"
    },
    {
      "question": "植物",
      "answer": "しょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "plant, vegetation"
    },
    {
      "question": "一般的",
      "answer": "いっぱんてき",
      "meaning": "general, popular, common, typical"
    },
    {
      "question": "入学",
      "answer": "にゅうがく",
      "meaning": "entry to school or university, matriculation, enrolment (in university, etc.) (enrollment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪悪感",
      "answer": "ざいあくかん",
      "meaning": "feelings of guilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "如く",
      "answer": "ごとく,しく",
      "meaning": "like, as if, the same as, to match, to equal, to catch up with, to overtake"
    },
    {
      "question": "優雅",
      "answer": "ゆうが",
      "meaning": "elegant, graceful, refined"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼食",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょく,ちゅうじき,ひるげ",
      "meaning": "lunch, midday meal, food served at a tea party (tea ceremony)"
    },
    {
      "question": "当初",
      "answer": "とうしょ",
      "meaning": "beginning, start, outset, at first, at the beginning, initially, originally"
    },
    {
      "question": "出番",
      "answer": "でばん",
      "meaning": "one's turn, one's shift, one's turn on stage, screen time, screentime"
    },
    {
      "question": "未だに",
      "answer": "いまだに",
      "meaning": "still, even now, to this day"
    },
    {
      "question": "目撃",
      "answer": "もくげき",
      "meaning": "witnessing, observing, sighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛大",
      "answer": "せいだい",
      "meaning": "grand, magnificent, lavish, large scale, prosperous, thriving, lively, forceful, powerful, vigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "層",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "layer, stratum, seam, bed, class, bracket, group, sheaf, counter for stories (of a building)"
    },
    {
      "question": "争い",
      "answer": "あらそい",
      "meaning": "dispute, strife, quarrel, dissension, conflict, rivalry, contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "理不尽",
      "answer": "りふじん",
      "meaning": "unreasonable, irrational, outrageous, absurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "共有",
      "answer": "きょうゆう",
      "meaning": "joint ownership, co-ownership, sharing (e.g. a viewpoint), sharing (files, devices on a network, pos"
    },
    {
      "question": "築く",
      "answer": "きずく",
      "meaning": "to build, to construct, to erect, to amass (e.g. fortune), to pile up"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼鏡",
      "answer": "めがね,がんきょう",
      "meaning": "glasses, eyeglasses, spectacles, judgment, judgement, discrimination, discernment, insight"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち",
      "answer": "もち",
      "meaning": "having, holding, possessing, owning, using, holder, owner, user, wear, durability, life, charge, exp"
    },
    {
      "question": "専用",
      "answer": "せんよう",
      "meaning": "(one's) exclusive use, private use, personal use, dedicated use, use for a particular purpose, exclu"
    },
    {
      "question": "大陸",
      "answer": "たいりく",
      "meaning": "continent, continental Asia (esp. mainland China), continental Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳裏",
      "answer": "のうり",
      "meaning": "one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒",
      "answer": "ぼう",
      "meaning": "pole, rod, stick, baton, line, dash, spoken monotonously"
    },
    {
      "question": "良く",
      "answer": "よく",
      "meaning": "nicely, properly, well, skillfully, skilfully, frequently, often, I'm glad that you ..., thank you f"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神的",
      "answer": "せいしんてき",
      "meaning": "mental, spiritual, emotional"
    },
    {
      "question": "燃やす",
      "answer": "もやす",
      "meaning": "to burn, to burn with (emotion, feeling), to be fired up"
    },
    {
      "question": "挑戦",
      "answer": "ちょうせん",
      "meaning": "challenge, defiance, dare, attempt, try"
    },
    {
      "question": "領域",
      "answer": "りょういき",
      "meaning": "area, domain, territory, field, range, region, regime"
    },
    {
      "question": "表面",
      "answer": "ひょうめん",
      "meaning": "surface, face, outside, exterior, appearances, superficiality"
    },
    {
      "question": "取引",
      "answer": "とりひき",
      "meaning": "transactions, dealings, business"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠片",
      "answer": "かけら",
      "meaning": "fragment, broken piece, chip, splinter, shard, ounce (of truth, conscience, etc.), trace, shred, scr"
    },
    {
      "question": "大抵",
      "answer": "たいてい",
      "meaning": "mostly, ordinarily, usually, generally, probably, most, almost all, ordinary, proper, appropriate, m"
    },
    {
      "question": "見張る",
      "answer": "みはる",
      "meaning": "to stand watch, to stand guard, to look out, to open (one's eyes) wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽きる",
      "answer": "つきる",
      "meaning": "to be used up, to be run out, to be exhausted, to be consumed, to come to an end"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮",
      "answer": "りょう,つかさ",
      "meaning": "hostel, dormitory, bureau (government department beneath a ministry under the ritsuryo system), tea-"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き出す",
      "answer": "ひきだす",
      "meaning": "to pull out, to take out, to draw out, to lead out (e.g. a horse from a stable), to summon (e.g. to"
    },
    {
      "question": "透明",
      "answer": "とうめい",
      "meaning": "transparent, clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "致す",
      "answer": "いたす",
      "meaning": "to do"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を取る",
      "answer": "てをとる",
      "meaning": "to take someone's hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "図書館",
      "answer": "としょかん,ずしょかん",
      "meaning": "library"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫁",
      "answer": "よめ",
      "meaning": "wife, bride, (one's) daughter-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "間近",
      "answer": "まぢか,まじか",
      "meaning": "proximity, nearness, soon, nearby"
    },
    {
      "question": "商売",
      "answer": "しょうばい",
      "meaning": "trade, business, commerce, transaction, occupation"
    },
    {
      "question": "贈る",
      "answer": "おくる",
      "meaning": "to give (as a gift), to present, to confer, to bestow, to award"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼う",
      "answer": "かう",
      "meaning": "to keep (a pet or other animal), to have, to own, to raise, to rear, to feed"
    },
    {
      "question": "好く",
      "answer": "すく,よく",
      "meaning": "to like, to love, to be fond of, nicely, properly, well, skillfully, skilfully, frequently, often, I"
    },
    {
      "question": "表す",
      "answer": "あらわす,ひょうす",
      "meaning": "to represent, to signify, to stand for, to reveal, to show, to display, to express, to make widely k"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮らし",
      "answer": "くらし",
      "meaning": "life, living, livelihood, life circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "体重",
      "answer": "たいじゅう",
      "meaning": "(body) weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "根",
      "answer": "ね,こん",
      "meaning": "root (of a plant), root (of a tooth, hair, etc.), center (of a pimple, etc.), root (of all evil, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪意",
      "answer": "あくい",
      "meaning": "ill will, spite, evil intention, malice, bad meaning, mala fides, bad faith, criminal intent to dece"
    },
    {
      "question": "目線",
      "answer": "めせん",
      "meaning": "(one's) gaze, direction in which one is looking, point of view, standpoint, line covering someone's"
    },
    {
      "question": "眩しい",
      "answer": "まぶしい,まぼしい",
      "meaning": "dazzling, radiant"
    },
    {
      "question": "本能",
      "answer": "ほんのう",
      "meaning": "instinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻",
      "answer": "けつ,しり",
      "meaning": "ass, arse, buttocks, rear, end, behind, rump, bottom, hips, undersurface, last place, consequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信",
      "answer": "つうしん",
      "meaning": "correspondence, communication, transmission, news, signal, telecommunications"
    },
    {
      "question": "気遣う",
      "answer": "きづかう",
      "meaning": "to worry about (someone's welfare or comfort), to feel anxious about, to have apprehensions of"
    },
    {
      "question": "救い",
      "answer": "すくい",
      "meaning": "help, rescue, aid, relief, salvation, solace, (source of) comfort, saving grace, (religious) salvati"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉まる",
      "answer": "しまる",
      "meaning": "to be shut, to close, to be closed, to be locked, to tighten, to be tightened, to become sober, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "脅威",
      "answer": "きょうい",
      "meaning": "threat, menace"
    },
    {
      "question": "色んな",
      "answer": "いろんな",
      "meaning": "various"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮肉",
      "answer": "ひにく",
      "meaning": "irony, sarcasm, cynicism, satire, unexpected, different from what one expected, not as one had plann"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し込む",
      "answer": "おしこむ",
      "meaning": "to push into, to cram into, to stuff into, to crowd into, to break in, to burgle, to burglarize"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴力",
      "answer": "ぼうりょく",
      "meaning": "violence, mayhem"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己紹介",
      "answer": "じこしょうかい",
      "meaning": "self-introduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "要するに",
      "answer": "ようするに",
      "meaning": "in short, in a word, to sum up, to put it simply, to make a long story short, after all"
    },
    {
      "question": "未だ",
      "answer": "まだ,いまだ",
      "meaning": "still, as yet, only, (not) yet, more, (more) still, at least, comparatively, relatively, unfinished,"
    },
    {
      "question": "自室",
      "answer": "じしつ",
      "meaning": "one's own room"
    },
    {
      "question": "怒鳴る",
      "answer": "どなる",
      "meaning": "to shout (in anger), to yell"
    },
    {
      "question": "賛成",
      "answer": "さんせい",
      "meaning": "approval, agreement, support, favour, favor"
    },
    {
      "question": "達成",
      "answer": "たっせい",
      "meaning": "achievement, attainment, accomplishment, realization"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩む",
      "answer": "ゆるむ",
      "meaning": "to become loose, to slacken (e.g. rope), to become less tense, to relax, to let one's guard down, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌打ち",
      "answer": "したうち",
      "meaning": "smacking lips, clicking tongue, tut-tut"
    },
    {
      "question": "響き",
      "answer": "どよめき,ひびき",
      "meaning": "commotion, stir, echo, reverberation, sound (esp. the distinctive sound of an object or activity, e."
    },
    {
      "question": "途切れる",
      "answer": "とぎれる",
      "meaning": "to break off, to come to an end, to be interrupted, to be cut short, to pause"
    },
    {
      "question": "唸る",
      "answer": "うなる",
      "meaning": "to groan, to moan, to roar, to howl, to growl, to hum (engine, wind, etc.), to buzz, to whiz, to sou"
    },
    {
      "question": "通用",
      "answer": "つうよう",
      "meaning": "popular use, circulation, to pass as, to pass for"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖",
      "answer": "みずうみ,こ",
      "meaning": "lake, lake (in place names)"
    },
    {
      "question": "王家",
      "answer": "おうけ",
      "meaning": "royal family"
    },
    {
      "question": "下す",
      "answer": "くだす,おろす",
      "meaning": "to make a decision, to draw a conclusion, to give a judgement, to hand down a verdict, to pass a sen"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞄",
      "answer": "かばん",
      "meaning": "bag, satchel, briefcase, basket"
    },
    {
      "question": "首筋",
      "answer": "くびすじ",
      "meaning": "nape of the neck, back of the neck, scruff of the neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "避難",
      "answer": "ひなん",
      "meaning": "taking refuge, finding shelter, evacuation, escape, seeking safe haven"
    },
    {
      "question": "上昇",
      "answer": "じょうしょう",
      "meaning": "rising, ascending, climbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "部長",
      "answer": "ぶちょう",
      "meaning": "head (chief, director) of a section or department, head of a (school) club, head of a (school) team"
    },
    {
      "question": "期間",
      "answer": "きかん",
      "meaning": "period, term, interval"
    },
    {
      "question": "率いる",
      "answer": "ひきいる",
      "meaning": "to lead, to spearhead (a group), to command (troops)"
    },
    {
      "question": "模様",
      "answer": "もよう",
      "meaning": "pattern, figure, design, state, condition, conjecture of the current situation, the way it seems, mo"
    },
    {
      "question": "入り",
      "answer": "いり",
      "meaning": "entering, setting (of the Sun), containing, content, audience, income, beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "一定",
      "answer": "いってい,いちじょう",
      "meaning": "fixed, settled, constant, definite, uniform, regularized, regularised, defined, standardized, standa"
    },
    {
      "question": "畑",
      "answer": "はたけ,はた",
      "meaning": "field (for fruits, vegetables, etc.), cultivated land, vegetable plot, kitchen garden, plantation, f"
    },
    {
      "question": "生命",
      "answer": "せいめい",
      "meaning": "life, existence, (one's) working life, career, life force, lifeblood, soul, essence"
    },
    {
      "question": "是非",
      "answer": "ぜひ",
      "meaning": "certainly, without fail, right and wrong, pros and cons"
    },
    {
      "question": "敏感",
      "answer": "びんかん",
      "meaning": "sensitive, alert, aware, susceptible"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼ける",
      "answer": "やける",
      "meaning": "to burn, to be roasted, to be heated, to be sunburnt, to fade (in the sun), to glow red (i.e. of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸い",
      "answer": "まるい,まろい",
      "meaning": "round, circular, spherical, curved, smooth, harmonious, calm, peaceful, amiable, amicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "無くなる",
      "answer": "なくなる",
      "meaning": "to be lost (e.g. luggage), to be missing, to be used up, to be run out, to be exhausted, to be consu"
    },
    {
      "question": "侯爵",
      "answer": "こうしゃく",
      "meaning": "marquis, marquess"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "perception, intuition, the sixth sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "選手",
      "answer": "せんしゅ",
      "meaning": "player (sports), athlete, team member"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り裂く",
      "answer": "きりさく",
      "meaning": "to cut off, to cut up, to tear to pieces"
    },
    {
      "question": "友",
      "answer": "とも,ゆう",
      "meaning": "friend, companion, comrade, pal, accompaniment, companion (e.g. book), complement, accessory, affect"
    },
    {
      "question": "無意味",
      "answer": "むいみ",
      "meaning": "nonsense, no meaning, meaningless"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅刻",
      "answer": "ちこく",
      "meaning": "lateness, tardiness, arriving late"
    },
    {
      "question": "疲労",
      "answer": "ひろう",
      "meaning": "fatigue, weariness"
    },
    {
      "question": "臭い",
      "answer": "くさい,におい",
      "meaning": "stinking, smelly, suspicious, fishy, clumsy, unskilled, smelling of, looking like, appearing like, s"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き取る",
      "answer": "ひきとる",
      "meaning": "to take into one's possession, to receive, to accept, to collect, to claim, to take into one's care"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費",
      "answer": "しょうひ",
      "meaning": "consumption, expenditure"
    },
    {
      "question": "野",
      "answer": "の,や,ぬ",
      "meaning": "plain, field, hidden (structural) member, wild, lacking a political post"
    },
    {
      "question": "絆",
      "answer": "きずな,きづな",
      "meaning": "bonds (between people), (emotional) ties, relationship, connection, link, tether, fetters"
    },
    {
      "question": "庇う",
      "answer": "かばう",
      "meaning": "to protect (someone), to look after (e.g. an injured leg), to defend, to cover for, to stand up for,"
    },
    {
      "question": "支援",
      "answer": "しえん",
      "meaning": "support, backing, aid, assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉間",
      "answer": "みけん",
      "meaning": "brow, glabella, middle forehead, area between the eyebrows"
    },
    {
      "question": "領",
      "answer": "えり,りょう",
      "meaning": "collar, lapel, neckband, neck, nape of the neck, scruff of the neck, territory (of country, feudal d"
    },
    {
      "question": "進化",
      "answer": "しんか",
      "meaning": "evolution, progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "躊躇",
      "answer": "ちゅうちょ",
      "meaning": "hesitation, indecision, vacillation"
    },
    {
      "question": "自殺",
      "answer": "じさつ",
      "meaning": "suicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩める",
      "answer": "ゆるめる",
      "meaning": "to loosen, to slacken, to relax (attention, efforts, etc.), to let down (one's guard), to relieve (t"
    },
    {
      "question": "口に出す",
      "answer": "くちにだす",
      "meaning": "to express (orally), to put into words, to say out loud"
    },
    {
      "question": "神経",
      "answer": "しんけい",
      "meaning": "nerve, nerves, sensitivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪華",
      "answer": "ごうか",
      "meaning": "extravagant, lavish, opulent, luxurious, magnificent, splendid, fancy, gorgeous"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍋",
      "answer": "なべ",
      "meaning": "saucepan, pot, stew, hot pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "例外",
      "answer": "れいがい",
      "meaning": "exception"
    },
    {
      "question": "近付く",
      "answer": "ちかづく,ちかずく",
      "meaning": "to approach, to draw near, to get close, to get acquainted with, to get closer to, to get to know"
    },
    {
      "question": "田",
      "answer": "た",
      "meaning": "rice field"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦笑い",
      "answer": "にがわらい",
      "meaning": "bitter smile, wry smile, forced smile, strained laugh"
    },
    {
      "question": "本番",
      "answer": "ほんばん",
      "meaning": "performance, take, going before an audience or on-air, game, season, crucial moment, penetrative vag"
    },
    {
      "question": "上る",
      "answer": "あがる,のぼる",
      "meaning": "to rise, to go up, to come up, to ascend, to be raised, to enter (esp. from outdoors), to come in, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "残酷",
      "answer": "ざんこく",
      "meaning": "cruel, brutal, ruthless, merciless, inhuman"
    },
    {
      "question": "無邪気",
      "answer": "むじゃき",
      "meaning": "innocent, simple-minded"
    },
    {
      "question": "話し合い",
      "answer": "はなしあい",
      "meaning": "discussion, talk, tête-à-tête, conference"
    },
    {
      "question": "証言",
      "answer": "しょうげん",
      "meaning": "testimony, (verbal) evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "任す",
      "answer": "まかす",
      "meaning": "to entrust, to leave to a person"
    },
    {
      "question": "咲く",
      "answer": "さく",
      "meaning": "to bloom, to flower, to blossom, to open"
    },
    {
      "question": "勧める",
      "answer": "すすめる",
      "meaning": "to recommend (someone to do), to advise, to encourage, to urge, to recommend (a book, someone for a"
    },
    {
      "question": "高級",
      "answer": "こうきゅう",
      "meaning": "high class, high grade, high rank, seniority"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤独",
      "answer": "こどく",
      "meaning": "solitude, loneliness, isolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜る",
      "answer": "くぐる,もぐる,むぐる",
      "meaning": "to go under, to pass under, to go through, to pass through, to dive (into or under the water), to ev"
    },
    {
      "question": "到達",
      "answer": "とうたつ",
      "meaning": "reaching, attaining, arrival"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑い",
      "answer": "うたがい",
      "meaning": "doubt, question, uncertainty, skepticism, scepticism, suspicion, distrust"
    },
    {
      "question": "士",
      "answer": "さむらい,し",
      "meaning": "warrior (esp. of military retainers of daimyos in the Edo period), samurai, man (esp. one who is wel"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇る",
      "answer": "のぼる",
      "meaning": "to ascend, to go up, to climb, to ascend (as a natural process, e.g. the Sun), to rise, to go to (th"
    },
    {
      "question": "当日",
      "answer": "とうじつ",
      "meaning": "day in question, appointed day, that very day, the day (of issue, publication, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誇り",
      "answer": "ほこり",
      "meaning": "pride, boast, credit (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "容易",
      "answer": "ようい",
      "meaning": "easy, simple, plain"
    },
    {
      "question": "二階",
      "answer": "にかい",
      "meaning": "second floor, upstairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "何かしら",
      "answer": "なにかしら",
      "meaning": "somehow (or other), for some reason, without knowing why, something (or other), some ... or other"
    },
    {
      "question": "人質",
      "answer": "ひとじち",
      "meaning": "hostage"
    },
    {
      "question": "市",
      "answer": "いち,し",
      "meaning": "market, fair, city"
    },
    {
      "question": "地域",
      "answer": "ちいき",
      "meaning": "area, region"
    },
    {
      "question": "突入",
      "answer": "とつにゅう",
      "meaning": "rushing into, breaking into, storming, plunging into (war, etc.), embarking on (a new venture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖る",
      "answer": "とがる,とんがる",
      "meaning": "to taper to a point, to become pointed, to become sharp, to look displeased, to look sour, to be on"
    },
    {
      "question": "水着",
      "answer": "みずぎ",
      "meaning": "bathing suit, swimsuit, swimmers"
    },
    {
      "question": "確定",
      "answer": "かくてい",
      "meaning": "decision, settlement, definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱点",
      "answer": "じゃくてん",
      "meaning": "weak point, weakness, shortcoming, defect, flaw, sore spot, tender spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "最終",
      "answer": "さいしゅう",
      "meaning": "last, final, closing"
    },
    {
      "question": "近所",
      "answer": "きんじょ",
      "meaning": "neighbourhood, neighborhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "埋まる",
      "answer": "うまる,うずまる",
      "meaning": "to be buried, to be covered, to be surrounded, to overflow, to be crowded, to be filled, to be repai"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔面",
      "answer": "がんめん",
      "meaning": "face (of person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "案",
      "answer": "あん,つくえ",
      "meaning": "idea, plan, proposal, suggestion, (government) bill, draft, rough copy, expectation, desk, stand"
    },
    {
      "question": "心の底",
      "answer": "こころのそこ",
      "meaning": "bottom of one's heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "可哀想",
      "answer": "かわいそう",
      "meaning": "poor, pitiable, pathetic, pitiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち出す",
      "answer": "もちだす",
      "meaning": "to take out, to carry out, to bring out from where it belongs, to mention something, to broach a top"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗北",
      "answer": "はいぼく",
      "meaning": "defeat, to be defeated"
    },
    {
      "question": "遥か",
      "answer": "はるか",
      "meaning": "far, far away, distant, remote, far off"
    },
    {
      "question": "数々",
      "answer": "しばしば,かずかず",
      "meaning": "often, again and again, frequently, repeatedly, many, numerous, various, large number of"
    },
    {
      "question": "錯覚",
      "answer": "さっかく",
      "meaning": "optical illusion, hallucination, misapprehension, delusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "決まり",
      "answer": "きまり",
      "meaning": "rule, regulation, settlement, conclusion, end, agreement, arrangement, habit, custom, habitual way,"
    },
    {
      "question": "説教",
      "answer": "せっきょう",
      "meaning": "sermon, preaching, remonstration, scolding, lecturing"
    },
    {
      "question": "目に入る",
      "answer": "めにはいる",
      "meaning": "to catch sight of, to come into view, to happen to see"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩む",
      "answer": "あゆむ",
      "meaning": "to walk, to go on foot, to tread (a figurative path), to follow, to lead (a life), to experience, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "用いる",
      "answer": "もちいる",
      "meaning": "to use, to make use of, to utilize, to utilise"
    },
    {
      "question": "お帰り",
      "answer": "おかえり",
      "meaning": "return, welcome home"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱心",
      "answer": "ねっしん",
      "meaning": "zealous, enthusiastic, ardent, fervent, keen, eager"
    },
    {
      "question": "装置",
      "answer": "そうち",
      "meaning": "equipment, device, installation, apparatus, stage setting"
    },
    {
      "question": "団長",
      "answer": "だんちょう",
      "meaning": "leader of a delegation (body, party)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帽子",
      "answer": "ぼうし",
      "meaning": "hat, cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "深刻",
      "answer": "しんこく",
      "meaning": "serious, severe, grave, acute"
    },
    {
      "question": "砕く",
      "answer": "くだく",
      "meaning": "to break, to smash"
    },
    {
      "question": "電気",
      "answer": "でんき",
      "meaning": "electricity, (electric) light"
    },
    {
      "question": "次回",
      "answer": "じかい",
      "meaning": "next time (occasion)"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し込む",
      "answer": "さしこむ",
      "meaning": "to insert, to put in, to thrust in, to plug in, to have a griping pain, to flow in, to shine in"
    },
    {
      "question": "前世",
      "answer": "ぜんせ,ぜんせい",
      "meaning": "one's previous life, previous existence, antiquity, the previous era"
    },
    {
      "question": "職人",
      "answer": "しょくにん",
      "meaning": "craftsman, artisan, tradesman, worker, workman"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝動",
      "answer": "しょうどう",
      "meaning": "impulse, impetus, urge"
    },
    {
      "question": "一件",
      "answer": "いっけん",
      "meaning": "(one) matter, (one) item, (one) case"
    },
    {
      "question": "策",
      "answer": "さく,むち",
      "meaning": "plan, policy, means, measure, stratagem, scheme, fifth principle of the Eight Principles of Yong, ri"
    },
    {
      "question": "小学生",
      "answer": "しょうがくせい",
      "meaning": "elementary school student, primary school student, grade school student"
    },
    {
      "question": "習う",
      "answer": "ならう",
      "meaning": "to take lessons in, to be taught, to learn (from a teacher), to study (under a teacher), to get trai"
    },
    {
      "question": "平民",
      "answer": "へいみん",
      "meaning": "commoner, plebeian"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘇る",
      "answer": "よみがえる",
      "meaning": "to be resurrected, to be resuscitated, to be rehabilitated, to be revived, to be refreshed, to be re"
    },
    {
      "question": "状",
      "answer": "じょう,さま",
      "meaning": "form, shape, appearance, state, condition, circumstances, letter, correspondence, Mr., Mrs., Miss, M"
    },
    {
      "question": "潰れる",
      "answer": "つぶれる",
      "meaning": "to be crushed, to be smashed, to be broken, to collapse, to become useless, to cease functioning, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "王様",
      "answer": "おうさま",
      "meaning": "king"
    },
    {
      "question": "発展",
      "answer": "はってん",
      "meaning": "development, growth, expansion, extension, flourishing, development (of a situation, story, etc.), a"
    },
    {
      "question": "等しい",
      "answer": "ひとしい",
      "meaning": "equal, identical, the same, no different (to), just like, equivalent"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼓動",
      "answer": "こどう",
      "meaning": "beat, palpitation, pulsation, throbbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "載せる",
      "answer": "のせる",
      "meaning": "to place on (something), to give (someone) a ride, to give a lift, to pick up, to help on board, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "高",
      "answer": "たか,だか,こう",
      "meaning": "quantity, amount, volume, number, amount of money, high, high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "座",
      "answer": "ざ",
      "meaning": "seat, place, position, status, gathering, party, company, atmosphere (of a gathering), stand, pedest"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い切る",
      "answer": "おもいきる",
      "meaning": "to give up all thoughts of, to abandon, to despair of, to make up one's mind, to take a momentous de"
    },
    {
      "question": "減らす",
      "answer": "へらす",
      "meaning": "to abate, to decrease, to diminish, to shorten"
    },
    {
      "question": "掌",
      "answer": "てのひら,たなごころ,しょう",
      "meaning": "palm (of one's hand)"
    },
    {
      "question": "利く",
      "answer": "きく",
      "meaning": "to be effective, to take effect, to be good (for), to work, to function well, to be possible (to do,"
    },
    {
      "question": "咄嗟に",
      "answer": "とっさに",
      "meaning": "at once, right away, promptly, on the spur of the moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "目的地",
      "answer": "もくてきち",
      "meaning": "place of destination"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗議",
      "answer": "こうぎ",
      "meaning": "protest, objection"
    },
    {
      "question": "池",
      "answer": "いけ",
      "meaning": "pond"
    },
    {
      "question": "班",
      "answer": "はん",
      "meaning": "group, party, team, squad, section"
    },
    {
      "question": "国家",
      "answer": "こっか",
      "meaning": "state, country, nation"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺し",
      "answer": "ころし",
      "meaning": "murder, killing, murderer"
    },
    {
      "question": "権力",
      "answer": "けんりょく",
      "meaning": "(political) power, authority, influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "装う",
      "answer": "よそおう,よそう",
      "meaning": "to dress (oneself in), to attire oneself in, to adorn, to decorate, to pretend, to feign, to affect,"
    },
    {
      "question": "田舎",
      "answer": "いなか,でんしゃ,でんじゃ",
      "meaning": "rural area, countryside, the sticks, hometown, country, country home"
    },
    {
      "question": "無限",
      "answer": "むげん",
      "meaning": "infinity, infinitude, eternity, infinite, limitless"
    },
    {
      "question": "用件",
      "answer": "ようけん",
      "meaning": "business, thing to be done, something that should be performed, information that should be conveyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "脅す",
      "answer": "おどす",
      "meaning": "to threaten, to menace, to frighten (into doing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人差し指",
      "answer": "ひとさしゆび",
      "meaning": "index finger, forefinger"
    },
    {
      "question": "平然",
      "answer": "へいぜん",
      "meaning": "calm, composed, cool, quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "将軍",
      "answer": "しょうぐん",
      "meaning": "general, shogun"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔立ち",
      "answer": "かおだち",
      "meaning": "looks, features"
    },
    {
      "question": "係",
      "answer": "かかり,がかり",
      "meaning": "charge, duty, person in charge, official, clerk, connection, linking"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇帝",
      "answer": "こうてい,おうだい",
      "meaning": "emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "撮影",
      "answer": "さつえい",
      "meaning": "photography (still or motion), photographing, filming, shooting, (video) recording"
    },
    {
      "question": "演じる",
      "answer": "えんじる",
      "meaning": "to perform (a play), to play (a part), to act (a part), to commit (a blunder)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高まる",
      "answer": "たかまる",
      "meaning": "to rise, to swell, to be promoted"
    },
    {
      "question": "店内",
      "answer": "てんない",
      "meaning": "store interior, inside of a shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "降り注ぐ",
      "answer": "ふりそそぐ",
      "meaning": "to rain incessantly, to downpour"
    },
    {
      "question": "登録",
      "answer": "とうろく",
      "meaning": "registration, accession, register, entry, record"
    },
    {
      "question": "突撃",
      "answer": "とつげき",
      "meaning": "charge, rush, dash, assault, attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "孫",
      "answer": "まご,そん",
      "meaning": "grandchild, descendant (usu. of a certain generation), lineage, pedigree"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦い",
      "answer": "にがい",
      "meaning": "bitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "我に返る",
      "answer": "われにかえる",
      "meaning": "to come to one's senses, to calm down"
    },
    {
      "question": "二日",
      "answer": "ふつか",
      "meaning": "second day of the month, two days"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐る恐る",
      "answer": "おそるおそる",
      "meaning": "fearfully, timidly, nervously, cautiously, gingerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "高める",
      "answer": "たかめる",
      "meaning": "to raise, to lift, to boost, to enhance"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾",
      "answer": "たま,だん",
      "meaning": "ball, sphere, globe, orb, bead (of sweat, dew, etc.), drop, droplet, ball (in sports), pile (of nood"
    },
    {
      "question": "中学",
      "answer": "ちゅうがく",
      "meaning": "junior high school, middle school, lower secondary school"
    },
    {
      "question": "手配",
      "answer": "てはい",
      "meaning": "arrangement, preparations, search (by police)"
    },
    {
      "question": "発想",
      "answer": "はっそう",
      "meaning": "idea, conception, way of thinking, expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "不審",
      "answer": "ふしん",
      "meaning": "incomplete understanding, doubt, question, distrust, suspicion, strangeness, infidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "利益",
      "answer": "りえき,りやく",
      "meaning": "profit, gains, benefit, advantage, interest (of the public, etc.), grace (of God, Buddha, etc.) (esp"
    },
    {
      "question": "振る舞う",
      "answer": "ふるまう",
      "meaning": "to behave, to conduct oneself, to entertain, to treat someone (to a drink), to make tea for someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "反射的",
      "answer": "はんしゃてき",
      "meaning": "reflexive, reflecting"
    },
    {
      "question": "界",
      "answer": "さかい,かい",
      "meaning": "border, boundary, turning point, watershed, area, region, spot, space, environment, psychological st"
    },
    {
      "question": "二本",
      "answer": "にほん",
      "meaning": "two (long cylindrical things)"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り払う",
      "answer": "ふりはらう",
      "meaning": "to shake off"
    },
    {
      "question": "神殿",
      "answer": "しんでん",
      "meaning": "temple, sacred place, shrine, sanctuary, tabernacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩み寄る",
      "answer": "あゆみよる",
      "meaning": "to compromise, to meet halfway, to step up to, to walk up to, to approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰還",
      "answer": "きかん",
      "meaning": "repatriation, return, (electrical) feedback"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜む",
      "answer": "ひそむ",
      "meaning": "to lurk, to be hidden, to be concealed, to lie dormant, to be latent"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い放つ",
      "answer": "いいはなつ",
      "meaning": "to declare, to assert, to say bluntly, to say straight out"
    },
    {
      "question": "再現",
      "answer": "さいげん",
      "meaning": "reappearance, reemergence, return, revival, reproduction, reenactment, recreation"
    },
    {
      "question": "高度",
      "answer": "こうど",
      "meaning": "altitude, height, elevation, high-degree, high-grade, advanced, sophisticated, strong"
    },
    {
      "question": "光栄",
      "answer": "こうえい",
      "meaning": "honour, honor, glory, privilege"
    },
    {
      "question": "職業",
      "answer": "しょくぎょう",
      "meaning": "occupation, profession, job, vocation, trade, calling, business"
    },
    {
      "question": "向こう側",
      "answer": "むこうがわ",
      "meaning": "other side, opposite side, other party"
    },
    {
      "question": "支度",
      "answer": "したく",
      "meaning": "preparation, arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "割",
      "answer": "わり",
      "meaning": "rate, ratio, proportion, percentage, profit, assignment, 10%, unit of ten percent, match, schedule o"
    },
    {
      "question": "好意",
      "answer": "こうい",
      "meaning": "kindness, favor, favour, friendliness, goodwill, affection, liking (for someone), love"
    },
    {
      "question": "横たわる",
      "answer": "よこたわる",
      "meaning": "to lie down, to stretch out, to lie ahead (of danger, difficulty, etc.), to lie in wait"
    },
    {
      "question": "体内",
      "answer": "たいない",
      "meaning": "interior of the body"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜中",
      "answer": "よなか,やちゅう,よじゅう",
      "meaning": "middle of the night, dead of night, during the night, at night, all night, the whole night"
    },
    {
      "question": "捜査",
      "answer": "そうさ",
      "meaning": "search (esp. in criminal investigations), investigation, inquiry, enquiry"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜空",
      "answer": "よぞら",
      "meaning": "night sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "無力",
      "answer": "むりょく",
      "meaning": "powerlessness, helplessness, incompetent"
    },
    {
      "question": "同然",
      "answer": "どうぜん",
      "meaning": "similar to, same, right, proper, just, natural"
    },
    {
      "question": "深々",
      "answer": "ふかぶか,しんしん",
      "meaning": "very deeply, silent (esp. of the passing of the night), piercing (cold)"
    },
    {
      "question": "役立つ",
      "answer": "やくだつ",
      "meaning": "to be useful, to be helpful, to serve the purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "配る",
      "answer": "くばる",
      "meaning": "to distribute, to hand out, to deliver, to deal out, to serve out, to allot, to allocate, to place ("
    },
    {
      "question": "鎖",
      "answer": "くさり,じょう",
      "meaning": "chain, chains, lock, padlock, tablet, lozenge, pill"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い込む",
      "answer": "おもいこむ",
      "meaning": "to be convinced (that), to be under the impression (that), to feel sure (that), to assume (that), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍ら",
      "answer": "かたわら",
      "meaning": "side, edge, beside, besides, nearby, while (doing), in addition to, at the same time"
    },
    {
      "question": "流",
      "answer": "りゅう,る",
      "meaning": "fashion, way, style, manner, school (of thought), class, rank, rate, current (electrical, water, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "座り込む",
      "answer": "すわりこむ",
      "meaning": "to sit down (and refuse to move), to sit-in (in protest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣る",
      "answer": "つる",
      "meaning": "to fish, to angle, to catch, to lure in, to tempt, to attract, to entice, to allure"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾く",
      "answer": "かたむく,かたぶく,かぶく",
      "meaning": "to incline toward, to slant, to lurch, to heel over, to be disposed to, to trend toward, to be prone"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦しみ",
      "answer": "くるしみ",
      "meaning": "pain, anguish, distress, suffering, hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "不快",
      "answer": "ふかい",
      "meaning": "displeasure, discomfort, unpleasantness, indisposition, ailment"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭り",
      "answer": "まつり",
      "meaning": "festival, feast, harassment by an Internet pitchfork mob, online shaming, flaming, galore (as in 'go"
    },
    {
      "question": "家庭",
      "answer": "かてい",
      "meaning": "home, family, household"
    },
    {
      "question": "言動",
      "answer": "げんどう",
      "meaning": "speech and conduct, words and deeds"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁当",
      "answer": "べんとう",
      "meaning": "bento, Japanese box lunch"
    },
    {
      "question": "一時的",
      "answer": "いちじてき",
      "meaning": "temporary"
    },
    {
      "question": "実現",
      "answer": "じつげん",
      "meaning": "implementation (e.g. of a system), materialization, materialisation, realization, realisation, actua"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪",
      "answer": "あく,わる",
      "meaning": "evil, wickedness, (role of) the villain (in theatre, etc.), the bad guy, wicked person, evil person,"
    },
    {
      "question": "生意気",
      "answer": "なまいき",
      "meaning": "impertinent, saucy, cheeky, impudent, audacious, cocky, pert, brash"
    },
    {
      "question": "当主",
      "answer": "とうしゅ",
      "meaning": "(present) head of a family"
    },
    {
      "question": "小柄",
      "answer": "こがら,こづか,しょうへい",
      "meaning": "small build, small stature, petite, small pattern, knife attached to the sheath of a sword, sterigma"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷く",
      "answer": "しく",
      "meaning": "to spread out, to lay out, to take a position, to impose widely (e.g. over a city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気を遣う",
      "answer": "きをつかう",
      "meaning": "to pay attention to another's needs, to attend to, to fuss about, to take into consideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪",
      "answer": "りん,わ",
      "meaning": "counter for wheels and flowers, ring, circle, loop, hoop, wheel, circle (e.g. of friends)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前提",
      "answer": "ぜんてい",
      "meaning": "condition, assumption, prerequisite, hypothesis, intention, intent, aim, goal, premise (in logic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "記す",
      "answer": "しるす,きす",
      "meaning": "to write down, to note, to jot down, to remember"
    },
    {
      "question": "争う",
      "answer": "あらそう,あらがう",
      "meaning": "to compete, to contest, to contend, to quarrel, to argue, to dispute, to be at variance, to oppose,"
    },
    {
      "question": "中でも",
      "answer": "なかでも",
      "meaning": "among (other things), especially, particularly, inter alia, above all (else)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揃える",
      "answer": "そろえる",
      "meaning": "to collect, to gather, to get together, to complete (a collection), to arrange, to put in order, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "洞窟",
      "answer": "どうくつ",
      "meaning": "cavern, cave, cave system, grotto"
    },
    {
      "question": "混ざる",
      "answer": "まざる",
      "meaning": "to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with, to mingle with, to join"
    },
    {
      "question": "慕う",
      "answer": "したう",
      "meaning": "to yearn for, to long for, to pine for, to miss, to love dearly, to adore, to follow (someone), to i"
    },
    {
      "question": "着地",
      "answer": "ちゃくち",
      "meaning": "landing"
    },
    {
      "question": "砕ける",
      "answer": "くだける",
      "meaning": "to break (into pieces), to be broken, to be smashed, to collapse, to crumble, to decline, to cool (e"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞",
      "answer": "しんぶん",
      "meaning": "newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "恨み",
      "answer": "うらみ",
      "meaning": "resentment, grudge, malice, bitterness, matter for regret, regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "見失う",
      "answer": "みうしなう",
      "meaning": "to lose sight of, to miss"
    },
    {
      "question": "満面",
      "answer": "まんめん",
      "meaning": "(the) whole face"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮮やか",
      "answer": "あざやか",
      "meaning": "vivid, bright, brilliant, clear, fresh, vibrant, skillful, skilful, adept, adroit, deft, beautiful,"
    },
    {
      "question": "食",
      "answer": "しょく,じき,し",
      "meaning": "food, foodstuff, eating, appetite, meal, eclipse (solar, lunar, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "同時",
      "answer": "どうじ",
      "meaning": "simultaneous, concurrent, same time, synchronous, together"
    },
    {
      "question": "硬直",
      "answer": "こうちょく",
      "meaning": "stiffening, rigidity, rigor, stiffness, ossification, petrification"
    },
    {
      "question": "加減",
      "answer": "かげん",
      "meaning": "degree, extent, amount, balance, state, condition, (health) condition, state of health, adjustment,"
    },
    {
      "question": "構成",
      "answer": "こうせい",
      "meaning": "composition, construction, formation, makeup, structure, organization, organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "中庭",
      "answer": "なかにわ",
      "meaning": "courtyard, quadrangle, middle court"
    },
    {
      "question": "執事",
      "answer": "しつじ",
      "meaning": "steward, butler, court official, deacon (Anglican, Lutheran, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "横目",
      "answer": "よこめ",
      "meaning": "sidelong glance, short grain (paper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本人",
      "answer": "にほんじん,にっぽんじん",
      "meaning": "Japanese person, Japanese people"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨く",
      "answer": "みがく",
      "meaning": "to polish, to shine, to brush (e.g. teeth), to grind (e.g. lens), to refine (e.g. a skill), to impro"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢い",
      "answer": "かしこい",
      "meaning": "wise, clever, smart"
    },
    {
      "question": "頼もしい",
      "answer": "たのもしい",
      "meaning": "reliable, trustworthy, hopeful, promising"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴き声",
      "answer": "なきごえ",
      "meaning": "cry (esp. animal), roar, chirp, tweet, bark, whine, meow"
    },
    {
      "question": "幸福",
      "answer": "こうふく",
      "meaning": "happiness, well-being, joy, welfare, blessedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "長年",
      "answer": "ながねん",
      "meaning": "long time, many years"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉む",
      "answer": "もむ",
      "meaning": "to rub, to crumple, to massage, to argue, to have a heated discussion, to train, to coach, to jostle"
    },
    {
      "question": "何とも",
      "answer": "なんとも",
      "meaning": "really, very, extremely, terribly, awfully, (not) anything, (not) at all, (not) a bit"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝う",
      "answer": "つたう",
      "meaning": "to go along, to walk along, to follow"
    },
    {
      "question": "例え",
      "answer": "たとえ",
      "meaning": "example, simile, metaphor, allegory, fable, parable"
    },
    {
      "question": "加護",
      "answer": "かご",
      "meaning": "divine protection"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫌がらせ",
      "answer": "いやがらせ",
      "meaning": "harassment, pestering"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸収",
      "answer": "きゅうしゅう",
      "meaning": "absorption, suction, attraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "挑発",
      "answer": "ちょうはつ",
      "meaning": "provocation, stirring up, arousal, excitement, stimulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛",
      "answer": "け,もう",
      "meaning": "hair, fur, wool, down, plumage, feathers, one-thousandth, 0.03 mm (one-thousandth of a sun), 0.01 pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "手間",
      "answer": "てま",
      "meaning": "time, labour, labor"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺さる",
      "answer": "ささる",
      "meaning": "to stick into (of something with a sharp point), to prick, to pierce, to get stuck (in), to lodge (i"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆け出す",
      "answer": "かけだす",
      "meaning": "to run off, to break into a run, to start running"
    },
    {
      "question": "深夜",
      "answer": "しんや",
      "meaning": "late at night"
    },
    {
      "question": "何にも",
      "answer": "なんにも,なににも",
      "meaning": "(not) anything, (nothing) at all, (not) any, everything, all"
    },
    {
      "question": "来年",
      "answer": "らいねん",
      "meaning": "next year"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰掛ける",
      "answer": "こしかける",
      "meaning": "to sit (down)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠ざかる",
      "answer": "とおざかる",
      "meaning": "to go away, to become more distant, to fade away, to die away, to be estranged"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れる",
      "answer": "たれる,しだれる",
      "meaning": "to hang, to droop, to dangle, to sag, to lower, to pull down, to leave behind (at death), to give, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆弾",
      "answer": "ばくだん",
      "meaning": "bomb, alcohol with liquor added (esp. wine-based shōchū highball, also beer with whiskey)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀色",
      "answer": "ぎんいろ",
      "meaning": "silver (color, colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "財布",
      "answer": "さいふ",
      "meaning": "purse, handbag, wallet"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎年",
      "answer": "まいとし,まいねん",
      "meaning": "every year, yearly, annually"
    },
    {
      "question": "五十",
      "answer": "ごじゅう,いそ,い",
      "meaning": "fifty, 50"
    },
    {
      "question": "一種",
      "answer": "いっしゅ,ひとくさ",
      "meaning": "species, kind, variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "有効",
      "answer": "ゆうこう",
      "meaning": "valid, effective, yuko (judo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "改める",
      "answer": "あらためる",
      "meaning": "to change, to alter, to revise, to replace, to reform, to correct, to mend, to improve, to examine,"
    },
    {
      "question": "新人",
      "answer": "しんじん",
      "meaning": "new face, newcomer, rookie, fresh recruit, modern humans (from Cro-Magnon man onwards)"
    },
    {
      "question": "相性",
      "answer": "あいしょう",
      "meaning": "affinity, compatibility, chemistry (between people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕業",
      "answer": "しわざ",
      "meaning": "deed (esp. negative), act, action, one's doing"
    },
    {
      "question": "一点",
      "answer": "いってん",
      "meaning": "speck, dot, point, only a little, particle, only one"
    },
    {
      "question": "兄ちゃん",
      "answer": "にいちゃん,あんちゃん",
      "meaning": "(one's) older brother, young man, sonny, lad"
    },
    {
      "question": "見届ける",
      "answer": "みとどける",
      "meaning": "to make sure of, to assure oneself of, to see with one's own eyes, to ascertain"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪訝",
      "answer": "けげん",
      "meaning": "dubious, puzzled, suspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "快楽",
      "answer": "かいらく,けらく",
      "meaning": "pleasure, supreme pleasure obtained by freeing oneself from earthly desires"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘める",
      "answer": "ひめる",
      "meaning": "to hide, to keep to oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "横顔",
      "answer": "よこがお",
      "meaning": "profile, face in profile, face seen from the side, (personal) profile, (biographical) sketch, outlin"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り込む",
      "answer": "とりこむ",
      "meaning": "to take in, to bring in, to adopt (e.g. behaviour), to introduce, to capture (e.g. image), to import"
    },
    {
      "question": "余地",
      "answer": "よち",
      "meaning": "place, room, margin, scope"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き飛ぶ",
      "answer": "ふきとぶ",
      "meaning": "to be blown off, to blow off, to blow away, to vanish, to disappear"
    },
    {
      "question": "大型",
      "answer": "おおがた",
      "meaning": "large, large-sized, large-scale, big"
    },
    {
      "question": "横になる",
      "answer": "よこになる",
      "meaning": "to lie down (and rest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟子",
      "answer": "でし,ていし",
      "meaning": "pupil, disciple, adherent, follower, apprentice, young person, teacher's student-helper"
    },
    {
      "question": "課題",
      "answer": "かだい",
      "meaning": "subject, theme, issue, matter, homework, assignment, task, challenge, problem, question"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕飯",
      "answer": "ゆうはん,ゆうめし",
      "meaning": "evening meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "合格",
      "answer": "ごうかく",
      "meaning": "success, passing (e.g. exam), eligibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "風邪",
      "answer": "かぜ,ふうじゃ",
      "meaning": "(common) cold, influenza, flu, ague, inflammatory respiratory system illness (in general)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶叫",
      "answer": "ぜっきょう",
      "meaning": "scream, shriek, shout, exclamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "性質",
      "answer": "せいしつ",
      "meaning": "nature, property, disposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "割と",
      "answer": "わりと",
      "meaning": "relatively, comparatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "高速",
      "answer": "こうそく",
      "meaning": "high-speed, rapid, express, highway, freeway, expressway, motorway"
    },
    {
      "question": "到底",
      "answer": "とうてい",
      "meaning": "(cannot) possibly, (not) by any means, (not) at all, utterly, absolutely"
    },
    {
      "question": "拒む",
      "answer": "こばむ",
      "meaning": "to refuse, to reject, to decline, to prevent (from doing), to deny (e.g. access), to block"
    },
    {
      "question": "切ない",
      "answer": "せつない",
      "meaning": "painful, heartrending, trying, oppressive, suffocating, miserable"
    },
    {
      "question": "温泉",
      "answer": "おんせん",
      "meaning": "hot spring, onsen, hot spring resort, hot spring spa"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤む",
      "answer": "うるむ",
      "meaning": "to be wet, to be moist, to get dim, to become blurred, to get cloudy, to get muddy, to be bleared, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "喰う",
      "answer": "くう",
      "meaning": "to eat, to live, to make a living, to survive, to bite, to sting (as insects do), to tease, to torme"
    },
    {
      "question": "振動",
      "answer": "しんどう",
      "meaning": "oscillation, vibration, swing (e.g. of a pendulum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書",
      "answer": "ふみ,しょ",
      "meaning": "letter, writings, book, document, calligraphy (esp. Chinese), penmanship, handwriting, note"
    },
    {
      "question": "名誉",
      "answer": "めいよ",
      "meaning": "honor, honour, credit, prestige"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦り",
      "answer": "あせり",
      "meaning": "impatience"
    },
    {
      "question": "体温",
      "answer": "たいおん",
      "meaning": "temperature, body temperature (human, animal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "方針",
      "answer": "ほうしん",
      "meaning": "policy, course, plan (of action), principle, magnetic needle"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛しい",
      "answer": "いとしい,かなしい,うつくしい",
      "meaning": "lovely, dear, beloved, darling, dearest, pitiable, pitiful, sad, miserable, unhappy, sorrowful, lame"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀れ",
      "answer": "あわれ,あはれ",
      "meaning": "pity, sorrow, grief, misery, compassion, pathos, pitiable, pitiful, pathetic, miserable, alack, alas"
    },
    {
      "question": "起動",
      "answer": "きどう",
      "meaning": "startup, booting up, activation, starting (e.g. engine, computer), launch"
    },
    {
      "question": "決着",
      "answer": "けっちゃく",
      "meaning": "conclusion, decision, end, settlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "素振り",
      "answer": "そぶり,すぶり",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour, manner, attitude, bearing, practice-swinging (sword, bat, tennis racket, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中途半端",
      "answer": "ちゅうとはんぱ",
      "meaning": "halfway, half measures, unfinished, incomplete, by halves, half-baked, half-cocked, half-hearted, ha"
    },
    {
      "question": "知り合う",
      "answer": "しりあう",
      "meaning": "to get to know each other, to make acquaintance"
    },
    {
      "question": "拠点",
      "answer": "きょてん",
      "meaning": "position, location, base, point, site"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝室",
      "answer": "しんしつ",
      "meaning": "bedroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "看板",
      "answer": "かんばん",
      "meaning": "signboard, sign, billboard, hoarding, doorplate, draw, attraction, feature, highlight, spokesman, fi"
    },
    {
      "question": "先頭",
      "answer": "せんとう",
      "meaning": "head, lead, vanguard, first"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩る",
      "answer": "かる",
      "meaning": "to hunt (animals), to search (for a criminal), to go looking for (flowers, etc.), to gather (mushroo"
    },
    {
      "question": "根拠",
      "answer": "こんきょ",
      "meaning": "basis, foundation, grounds, authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰宅",
      "answer": "きたく",
      "meaning": "returning home"
    },
    {
      "question": "人目",
      "answer": "ひとめ,じんもく",
      "meaning": "public gaze, public notice, attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "干渉",
      "answer": "かんしょう",
      "meaning": "interference, intervention, meddling"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤ちゃん",
      "answer": "あかちゃん",
      "meaning": "baby, infant"
    },
    {
      "question": "最低限",
      "answer": "さいていげん",
      "meaning": "minimum, at the very least"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩",
      "answer": "しお,えん",
      "meaning": "salt (i.e. sodium chloride), common salt, table salt, salt (e.g. sodium chloride, calcium sulfate, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "履く",
      "answer": "はく",
      "meaning": "to put on (lower-body clothing, e.g. pants, skirt, footwear), to wear, to affix (a sword to one's hi"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰る",
      "answer": "おっしゃる",
      "meaning": "to say, to speak, to tell, to talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰す",
      "answer": "かえす,きす",
      "meaning": "to send (someone) back, to send (someone) home, to come to (in the end), to end in, to attribute, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "三年",
      "answer": "さんねん",
      "meaning": "three years"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃",
      "answer": "い",
      "meaning": "stomach, Chinese 'stomach' constellation (one of the 28 mansions)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不要",
      "answer": "ふよう",
      "meaning": "unnecessary, unneeded"
    },
    {
      "question": "試練",
      "answer": "しれん",
      "meaning": "test, trial, probation, ordeal, tribulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "角度",
      "answer": "かくど",
      "meaning": "angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "久々",
      "answer": "ひさびさ",
      "meaning": "(in a) long time, long time (ago), while (ago), long ago, long while (ago), (in a) long while"
    },
    {
      "question": "双子",
      "answer": "ふたご,そうし",
      "meaning": "twins, twin"
    },
    {
      "question": "親戚",
      "answer": "しんせき",
      "meaning": "relative, relation, kin"
    },
    {
      "question": "派遣",
      "answer": "はけん",
      "meaning": "dispatch, despatch, deployment, temporary employee (esp. from an agency), temporary worker, agency t"
    },
    {
      "question": "大胆",
      "answer": "だいたん",
      "meaning": "bold, daring, audacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "目に遭う",
      "answer": "めにあう",
      "meaning": "to go through, to suffer, to experience (something unpleasant)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全滅",
      "answer": "ぜんめつ",
      "meaning": "annihilation, total destruction, complete destruction, crushing defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "何事",
      "answer": "なにごと",
      "meaning": "what, what sort of thing, everything, anything, what (on earth)?, what's the meaning of this ...?, w"
    },
    {
      "question": "繰り出す",
      "answer": "くりだす",
      "meaning": "to draw (a thread), to let out (e.g. a rope), to head out as a group, to set out in large numbers, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "冒険",
      "answer": "ぼうけん",
      "meaning": "adventure, venture, venture which is unlikely to succeed, risky attempt, danger, hazard, risk"
    },
    {
      "question": "経る",
      "answer": "へる",
      "meaning": "to pass, to elapse, to go by, to pass through, to go through, to experience, to undergo"
    },
    {
      "question": "判明",
      "answer": "はんめい",
      "meaning": "establishing, proving, ascertaining, identifying, confirming"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い返す",
      "answer": "いいかえす",
      "meaning": "to talk back, to answer back, to retort, to reply, to respond, to say over, to repeat (what one has"
    },
    {
      "question": "別れ",
      "answer": "わかれ",
      "meaning": "parting, separation, farewell"
    },
    {
      "question": "静寂",
      "answer": "せいじゃく,しじま",
      "meaning": "silence, stillness, quietness"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰ぐ",
      "answer": "あおぐ",
      "meaning": "to look up (at), to look up to, to respect, to revere, to ask for (e.g. guidance), to seek, to turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪夢",
      "answer": "あくむ",
      "meaning": "nightmare, bad dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "効率",
      "answer": "こうりつ",
      "meaning": "efficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "締める",
      "answer": "しめる",
      "meaning": "to tie, to fasten, to tighten, to wear (necktie, belt), to put on, to total, to sum, to be strict wi"
    },
    {
      "question": "本部",
      "answer": "ほんぶ",
      "meaning": "headquarters, head office, main office"
    },
    {
      "question": "直撃",
      "answer": "ちょくげき",
      "meaning": "direct hit"
    },
    {
      "question": "覚醒",
      "answer": "かくせい",
      "meaning": "waking up, awakening, arousal, revival, disillusion, disillusionment"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷宮",
      "answer": "めいきゅう",
      "meaning": "labyrinth, maze, mystery"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄り添う",
      "answer": "よりそう",
      "meaning": "to get close, to cuddle close together, to nestle close to, to snuggle up to"
    },
    {
      "question": "心当たり",
      "answer": "こころあたり",
      "meaning": "having in mind, happening to know of, idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "別人",
      "answer": "べつじん,べつにん",
      "meaning": "different person, another person, someone else, changed man"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚れる",
      "answer": "ほれる",
      "meaning": "to fall in love, to be in love, to be charmed with, to lose one's heart to"
    },
    {
      "question": "方面",
      "answer": "ほうめん",
      "meaning": "direction, district, area, field (e.g. of study), sphere, quarter, aspect, angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "撤退",
      "answer": "てったい",
      "meaning": "evacuation, withdrawal, revocation, repeal, retreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "解消",
      "answer": "かいしょう",
      "meaning": "cancellation, liquidation, resolution, reduction (e.g. of stress)"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ暗",
      "answer": "まっくら",
      "meaning": "total darkness, pitch dark, bleak future, poor prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "店主",
      "answer": "てんしゅ",
      "meaning": "shopkeeper, storekeeper, proprietor of a shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "制限",
      "answer": "せいげん",
      "meaning": "restriction, restraint, limitation, limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "煽る",
      "answer": "あおる",
      "meaning": "to fan (oneself, flames, etc.), to flap (in the wind), to instigate, to stir up, to incite, to agita"
    },
    {
      "question": "物騒",
      "answer": "ぶっそう",
      "meaning": "dangerous, unsettled, troubled, disturbed, insecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "徹底的",
      "answer": "てっていてき",
      "meaning": "thorough, exhaustive, complete"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎回",
      "answer": "まいかい",
      "meaning": "every time, each round"
    },
    {
      "question": "値",
      "answer": "あたい,ち,ね",
      "meaning": "price, cost, value, worth, merit, level"
    },
    {
      "question": "解散",
      "answer": "かいさん",
      "meaning": "breaking up (e.g. meeting), dispersing (e.g. crowd), dissolving (company, organization, etc.), liqui"
    },
    {
      "question": "お土産",
      "answer": "おみやげ,おみあげ",
      "meaning": "local specialty or souvenir bought as a gift while travelling, present brought by a visitor, somethi"
    },
    {
      "question": "極めて",
      "answer": "きわめて",
      "meaning": "exceedingly, extremely, decisively"
    },
    {
      "question": "気楽",
      "answer": "きらく",
      "meaning": "carefree, comfortable, at ease, easygoing, happy-go-lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方",
      "answer": "ちほう,じかた",
      "meaning": "district, region, area, locality, the country, countryside, the provinces, rural area, civilian soci"
    },
    {
      "question": "捜索",
      "answer": "そうさく",
      "meaning": "search (esp. for someone or something missing), manhunt, legally authorized search of a person, buil"
    },
    {
      "question": "対峙",
      "answer": "たいじ",
      "meaning": "confrontation, standing facing each other (e.g. mountains, buildings), squaring off against (adversa"
    },
    {
      "question": "結婚式",
      "answer": "けっこんしき",
      "meaning": "marriage ceremony, wedding, nuptials"
    },
    {
      "question": "男爵",
      "answer": "だんしゃく",
      "meaning": "baron, Irish cobbler (variety of potato)"
    },
    {
      "question": "目当て",
      "answer": "めあて",
      "meaning": "mark, guide, landmark, purpose, aim, goal, intention, end, sight (on a firearm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "招待",
      "answer": "しょうたい,しょうだい",
      "meaning": "invitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "有利",
      "answer": "ゆうり",
      "meaning": "advantageous, favourable, better, stronger, profitable, lucrative, gainful, paying"
    },
    {
      "question": "生徒会",
      "answer": "せいとかい",
      "meaning": "student council"
    },
    {
      "question": "丘",
      "answer": "おか,つかさ",
      "meaning": "hill, height, knoll, rising ground, bonus points awarded to the winner at the end of a game, mound"
    },
    {
      "question": "恵まれる",
      "answer": "めぐまれる",
      "meaning": "to be blessed with, to be rich in, to abound in"
    },
    {
      "question": "放り込む",
      "answer": "ほうりこむ",
      "meaning": "to throw into, to toss into"
    },
    {
      "question": "監督",
      "answer": "かんとく",
      "meaning": "supervision, control, superintendence, direction, director, superintendent, supervisor, coach, forem"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊急",
      "answer": "きんきゅう",
      "meaning": "urgency, emergency"
    },
    {
      "question": "叫び声",
      "answer": "さけびごえ",
      "meaning": "shout, yell, scream"
    },
    {
      "question": "上司",
      "answer": "じょうし",
      "meaning": "(one's) superior, (one's) boss, the higher-ups"
    },
    {
      "question": "反射",
      "answer": "はんしゃ",
      "meaning": "reflection, reverberation, reflex, reflexes"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵意",
      "answer": "てきい",
      "meaning": "hostility, animosity, enmity"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲げる",
      "answer": "まげる",
      "meaning": "to bend, to crook, to bow, to curve, to curl, to lean, to tilt, to incline, to slant, to bend (the t"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼休み",
      "answer": "ひるやすみ",
      "meaning": "lunch break, noon recess, noon rest period"
    },
    {
      "question": "外出",
      "answer": "がいしゅつ,そとで",
      "meaning": "going out, outing, leaving (one's home, office, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "数年",
      "answer": "すうねん",
      "meaning": "several years, a few years"
    },
    {
      "question": "造る",
      "answer": "つくる",
      "meaning": "to make, to produce, to manufacture, to build, to construct, to prepare (food), to brew (alcohol), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "十年",
      "answer": "じゅうねん",
      "meaning": "ten years, decade"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅びる",
      "answer": "ほろびる",
      "meaning": "to go to ruin, to go under, to fall, to be destroyed, to die out, to become extinct, to perish"
    },
    {
      "question": "明かす",
      "answer": "あかす",
      "meaning": "to pass (the night), to spend, to reveal, to divulge, to disclose, to expose, to prove, to verify"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み出す",
      "answer": "ふみだす",
      "meaning": "to step forward, to step forth, to advance, to start, to embark on, to set forth on, to take steps t"
    },
    {
      "question": "放棄",
      "answer": "ほうき",
      "meaning": "abandonment, renunciation, resignation, abdication (responsibility, right)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗅ぐ",
      "answer": "かぐ",
      "meaning": "to sniff, to smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "上着",
      "answer": "うわぎ",
      "meaning": "coat, tunic, jacket, outer garment"
    },
    {
      "question": "死者",
      "answer": "ししゃ",
      "meaning": "dead person, (the) deceased, (the) dead, casualties"
    },
    {
      "question": "温度",
      "answer": "おんど",
      "meaning": "temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓶",
      "answer": "かめ,びん,へい",
      "meaning": "earthenware pot, bottle, jar, decanter, flagon, phial, vial, jar or vase with a long narrow neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "誕生",
      "answer": "たんじょう",
      "meaning": "birth, creation, formation"
    },
    {
      "question": "休日",
      "answer": "きゅうじつ",
      "meaning": "holiday, day off"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り囲む",
      "answer": "とりかこむ",
      "meaning": "to surround, to crowd around"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い返す",
      "answer": "おもいかえす",
      "meaning": "to re-think, to think back upon, to change one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "気遣い",
      "answer": "きづかい",
      "meaning": "consideration, concern, fear, worry, solicitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚い",
      "answer": "あつい",
      "meaning": "thick, deep, heavy, kind, cordial, hospitable, warm, faithful, abundant"
    },
    {
      "question": "限定",
      "answer": "げんてい",
      "meaning": "limit, restriction"
    },
    {
      "question": "無防備",
      "answer": "むぼうび",
      "meaning": "defenseless, defenceless, unprotected, vulnerable"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き返す",
      "answer": "ひきかえす",
      "meaning": "to turn back, to go back, to come back, to return, to retrace one's steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "重大",
      "answer": "じゅうだい",
      "meaning": "serious, important, significant, grave, weighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "身内",
      "answer": "みうち",
      "meaning": "relatives, one's family, friends, members of the same organization, followers, henchmen, one's whole"
    },
    {
      "question": "板",
      "answer": "いた",
      "meaning": "board, plank, sheet (of metal), plate (of glass), pane, slab, cutting board, chopping board, chef (e"
    },
    {
      "question": "惹く",
      "answer": "ひく",
      "meaning": "to draw (attention, sympathy, etc.), to attract (e.g. interest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭部",
      "answer": "とうぶ",
      "meaning": "head, cranium, cephalic"
    },
    {
      "question": "構造",
      "answer": "こうぞう",
      "meaning": "structure, construction, makeup, framework, organization, pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "気力",
      "answer": "きりょく",
      "meaning": "willpower, energy, vitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑誌",
      "answer": "ざっし",
      "meaning": "journal, magazine, periodical"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け継ぐ",
      "answer": "うけつぐ",
      "meaning": "to inherit, to succeed, to take over"
    },
    {
      "question": "年下",
      "answer": "としした",
      "meaning": "younger, junior"
    },
    {
      "question": "分厚い",
      "answer": "ぶあつい",
      "meaning": "bulky, massive, thick, heavy"
    },
    {
      "question": "支払う",
      "answer": "しはらう",
      "meaning": "to pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "思惑",
      "answer": "おもわく,しわく",
      "meaning": "expectation, anticipation, prediction, forecast, calculations, purpose, intention, motive, ulterior"
    },
    {
      "question": "俺様",
      "answer": "おれさま",
      "meaning": "I, me, self-centered man, egotistical man, pompous man"
    },
    {
      "question": "差す",
      "answer": "さす",
      "meaning": "to shine, to be visible, to be tinged with, to rise (of water levels), to flow in, to be felt (i.e."
    },
    {
      "question": "手加減",
      "answer": "てかげん",
      "meaning": "measuring by feel, adjusting by feel, doing by feel, knack, skill, adapting to the situation (one's"
    },
    {
      "question": "贅沢",
      "answer": "ぜいたく",
      "meaning": "luxury, extravagance, to live in luxury, to indulge oneself, lavish (use of something), abundant, co"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸命",
      "answer": "けんめい",
      "meaning": "eager, earnest, strenuous, fervent, assiduous, with utmost effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "下半身",
      "answer": "かはんしん,しもはんしん",
      "meaning": "lower half of the body"
    },
    {
      "question": "結末",
      "answer": "けつまつ",
      "meaning": "end, conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "連れ出す",
      "answer": "つれだす",
      "meaning": "to take (someone) out (for a walk, to lunch, etc.), to entice out, to lure away"
    },
    {
      "question": "独り言",
      "answer": "ひとりごと",
      "meaning": "soliloquy, monologue, speaking to oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化",
      "answer": "ぶんか",
      "meaning": "culture, civilization, civilisation, Bunka era (1804.2.11-1818.4.22)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い込む",
      "answer": "おいこむ",
      "meaning": "to herd, to drive, to chase, to corral, to corner, to force someone into doing, to go hard, to push"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨人",
      "answer": "きょじん",
      "meaning": "giant, great man, Tokyo Giants (baseball team)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本体",
      "answer": "ほんたい,ほんだい",
      "meaning": "substance, real form, main part, main unit, body (of a machine), this machine, this appliance, objec"
    },
    {
      "question": "質",
      "answer": "しつ,たち,しち",
      "meaning": "quality, value, nature, inherent quality, character, logical quality, nature (of a person), disposit"
    },
    {
      "question": "掘る",
      "answer": "ほる",
      "meaning": "to dig, to excavate, to hollow, to delve into, to dig up (e.g. vegetables), (for two men) to have an"
    },
    {
      "question": "繊細",
      "answer": "せんさい",
      "meaning": "dainty, delicate (e.g. fingers), fine, slim, sensitive, delicate (feelings, sense, etc.), subtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "国民",
      "answer": "こくみん,くにたみ",
      "meaning": "people (of a country), nation, citizen, national, people of a country"
    },
    {
      "question": "初日",
      "answer": "しょにち,しょじつ,はつひ",
      "meaning": "first day, opening day, New Year's Day sunrise"
    },
    {
      "question": "微笑",
      "answer": "びしょう",
      "meaning": "smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "番号",
      "answer": "ばんごう",
      "meaning": "number, series of digits"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼前",
      "answer": "がんぜん",
      "meaning": "before one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴染む",
      "answer": "なじむ",
      "meaning": "to become familiar with, to fit in, to adapt oneself, to get used to, to grow accustomed to"
    },
    {
      "question": "漆黒",
      "answer": "しっこく",
      "meaning": "jet black"
    },
    {
      "question": "不利",
      "answer": "ふり",
      "meaning": "disadvantage, handicap, unfavorable position"
    },
    {
      "question": "機嫌",
      "answer": "きげん",
      "meaning": "humour, humor, temper, mood, spirits, safety, health, well-being, one's situation, in a good mood, i"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍る",
      "answer": "こおる",
      "meaning": "to freeze, to be frozen over, to congeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳にする",
      "answer": "みみにする",
      "meaning": "to hear, to hear by chance, to hear by accident, to catch (the sound)"
    },
    {
      "question": "初対面",
      "answer": "しょたいめん",
      "meaning": "first meeting, first interview with"
    },
    {
      "question": "独特",
      "answer": "どくとく",
      "meaning": "peculiarity, uniqueness, characteristic"
    },
    {
      "question": "一致",
      "answer": "いっち",
      "meaning": "coincidence, agreement, union, match, conformity, consistency, cooperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "一通り",
      "answer": "ひととおり",
      "meaning": "generally, in the main, briefly (look over, explain, etc.), roughly, more or less, (more or less) ev"
    },
    {
      "question": "運",
      "answer": "うん",
      "meaning": "fortune, luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "何一つ",
      "answer": "なにひとつ",
      "meaning": "(not) one"
    },
    {
      "question": "事にする",
      "answer": "ことにする",
      "meaning": "to decide to, to pretend that, to make a practice of doing, to make it a rule to"
    },
    {
      "question": "異変",
      "answer": "いへん",
      "meaning": "unusual event, strange occurrence, strange phenomenon, something abnormal, change (for the worse), a"
    },
    {
      "question": "指揮",
      "answer": "しき",
      "meaning": "command, direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "励ます",
      "answer": "はげます",
      "meaning": "to encourage, to cheer, to raise (the voice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "神聖",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "holiness, sacredness, sanctity, dignity"
    },
    {
      "question": "大いに",
      "answer": "おおいに",
      "meaning": "very, much, greatly, a lot of"
    },
    {
      "question": "醜い",
      "answer": "みにくい",
      "meaning": "ugly, unattractive, unsightly, unseemly"
    },
    {
      "question": "無関係",
      "answer": "むかんけい",
      "meaning": "unrelated"
    },
    {
      "question": "小学校",
      "answer": "しょうがっこう",
      "meaning": "primary school, elementary school, grade school"
    },
    {
      "question": "足る",
      "answer": "たる",
      "meaning": "to be sufficient, to be enough, to be worth doing, to be worthy of, to deserve, to do (the job), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "職員",
      "answer": "しょくいん",
      "meaning": "staff member, personnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼ねる",
      "answer": "かねる",
      "meaning": "to be unable to, to find difficult (unpleasant, awkward, painful) to do, to serve two or more functi"
    },
    {
      "question": "小屋",
      "answer": "こや,しょうおく",
      "meaning": "hut, cabin, shed, (animal) pen, small theatre (theater), temporary playhouse, circus tent, booth, on"
    },
    {
      "question": "収穫",
      "answer": "しゅうかく",
      "meaning": "harvest, crop, ingathering, fruits (of one's labors), gain, result, returns"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き",
      "answer": "ぬき",
      "meaning": "leaving out, omitting, skipping, dispensing with, (beating) in succession, in a row"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱る",
      "answer": "よわる",
      "meaning": "to weaken, to grow weak, to wane, to decline (of one's health), to be downcast, to be dejected, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "集合",
      "answer": "しゅうごう",
      "meaning": "meeting up, gathering, assembly, set"
    },
    {
      "question": "多数",
      "answer": "たすう",
      "meaning": "large number (of), many, majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "劣る",
      "answer": "おとる",
      "meaning": "to be inferior to, to be less good at, to fall behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "分析",
      "answer": "ぶんせき",
      "meaning": "analysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝視",
      "answer": "ぎょうし",
      "meaning": "stare, gaze, fixation"
    },
    {
      "question": "親指",
      "answer": "おやゆび",
      "meaning": "thumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "面々",
      "answer": "めんめん",
      "meaning": "every person, each one, everybody"
    },
    {
      "question": "列",
      "answer": "れつ",
      "meaning": "row, line, file, column, queue, rank, procession, company (of someone), group, ranks, sequence, coun"
    },
    {
      "question": "交流",
      "answer": "こうりゅう",
      "meaning": "(cultural) exchange, interchange, interaction, (inter-) mingling, (social, etc.) networking, interco"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷地",
      "answer": "しきち",
      "meaning": "site, plot, lot, grounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "億",
      "answer": "おく",
      "meaning": "10^8, 100,000,000, hundred million"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉ざす",
      "answer": "とざす",
      "meaning": "to shut, to close, to fasten, to lock, to block (a street, entrance, etc.), to shut in (with snow, i"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫力",
      "answer": "はくりょく",
      "meaning": "impressiveness, impact, force, intensity, appeal, strength, punch, edge, vigor"
    },
    {
      "question": "患者",
      "answer": "かんじゃ",
      "meaning": "patient"
    },
    {
      "question": "生地",
      "answer": "きじ,せいち",
      "meaning": "cloth, fabric, material, texture, dough, batter, inherent quality, one's true character, one's true"
    },
    {
      "question": "金額",
      "answer": "きんがく",
      "meaning": "amount of money"
    },
    {
      "question": "在る",
      "answer": "ある",
      "meaning": "to be, to exist, to live, to have, to be located, to be equipped with, to happen, to come about"
    },
    {
      "question": "位",
      "answer": "くらい,い",
      "meaning": "throne, crown, (nobleman's) seat, government position, court rank, social standing, rank, class, ech"
    },
    {
      "question": "進行",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "moving forward (e.g. vehicle), onward movement, advance (work, procedure, etc.), advancement, progre"
    },
    {
      "question": "愉快",
      "answer": "ゆかい",
      "meaning": "pleasant, delightful, enjoyable, joyful, cheerful, amusing, happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "察知",
      "answer": "さっち",
      "meaning": "sense, infer"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞼",
      "answer": "まぶた,まなぶた",
      "meaning": "eyelid"
    },
    {
      "question": "股間",
      "answer": "こかん",
      "meaning": "nether region, between the legs, groin, crotch"
    },
    {
      "question": "建てる",
      "answer": "たてる",
      "meaning": "to build, to construct"
    },
    {
      "question": "頼り",
      "answer": "たより",
      "meaning": "reliance, dependence"
    },
    {
      "question": "小娘",
      "answer": "こむすめ",
      "meaning": "young girl, lass, adolescent female"
    },
    {
      "question": "比較的",
      "answer": "ひかくてき",
      "meaning": "comparatively, relatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞬時",
      "answer": "しゅんじ",
      "meaning": "instant, moment, (split) second, (in a) flash, (in the) blink of an eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "強める",
      "answer": "つよめる",
      "meaning": "to strengthen, to emphasize, to emphasise"
    },
    {
      "question": "騒動",
      "answer": "そうどう",
      "meaning": "strife, riot, rebellion, turmoil, (media) uproar, brouhaha, (public) outcry, scandal, controversy, f"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務所",
      "answer": "じむしょ",
      "meaning": "office"
    },
    {
      "question": "健康",
      "answer": "けんこう",
      "meaning": "health, healthy, sound, fit, wholesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "手続き",
      "answer": "てつづき",
      "meaning": "procedure, process, proceedings, formalities"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘拐",
      "answer": "ゆうかい",
      "meaning": "abduction, kidnapping, kidnaping"
    },
    {
      "question": "好奇心",
      "answer": "こうきしん",
      "meaning": "curiosity, inquisitiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "外部",
      "answer": "がいぶ",
      "meaning": "outside (e.g. of a building), exterior, outside (of a group, company, etc.), outside world"
    },
    {
      "question": "職",
      "answer": "しょく,そく,しき",
      "meaning": "job, work, employment, occupation, position, duties, trade, skill, agency (government department bet"
    },
    {
      "question": "解釈",
      "answer": "かいしゃく",
      "meaning": "explanation, interpretation"
    },
    {
      "question": "余る",
      "answer": "あまる",
      "meaning": "to remain, to be left over, to be in excess, to be too many"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑色",
      "answer": "みどりいろ,りょくしょく",
      "meaning": "green, emerald green, green color of new foliage, verdure"
    },
    {
      "question": "使命",
      "answer": "しめい",
      "meaning": "mission, errand, task, duty, obligation"
    },
    {
      "question": "一角",
      "answer": "いっかく,ひとかど,いっかど",
      "meaning": "corner, section, point, part, one horn, narwhal (Monodon monoceros), a cut above the rest, superior,"
    },
    {
      "question": "年頃",
      "answer": "としごろ",
      "meaning": "approximate age, apparent age, marriageable age (esp. of a woman), age of maturity, age of adulthood"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴り響く",
      "answer": "なりひびく",
      "meaning": "to reverberate, to resound, to echo, to have one's fame spread, to be renowned"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗賊",
      "answer": "とうぞく",
      "meaning": "thief, robber, burglar, bandit"
    },
    {
      "question": "兄妹",
      "answer": "けいまい,きょうだい",
      "meaning": "older brother and younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "何だって",
      "answer": "なんだって",
      "meaning": "what?!, what did you say?!, why?, what for?, for what reason?, anyone, anything"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕込む",
      "answer": "しこむ",
      "meaning": "to train, to teach, to educate, to acquire (information), to learn, to cram, to stock, to stock up o"
    },
    {
      "question": "住民",
      "answer": "じゅうみん",
      "meaning": "inhabitant, resident, citizen, population"
    },
    {
      "question": "爽やか",
      "answer": "さわやか",
      "meaning": "fresh, refreshing, invigorating, clear (e.g. voice), fluent, eloquent"
    },
    {
      "question": "向き",
      "answer": "むき",
      "meaning": "direction, orientation, aspect, exposure, suited to, suitable for, designed for, tendency, inclinati"
    },
    {
      "question": "力を貸す",
      "answer": "ちからをかす",
      "meaning": "to assist, to help out"
    },
    {
      "question": "裂く",
      "answer": "さく",
      "meaning": "to tear, to rip up, to cut up, to cleave, to cut open (esp. the abdomen), to forcibly separate (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "噴き出す",
      "answer": "ふきだす",
      "meaning": "to spout out, to spurt out, to gush out, to jet out, to sprout, to bud, to burst into laughter, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "浸る",
      "answer": "ひたる",
      "meaning": "to be soaked in, to be flooded, to be submerged, to be immersed in (joy, memories, alcohol, etc.), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "披露",
      "answer": "ひろう",
      "meaning": "announcement, presentation, demonstration, displaying, showing, introducing, exhibiting, unveiling,"
    },
    {
      "question": "親切",
      "answer": "しんせつ",
      "meaning": "kind, gentle, considerate, generous, friendly, nice"
    },
    {
      "question": "配慮",
      "answer": "はいりょ",
      "meaning": "consideration, concern, attention, thoughtfulness, making arrangements, care, trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "演奏",
      "answer": "えんそう",
      "meaning": "musical performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "警告",
      "answer": "けいこく",
      "meaning": "warning, advice"
    },
    {
      "question": "不安定",
      "answer": "ふあんてい",
      "meaning": "instability, insecurity, crankiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "順番",
      "answer": "じゅんばん",
      "meaning": "turn (in line), order of things, sequential order"
    },
    {
      "question": "街道",
      "answer": "かいどう",
      "meaning": "highway (esp. one existing from the Edo period), main road, highway (e.g. to success), path (to beco"
    },
    {
      "question": "英語",
      "answer": "えいご",
      "meaning": "English (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "憎い",
      "answer": "にくい",
      "meaning": "hateful, abominable, poor-looking, detestable, amazing, fantastic, admirable, lovely, wonderful"
    },
    {
      "question": "武装",
      "answer": "ぶそう",
      "meaning": "arms, armament"
    },
    {
      "question": "人格",
      "answer": "じんかく",
      "meaning": "personality, character, individuality, personhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "相棒",
      "answer": "あいぼう",
      "meaning": "partner, pal, accomplice"
    },
    {
      "question": "見学",
      "answer": "けんがく",
      "meaning": "inspection, study by observation, field trip, tour, review"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘆く",
      "answer": "なげく",
      "meaning": "to lament, to grieve, to regret, to deplore"
    },
    {
      "question": "曇る",
      "answer": "くもる,くぐもる",
      "meaning": "to get cloudy, to cloud over, to become overcast, to cloud up, to fog up, to mist up, to become dim,"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み取る",
      "answer": "よみとる",
      "meaning": "to read and understand, to take in, to sense from external cues, to read (someone's) mind, to read ("
    },
    {
      "question": "卿",
      "answer": "きょう,けい",
      "meaning": "Lord, Sir, state minister (under the ritsuryo system), you (in reference to someone of lower status)"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮かれる",
      "answer": "うかれる",
      "meaning": "to make merry, to be festive"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り出す",
      "answer": "きりだす",
      "meaning": "to quarry, to cut (timber), to cut and carry off, to begin to talk, to break the ice, to broach, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "友情",
      "answer": "ゆうじょう",
      "meaning": "friendship, fellowship, camaraderie"
    },
    {
      "question": "自転車",
      "answer": "じてんしゃ,じでんしゃ",
      "meaning": "bicycle, bike"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦しめる",
      "answer": "くるしめる",
      "meaning": "to torment, to pain, to inflict (physical) pain, to hurt, to harass, to cause (emotional) pain, to a"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗う",
      "answer": "あらがう",
      "meaning": "to go against, to fight against, to oppose, to resist, to deny"
    },
    {
      "question": "阻止",
      "answer": "そし",
      "meaning": "obstruction, check, hindrance, prevention, impediment, interdiction, preemption, blocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "大騒ぎ",
      "answer": "おおさわぎ",
      "meaning": "clamour, clamor, uproar, tumult, furore, furor"
    },
    {
      "question": "留める",
      "answer": "とめる,とどめる",
      "meaning": "to stop, to turn off, to park, to prevent, to suppress (a cough), to hold back (tears), to hold (one"
    },
    {
      "question": "手入れ",
      "answer": "ていれ",
      "meaning": "care, looking after, repair, maintenance, tending, trimming, grooming, (police) raid, crackdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛",
      "answer": "うし,ぎゅう",
      "meaning": "cattle (Bos taurus), cow, bull, ox, calf, beef, Chinese 'Ox' constellation (one of the 28 mansions)"
    },
    {
      "question": "卑怯",
      "answer": "ひきょう",
      "meaning": "cowardice, meanness, unfairness"
    },
    {
      "question": "優勝",
      "answer": "ゆうしょう",
      "meaning": "overall victory, championship"
    },
    {
      "question": "行方不明",
      "answer": "ゆくえふめい",
      "meaning": "missing (of a person), lost, unaccounted for, whereabouts unknown"
    },
    {
      "question": "一晩",
      "answer": "ひとばん",
      "meaning": "one night, one evening, all night, overnight"
    },
    {
      "question": "溺れる",
      "answer": "おぼれる",
      "meaning": "to struggle in the water, to sink below the surface and become unable to breathe, to (nearly) drown,"
    },
    {
      "question": "呟き",
      "answer": "つぶやき",
      "meaning": "murmur, mutter, murmuring, tweet, Twitter post"
    },
    {
      "question": "斜め",
      "answer": "ななめ,なのめ",
      "meaning": "slanting, tilted, sloping, diagonal, oblique, distorted (feeling), slanted (e.g. view of the world),"
    },
    {
      "question": "勢力",
      "answer": "せいりょく",
      "meaning": "influence, power, might, strength, potency, force, energy"
    },
    {
      "question": "発射",
      "answer": "はっしゃ",
      "meaning": "firing (esp. a rocket or missile), launching, shooting, discharge, catapult, ejaculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "枕",
      "answer": "まくら",
      "meaning": "pillow, bolster, introduction (e.g. to a rakugo story), lead-in"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕留める",
      "answer": "しとめる",
      "meaning": "to bring down (an animal, opponent, etc.), to kill, to shoot dead, to shoot down"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧",
      "answer": "けしょう,けわい,けそう",
      "meaning": "make-up, makeup, cosmetics"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗殺",
      "answer": "あんさつ",
      "meaning": "assassination"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐性",
      "answer": "たいせい",
      "meaning": "resistance (e.g. to antibiotics), tolerance (e.g. drug tolerance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "文字通り",
      "answer": "もじどおり",
      "meaning": "literal, literally"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に",
      "answer": "しに",
      "meaning": "dying, death, dead, useless, damned"
    },
    {
      "question": "無礼",
      "answer": "ぶれい",
      "meaning": "impolite, rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "他国",
      "answer": "たこく",
      "meaning": "foreign country, other country, another province, strange land, alien land"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り",
      "answer": "ふり,ぶり",
      "meaning": "swing, shake, wave, swinging, appearance, behaviour, pretence (pretense), show, pretending (to), goi"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊",
      "answer": "くま",
      "meaning": "bear (any mammal of family Ursidae)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後半",
      "answer": "こうはん",
      "meaning": "second half, latter half"
    },
    {
      "question": "像",
      "answer": "ぞう",
      "meaning": "image, figure, statue, picture, portrait, form, shape, appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "入手",
      "answer": "にゅうしゅ",
      "meaning": "acquisition, obtaining, coming to hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "象徴",
      "answer": "しょうちょう",
      "meaning": "(abstract) symbol, emblem, representation"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜り込む",
      "answer": "もぐりこむ",
      "meaning": "to slip into, to crawl into (under), to conceal oneself (under), to sneak into, to infiltrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "制する",
      "answer": "せいする",
      "meaning": "to hold back (e.g. emotions), to rein in (e.g. a horse, unruly people), to bridle, to get the better"
    },
    {
      "question": "意地",
      "answer": "いじ",
      "meaning": "stubbornness, obstinacy, willpower, pride, disposition, nature, appetite, desire, greed"
    },
    {
      "question": "試みる",
      "answer": "こころみる",
      "meaning": "to try, to attempt, to have a go (at something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最期",
      "answer": "さいご",
      "meaning": "one's last moment, one's death, one's end"
    },
    {
      "question": "肘",
      "answer": "ひじ",
      "meaning": "elbow"
    },
    {
      "question": "矛盾",
      "answer": "むじゅん",
      "meaning": "contradiction, inconsistency"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱す",
      "answer": "みだす",
      "meaning": "to throw into disorder, to disarrange, to disturb (order, peace, etc.), to corrupt (public morals),"
    },
    {
      "question": "遭う",
      "answer": "あう",
      "meaning": "to meet, to encounter, to see, to have an accident, to have a bad experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺人",
      "answer": "さつじん",
      "meaning": "murder, homicide, manslaughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "太る",
      "answer": "ふとる",
      "meaning": "to put on weight, to gain weight, to grow fat, to get stout"
    },
    {
      "question": "受付",
      "answer": "うけつけ",
      "meaning": "reception (desk), information desk, receipt, acceptance"
    },
    {
      "question": "息をつく",
      "answer": "いきをつく",
      "meaning": "to take a breath, to take a short rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "一員",
      "answer": "いちいん",
      "meaning": "person, member"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙目",
      "answer": "なみだめ",
      "meaning": "teary eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "教授",
      "answer": "きょうじゅ",
      "meaning": "professor, teaching, instruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "処刑",
      "answer": "しょけい",
      "meaning": "execution"
    },
    {
      "question": "退治",
      "answer": "たいじ",
      "meaning": "extermination (e.g. of pests, demons, bandits), elimination, eradication, destruction, suppression,"
    },
    {
      "question": "逮捕",
      "answer": "たいほ",
      "meaning": "arrest, apprehension, capture"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭",
      "answer": "まつり",
      "meaning": "festival, feast, harassment by an Internet pitchfork mob, online shaming, flaming, galore (as in 'go"
    },
    {
      "question": "広まる",
      "answer": "ひろまる",
      "meaning": "to spread, to be propagated"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺体",
      "answer": "いたい",
      "meaning": "corpse, remains"
    },
    {
      "question": "花火",
      "answer": "はなび",
      "meaning": "fireworks"
    },
    {
      "question": "中止",
      "answer": "ちゅうし",
      "meaning": "suspension, stoppage, discontinuance, interruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉大",
      "answer": "いだい",
      "meaning": "great, grand, magnificent, outstanding, mighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾む",
      "answer": "はずむ",
      "meaning": "to spring, to bound, to bounce, to be stimulated, to be encouraged, to get lively, to pay handsomely"
    },
    {
      "question": "神社",
      "answer": "じんじゃ,じんしゃ",
      "meaning": "Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "谷",
      "answer": "たに",
      "meaning": "valley"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗濯",
      "answer": "せんたく,せんだく",
      "meaning": "washing, laundry, relaxing, taking a break"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙り込む",
      "answer": "だまりこむ",
      "meaning": "to say no more, to sink into silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "物体",
      "answer": "ぶったい,もったい",
      "meaning": "body, object, superior airs, air of importance, overemphasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮膚",
      "answer": "ひふ",
      "meaning": "skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "借金",
      "answer": "しゃっきん",
      "meaning": "debt, loan, liabilities, borrowing money"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶",
      "answer": "ちゃ",
      "meaning": "tea, tea plant (Camellia sinensis), tea preparation, making tea, brown, mockery"
    },
    {
      "question": "現代",
      "answer": "げんだい",
      "meaning": "nowadays, modern era, modern times, present-day"
    },
    {
      "question": "左腕",
      "answer": "さわん,ひだりうで",
      "meaning": "left arm, left-handed (baseball pitcher)"
    },
    {
      "question": "解る",
      "answer": "わかる",
      "meaning": "to understand, to comprehend, to grasp, to see, to get, to follow, to become clear, to be known, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "降ろす",
      "answer": "おろす",
      "meaning": "to take down, to bring down, to lower (a hand, flag, shutter, etc.), to drop (an anchor, curtain, et"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂糖",
      "answer": "さとう",
      "meaning": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "整備",
      "answer": "せいび",
      "meaning": "maintenance, servicing, putting in place, establishment, development, preparation, provision, outfit"
    },
    {
      "question": "薔薇",
      "answer": "ばら,しょうび,そうび",
      "meaning": "rose"
    },
    {
      "question": "以内",
      "answer": "いない",
      "meaning": "within, inside of, less than"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を貸す",
      "answer": "てをかす",
      "meaning": "to lend a hand, to help"
    },
    {
      "question": "上等",
      "answer": "じょうとう",
      "meaning": "superior, first-class, excellent, top quality, (that's) just fine!, bring it on!"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち込む",
      "answer": "うちこむ,ぶちこむ",
      "meaning": "to drive in (e.g. nail, stake), to hammer in, to hit (a ball, etc.), to drive, to smash, to fire int"
    },
    {
      "question": "放り出す",
      "answer": "ほうりだす,ひりだす",
      "meaning": "to throw out, to drop, to toss, to dump, to abandon, to neglect, to leave behind, to give up, to dis"
    },
    {
      "question": "滞在",
      "answer": "たいざい",
      "meaning": "stay, sojourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き込む",
      "answer": "たたきこむ",
      "meaning": "to drive into (e.g. a nail into a board), to hit into (e.g. a home run into the stands), to throw in"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕組み",
      "answer": "しくみ",
      "meaning": "structure, construction, arrangement, contrivance, mechanism, workings, plan, plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮気",
      "answer": "うわき",
      "meaning": "extramarital sex, affair, fooling around, infidelity, wantonness, unfaithfulness, inconstancy, fickl"
    },
    {
      "question": "割に",
      "answer": "わりに",
      "meaning": "comparatively, relatively, pretty, rather, unexpectedly, unusually, considering, for one's ..., for"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制",
      "answer": "きょうせい",
      "meaning": "compulsion, coercion, forcing (to do), enforcement"
    },
    {
      "question": "転がす",
      "answer": "ころがす",
      "meaning": "to roll, to turn over, to tip over, to throw down, to leave, to buy and sell (quickly for a profit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "破れる",
      "answer": "われる,やぶれる",
      "meaning": "to break, to be smashed, to split, to crack, to fissure, to be torn, to be divided (opinion, vote, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "治癒",
      "answer": "ちゆ",
      "meaning": "healing, cure, recovery"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺意",
      "answer": "さつい",
      "meaning": "intent to kill, intent to murder, urge to kill, murderous impulse"
    },
    {
      "question": "美女",
      "answer": "びじょ,びんじょ",
      "meaning": "beautiful woman, lady attendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が家",
      "answer": "わがや,わがいえ",
      "meaning": "one's house, one's home, one's family"
    },
    {
      "question": "共通",
      "answer": "きょうつう",
      "meaning": "common, shared, mutual, to be common (to), to be shared (by), -wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "涼しい",
      "answer": "すずしい",
      "meaning": "cool, refreshing, clear (e.g. eyes), bright, clear, distinct, composed (facial expression), unruffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "性能",
      "answer": "せいのう",
      "meaning": "ability, performance, efficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "水面",
      "answer": "すいめん,みなも",
      "meaning": "water's surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "代物",
      "answer": "しろもの,だいぶつ",
      "meaning": "article, goods, product, fine thing, fellow, affair, stuff, prostitute, price, cost, money, substitu"
    },
    {
      "question": "何しろ",
      "answer": "なにしろ",
      "meaning": "at any rate, anyhow, anyway, in any case, because, as you know, for you see"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑事",
      "answer": "けいじ",
      "meaning": "(police) detective, criminal matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "学院",
      "answer": "がくいん",
      "meaning": "institute, academy"
    },
    {
      "question": "賑やか",
      "answer": "にぎやか",
      "meaning": "bustling, busy, lively"
    },
    {
      "question": "物音",
      "answer": "ものおと",
      "meaning": "sounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "憎しみ",
      "answer": "にくしみ",
      "meaning": "hatred"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺気",
      "answer": "さっき",
      "meaning": "thirst for blood, bloodlust, determination to kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "傘",
      "answer": "かさ,からかさ",
      "meaning": "umbrella, parasol, something shaped like an umbrella or a conical hat, shade (of a lamp), mushroom c"
    },
    {
      "question": "台所",
      "answer": "だいどころ,だいどこ",
      "meaning": "kitchen, financial situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "変身",
      "answer": "へんしん",
      "meaning": "metamorphosis, disguise, transformation, shapeshifting, morphing"
    },
    {
      "question": "定める",
      "answer": "さだめる",
      "meaning": "to decide, to determine, to establish, to lay down, to prescribe, to provide, to stipulate, to bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "要請",
      "answer": "ようせい",
      "meaning": "appeal, call for something, request, claim, demand, axiom"
    },
    {
      "question": "決定的",
      "answer": "けっていてき",
      "meaning": "definite, final, decisive, conclusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛行",
      "answer": "ひこう,ひぎょう",
      "meaning": "aviation, flight, flying, to fly, to take a flight, flying without hindrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "痙攣",
      "answer": "けいれん",
      "meaning": "convulsion, cramp, spasm, tic, twitch, fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫",
      "answer": "むらさき",
      "meaning": "purple, violet, Lithospermum erythrorhizon (species of gromwell), type of soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡",
      "answer": "あわ,あぶく",
      "meaning": "bubble, foam, froth, head on beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "正気",
      "answer": "しょうき,せいき",
      "meaning": "sanity, consciousness, soberness, true character, true heart, true spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "結果的",
      "answer": "けっかてき",
      "meaning": "concerning the result (as opposed to the means used to achieve this result or the original goal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "了承",
      "answer": "りょうしょう",
      "meaning": "acknowledgement, acknowledgment, understanding (e.g. 'please be understanding of the mess during our"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬草",
      "answer": "やくそう",
      "meaning": "medicinal herb"
    },
    {
      "question": "重力",
      "answer": "じゅうりょく",
      "meaning": "gravity, gravitation, gravitational pull"
    },
    {
      "question": "消耗",
      "answer": "しょうもう,しょうこう",
      "meaning": "exhaustion, consumption, using up, dissipation, waste"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕掛け",
      "answer": "しかけ",
      "meaning": "device, contrivance, mechanism, gadget, trick, trap, calculated manipulation, gambit, (small) scale,"
    },
    {
      "question": "厨房",
      "answer": "ちゅうぼう",
      "meaning": "kitchen, galley, (Internet) troll"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥",
      "answer": "どろ",
      "meaning": "mud, slush, (wet) dirt, mire, thief"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾杯",
      "answer": "かんぱい",
      "meaning": "cheers, bottoms-up, prosit, toast, drink (in celebration or in honor of something), drinking one's g"
    },
    {
      "question": "提出",
      "answer": "ていしゅつ",
      "meaning": "presentation (of documents), submission (of an application, report, etc.), production (e.g. of evide"
    },
    {
      "question": "果て",
      "answer": "はて",
      "meaning": "the end, the extremity, the limit, the limits, the result"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱々しい",
      "answer": "よわよわしい",
      "meaning": "frail, slender, feminine"
    },
    {
      "question": "地点",
      "answer": "ちてん",
      "meaning": "site, point on a map, spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹",
      "answer": "き",
      "meaning": "tree, shrub, bush, wood, timber"
    },
    {
      "question": "義理",
      "answer": "ぎり",
      "meaning": "duty, sense of duty, honor, honour, decency, courtesy, debt of gratitude, social obligation, in-law,"
    },
    {
      "question": "損",
      "answer": "そん",
      "meaning": "loss, damage, harm, unprofitable, disadvantage, handicap, drawback, unfavorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "美貌",
      "answer": "びぼう",
      "meaning": "beautiful face, good looks, beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "一礼",
      "answer": "いちれい",
      "meaning": "bow (salute, greeting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "投げ出す",
      "answer": "なげだす",
      "meaning": "to throw down, to throw out, to stretch out (one's legs), to abandon, to resign, to give freely, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷蔵庫",
      "answer": "れいぞうこ",
      "meaning": "refrigerator, fridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "夫人",
      "answer": "ふじん,ぶにん,はしかし",
      "meaning": "wife, Mrs, madam, wife of a nobleman (aristocrat, etc.), consort of the emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "余り",
      "answer": "あまり,あんまり",
      "meaning": "remainder, remnant, rest, balance, surplus, remains (of a meal), leftovers, (not) very, (not) much,"
    },
    {
      "question": "後ろ姿",
      "answer": "うしろすがた",
      "meaning": "retreating figure, appearance from behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "上回る",
      "answer": "うわまわる",
      "meaning": "to exceed (esp. figures: profits, unemployment rate, etc.), to surpass, to be more than, to be bette"
    },
    {
      "question": "人材",
      "answer": "じんざい",
      "meaning": "capable person, talented person, human resources, personnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "止む",
      "answer": "やむ",
      "meaning": "to cease, to stop, to be over"
    },
    {
      "question": "一階",
      "answer": "いっかい",
      "meaning": "first floor, ground floor, one floor, one storey, one rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓋",
      "answer": "ふた",
      "meaning": "cover, lid, cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "物言い",
      "answer": "ものいい",
      "meaning": "manner of speaking, verbal argument, objection, protesting a decision (esp. that of a sumo referee),"
    },
    {
      "question": "突進",
      "answer": "とっしん",
      "meaning": "rush, charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽物",
      "answer": "にせもの,にせもん,ぎぶつ",
      "meaning": "spurious article, forgery, counterfeit, imitation, sham"
    },
    {
      "question": "天気",
      "answer": "てんき",
      "meaning": "weather, the elements, fair weather, fine weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "携帯電話",
      "answer": "けいたいでんわ",
      "meaning": "mobile telephone, cellular telephone"
    },
    {
      "question": "地元",
      "answer": "じもと",
      "meaning": "home area, home town, local"
    },
    {
      "question": "生涯",
      "answer": "しょうがい",
      "meaning": "life, lifetime, career, for life, all one's life, throughout one's life, as long as one lives"
    },
    {
      "question": "死亡",
      "answer": "しぼう",
      "meaning": "death, mortality, to die, to pass away"
    },
    {
      "question": "念",
      "answer": "ねん",
      "meaning": "sense, idea, thought, feeling, desire, concern, attention, care"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋台",
      "answer": "やたい",
      "meaning": "cart (esp. a food cart), stall, stand, festival float, portable shrine dedicated to a god and shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "歪める",
      "answer": "ゆがめる,いがめる",
      "meaning": "to bend, to curve, to warp, to distort, to disfigure, to bend (the truth), to falsify, to twist, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き裂く",
      "answer": "ひきさく",
      "meaning": "to tear up, to tear off, to rip up, to separate (e.g. a couple), to disrupt (a relationship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前向き",
      "answer": "まえむき",
      "meaning": "front-facing, forward-looking, positive, constructive"
    },
    {
      "question": "村人",
      "answer": "むらびと",
      "meaning": "villager"
    },
    {
      "question": "箇所",
      "answer": "かしょ",
      "meaning": "place, point, part, spot, area, passage, portion, counter for places, parts, passages, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "存分",
      "answer": "ぞんぶん",
      "meaning": "to one's heart's content, as much as one wants"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾丸",
      "answer": "だんがん",
      "meaning": "bullet, shot, shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "他者",
      "answer": "たしゃ",
      "meaning": "another person, others"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝",
      "answer": "たから",
      "meaning": "treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺さぶる",
      "answer": "ゆさぶる",
      "meaning": "to shake, to jolt, to rock, to swing, to sway, to shake (e.g. the political world), to disturb, to s"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠り",
      "answer": "ねむり,ねぶり",
      "meaning": "sleep, sleeping, inactivity, death"
    },
    {
      "question": "膨大",
      "answer": "ぼうだい",
      "meaning": "huge, vast, enormous, colossal, extensive, large, swelling, expansion"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り切る",
      "answer": "はりきる",
      "meaning": "to be in high spirits, to be full of vigor (vigour), to be enthusiastic, to be eager, to stretch to"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩",
      "answer": "ばん",
      "meaning": "evening, night, dinner, evening meal, counter for nights"
    },
    {
      "question": "都",
      "answer": "みやこ,と",
      "meaning": "capital (esp. Kyoto, Japan's former capital), seat of government, capital (of music, fashion, etc.),"
    },
    {
      "question": "密着",
      "answer": "みっちゃく",
      "meaning": "close adhesion, sticking firmly to, being glued to, relating closely to, having relevance to, contac"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶句",
      "answer": "ぜっく,ぜく",
      "meaning": "being lost for words, becoming speechless, jueju (Chinese quatrain with lines of either five or seve"
    },
    {
      "question": "中々",
      "answer": "なかなか",
      "meaning": "very, considerably, easily, readily, fairly, quite, highly, rather, by no means, not readily, middle"
    },
    {
      "question": "精液",
      "answer": "せいえき",
      "meaning": "semen"
    },
    {
      "question": "詠唱",
      "answer": "えいしょう",
      "meaning": "aria, singing, chanting"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢見る",
      "answer": "ゆめみる",
      "meaning": "to dream (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち着き",
      "answer": "おちつき",
      "meaning": "calmness, composure, presence of mind, stability, steadiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い知る",
      "answer": "おもいしる",
      "meaning": "to realize, to realise"
    },
    {
      "question": "心地",
      "answer": "ここち,しんじ",
      "meaning": "feeling, sensation, mood, sensation of doing, padding, lining, foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧",
      "answer": "きゅう,ふる,もと",
      "meaning": "old, former, ex-, the old, old things, old customs, old times, bygone days, Japan's old (lunisolar)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大規模",
      "answer": "だいきぼ",
      "meaning": "large-scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲",
      "answer": "よく",
      "meaning": "greed, craving, desire, appetite, hunger, avarice, wants"
    },
    {
      "question": "痺れる",
      "answer": "しびれる",
      "meaning": "to become numb, to go to sleep (e.g. a limb), to get an electric shock, to tingle (from an electric"
    },
    {
      "question": "強張る",
      "answer": "こわばる",
      "meaning": "to stiffen, to become stiff"
    },
    {
      "question": "気軽",
      "answer": "きがる",
      "meaning": "carefree, buoyant, lighthearted, sprightly, ease"
    },
    {
      "question": "印",
      "answer": "いん,しるし",
      "meaning": "stamp, seal, chop, seal impression, sealing, mark, print, mudra (symbolic hand gesture), ninja hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き刺す",
      "answer": "つきさす",
      "meaning": "to stab, to pierce, to thrust"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲劇",
      "answer": "ひげき",
      "meaning": "tragedy, tragic drama, tragic play, calamity, disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "好き勝手",
      "answer": "すきかって",
      "meaning": "doing whatever one pleases"
    },
    {
      "question": "副",
      "answer": "ふく",
      "meaning": "assistant, associate, vice-, sub-, deputy, substitute, auxiliary, supplementary, additional, collate"
    },
    {
      "question": "口を挟む",
      "answer": "くちをはさむ",
      "meaning": "to cut into (a conversation), to interject"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち帰る",
      "answer": "もちかえる",
      "meaning": "to bring back, to carry home, to take out (e.g. food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妨害",
      "answer": "ぼうがい",
      "meaning": "disturbance, obstruction, hindrance, jamming, interference"
    },
    {
      "question": "出席",
      "answer": "しゅっせき",
      "meaning": "attendance, presence, appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "未知",
      "answer": "みち",
      "meaning": "not yet known, unknown, strange"
    },
    {
      "question": "華やか",
      "answer": "はなやか",
      "meaning": "showy, brilliant, gorgeous, florid, gay"
    },
    {
      "question": "急激",
      "answer": "きゅうげき",
      "meaning": "sudden, abrupt, rapid, sharp, drastic, radical"
    },
    {
      "question": "無用",
      "answer": "むよう",
      "meaning": "useless, futile, unnecessary, needless, not on business, unrelated, unauthorised, unauthorized, proh"
    },
    {
      "question": "専門",
      "answer": "せんもん",
      "meaning": "speciality, specialty, subject of study, expert, area of expertise"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛らしい",
      "answer": "あいらしい",
      "meaning": "pretty, charming, lovely, adorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き出す",
      "answer": "ききだす",
      "meaning": "to get information out of a person, to begin listening"
    },
    {
      "question": "案の定",
      "answer": "あんのじょう",
      "meaning": "just as one thought, as usual, sure enough"
    },
    {
      "question": "食欲",
      "answer": "しょくよく",
      "meaning": "appetite (for food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹が立つ",
      "answer": "はらがたつ",
      "meaning": "to get angry, to take offense, to take offence, to be furious"
    },
    {
      "question": "入院",
      "answer": "にゅういん",
      "meaning": "hospitalization, hospitalisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来",
      "answer": "しゅったい,しゅつらい,でき",
      "meaning": "occurrence, happening, taking place, completion, workmanship, craftsmanship, execution, finish, grad"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣士",
      "answer": "けんし",
      "meaning": "swordsman, swordswoman, fencer"
    },
    {
      "question": "里",
      "answer": "さと,り",
      "meaning": "village, hamlet, countryside, country, home (of one's parents, etc.), hometown, one's origins, one's"
    },
    {
      "question": "間抜け",
      "answer": "まぬけ",
      "meaning": "stupid, foolish, idiotic, inane, fool, idiot, blockhead, half-wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "些細",
      "answer": "ささい",
      "meaning": "trivial, slight"
    },
    {
      "question": "上半身",
      "answer": "じょうはんしん,かみはんしん",
      "meaning": "upper half of the body, upper body"
    },
    {
      "question": "気を失う",
      "answer": "きをうしなう",
      "meaning": "to lose consciousness, to faint, to black out"
    },
    {
      "question": "不愉快",
      "answer": "ふゆかい",
      "meaning": "unpleasant, disagreeable, displeasing, uncomfortable, unhappy"
    },
    {
      "question": "十二",
      "answer": "じゅうに",
      "meaning": "twelve, 12, queen (playing card)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺らぐ",
      "answer": "ゆらぐ",
      "meaning": "to swing, to sway, to shake, to tremble, to waver, to feel shaken, to become unstable"
    },
    {
      "question": "震え",
      "answer": "ふるえ",
      "meaning": "shivering, trembling"
    },
    {
      "question": "経営",
      "answer": "けいえい",
      "meaning": "management, administration, operation, running (business), conducting"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰",
      "answer": "いん,かげ,ほと",
      "meaning": "(the) negative (e.g. pole), yin (in Chinese divination), hidden place, unseen part, private location"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧倒",
      "answer": "あっとう",
      "meaning": "to overwhelm (e.g. an opponent), to overpower, to crush, to defeat completely, to overwhelm (someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "急速",
      "answer": "きゅうそく",
      "meaning": "rapid (e.g. progress)"
    },
    {
      "question": "豚",
      "answer": "ぶた,とん",
      "meaning": "pig (Sus scrofa domesticus), pork, fatso, fatty, pig"
    },
    {
      "question": "破滅",
      "answer": "はめつ",
      "meaning": "ruin, destruction, fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "資金",
      "answer": "しきん",
      "meaning": "funds, capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び散る",
      "answer": "とびちる",
      "meaning": "to fly around, to scatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "送り込む",
      "answer": "おくりこむ",
      "meaning": "to send in"
    },
    {
      "question": "言",
      "answer": "げん,こと",
      "meaning": "word, remark, statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "群",
      "answer": "ぐん,むら",
      "meaning": "group, bunch, crowd, throng, swarm, band, gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨体",
      "answer": "きょたい",
      "meaning": "huge body, large build"
    },
    {
      "question": "記事",
      "answer": "きじ",
      "meaning": "article, news story, report, account"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡らす",
      "answer": "ぬらす",
      "meaning": "to wet, to moisten, to dampen, to soak, to dip"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵対",
      "answer": "てきたい",
      "meaning": "hostility, antagonism, opposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺害",
      "answer": "さつがい,せつがい,せちがい",
      "meaning": "killing, murder"
    },
    {
      "question": "各地",
      "answer": "かくち",
      "meaning": "every place, various places"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥様",
      "answer": "おくさま",
      "meaning": "wife, your wife, his wife, married lady, madam"
    },
    {
      "question": "心強い",
      "answer": "こころづよい",
      "meaning": "heartening, reassuring"
    },
    {
      "question": "深める",
      "answer": "ふかめる",
      "meaning": "to deepen, to heighten, to intensify"
    },
    {
      "question": "辺境",
      "answer": "へんきょう",
      "meaning": "remote region, frontier (district), border(land)"
    },
    {
      "question": "来週",
      "answer": "らいしゅう",
      "meaning": "next week"
    },
    {
      "question": "妃",
      "answer": "きさき,ひ",
      "meaning": "empress, queen, princess, consort"
    },
    {
      "question": "体格",
      "answer": "たいかく",
      "meaning": "physique, constitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "上級",
      "answer": "じょうきゅう",
      "meaning": "advanced level, high grade, senior"
    },
    {
      "question": "生まれ",
      "answer": "うまれ",
      "meaning": "birth, birthplace, born in (country, month, imperial era, zodiac year, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄れる",
      "answer": "うすれる",
      "meaning": "to fade, to become dim"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅多",
      "answer": "めった",
      "meaning": "thoughtless, reckless, careless, rash, seldom, rare, ordinary, usual, common, excessive, immoderate,"
    },
    {
      "question": "市民",
      "answer": "しみん",
      "meaning": "citizen, citizenry, public, city inhabitant, townspeople, bourgeoisie, middle class"
    },
    {
      "question": "観客",
      "answer": "かんきゃく",
      "meaning": "audience, spectator, spectators"
    },
    {
      "question": "身構える",
      "answer": "みがまえる",
      "meaning": "to put oneself on guard, to stand ready, to square off"
    },
    {
      "question": "一瞥",
      "answer": "いちべつ",
      "meaning": "(a) glance, (a) look"
    },
    {
      "question": "意",
      "answer": "い",
      "meaning": "feelings, thoughts, meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "解体",
      "answer": "かいたい",
      "meaning": "demolition, taking down, dismantling, disassembly, taking apart, dissolution (of an organization, co"
    },
    {
      "question": "店長",
      "answer": "てんちょう",
      "meaning": "shop manager"
    },
    {
      "question": "突如",
      "answer": "とつじょ",
      "meaning": "suddenly, all of a sudden"
    },
    {
      "question": "無謀",
      "answer": "むぼう",
      "meaning": "reckless, thoughtless, rash, ill-advised, impulsive, mad (e.g. scheme)"
    },
    {
      "question": "員",
      "answer": "いん",
      "meaning": "member"
    },
    {
      "question": "一般人",
      "answer": "いっぱんじん",
      "meaning": "ordinary person, member of the general public, non-celebrity"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦巻く",
      "answer": "うずまく",
      "meaning": "to whirl, to eddy, to swirl, to curl (smoke), to be all jumbled together (feelings, thoughts, etc.),"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄色い",
      "answer": "きいろい",
      "meaning": "yellow, high-pitched (voice), shrill"
    },
    {
      "question": "中学生",
      "answer": "ちゅうがくせい",
      "meaning": "junior high school student, middle school pupil"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒れる",
      "answer": "あれる",
      "meaning": "to be stormy, to be rough, to be rough (of skin), to be chapped, to be ruined, to fall into ruin, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "巫女",
      "answer": "みこ,ふじょ,のろ",
      "meaning": "miko, shrine maiden, young girl or woman (trad. an unmarried virgin) who assists priests at shrines,"
    },
    {
      "question": "傭兵",
      "answer": "ようへい",
      "meaning": "mercenary (soldier)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青ざめる",
      "answer": "あおざめる",
      "meaning": "to become pale, to turn pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "基準",
      "answer": "きじゅん",
      "meaning": "standard, basis, criterion, norm, reference, datum"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を見る",
      "answer": "めをみる",
      "meaning": "to experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "阻む",
      "answer": "はばむ",
      "meaning": "to keep someone from doing, to stop, to prevent, to check, to hinder, to obstruct, to oppose, to thw"
    },
    {
      "question": "文章",
      "answer": "ぶんしょう,もんじょう,もんぞう",
      "meaning": "writing, composition, essay, article, passage, prose, (writing) style, sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "託する",
      "answer": "たくする",
      "meaning": "to entrust (someone) with, to leave (a matter) with someone, to place under someone's care, to have"
    },
    {
      "question": "企む",
      "answer": "たくらむ",
      "meaning": "to scheme, to plan, to play a trick, to invent, to conspire, to frame up"
    },
    {
      "question": "働き",
      "answer": "はたらき",
      "meaning": "work, labor, labour, achievement, performance, ability, talent, salary, income, earnings, action, ac"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦",
      "answer": "うず",
      "meaning": "whirlpool, swirl, eddy, vortex, maelstrom"
    },
    {
      "question": "当たり",
      "answer": "あたり",
      "meaning": "hit, success, guess, prediction, affability, friendliness, sensation, touch, bruise (on fruit), situ"
    },
    {
      "question": "考慮",
      "answer": "こうりょ",
      "meaning": "consideration, taking into account"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈める",
      "answer": "しずめる",
      "meaning": "to sink (e.g. a ship), to submerge, to lower (e.g. one's body into a chair), to floor (an opponent)"
    },
    {
      "question": "頂点",
      "answer": "ちょうてん",
      "meaning": "top, summit, vertex"
    },
    {
      "question": "公",
      "answer": "きみ,おおやけ,こう",
      "meaning": "you, buddy, pal, monarch, ruler, sovereign, (one's) master, official, governmental, formal, public ("
    },
    {
      "question": "防衛",
      "answer": "ぼうえい",
      "meaning": "defense, defence, protection"
    },
    {
      "question": "不器用",
      "answer": "ぶきよう",
      "meaning": "clumsy, awkward, unskillfulness, lack of ability, tactless, awkward (e.g. socially), gauche, mean, c"
    },
    {
      "question": "関連",
      "answer": "かんれん",
      "meaning": "relation, connection, relevance"
    },
    {
      "question": "頂戴",
      "answer": "ちょうだい",
      "meaning": "receiving, reception, getting, being given, eating, drinking, having, please, please do for me"
    },
    {
      "question": "次元",
      "answer": "じげん",
      "meaning": "dimension, perspective, point of reference, level (of something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "方角",
      "answer": "ほうがく",
      "meaning": "direction, way, point of the compass, cardinal direction, bearing, method, means, approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳ぶ",
      "answer": "とぶ",
      "meaning": "to fly, to soar, to jump, to leap, to spring, to bound, to hop, to spatter, to scatter, to splash, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "強大",
      "answer": "きょうだい",
      "meaning": "mighty, powerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏腹",
      "answer": "うらはら",
      "meaning": "opposite, reverse, contrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し出",
      "answer": "もうしで",
      "meaning": "proposal, request, claim, report, notice, offer"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰り道",
      "answer": "かえりみち",
      "meaning": "the way back, the way home, return trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶かす",
      "answer": "とかす",
      "meaning": "to dissolve, to melt"
    },
    {
      "question": "面持ち",
      "answer": "おももち",
      "meaning": "expression, look, countenance, face"
    },
    {
      "question": "同級生",
      "answer": "どうきゅうせい",
      "meaning": "classmate"
    },
    {
      "question": "赴く",
      "answer": "おもむく,おもぶく",
      "meaning": "to go in the direction of, to proceed toward, to proceed according to, to repair to, to betake onese"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷口",
      "answer": "きずぐち",
      "meaning": "(opening of) a wound, (mouth of a) wound, cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "博士",
      "answer": "はかせ,はくし",
      "meaning": "expert, learned person, doctor, PhD, Dr., instructor at the imperial court (ritsuryo period), pitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "咳払い",
      "answer": "せきばらい",
      "meaning": "clearing one's throat, cough"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯",
      "answer": "ゆ,タン",
      "meaning": "hot water, hot bath, hot spring, molten iron, soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "放送",
      "answer": "ほうそう",
      "meaning": "broadcast, broadcasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "一行",
      "answer": "いちぎょう,いっこう",
      "meaning": "(one) line, (one) row, party, group, troop, company, one act, one action, one deed"
    },
    {
      "question": "映す",
      "answer": "うつす",
      "meaning": "to project, to reflect, to cast (shadow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "閣下",
      "answer": "かっか",
      "meaning": "your Excellency, his Excellency, her Excellency"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋼",
      "answer": "はがね,こう",
      "meaning": "steel"
    },
    {
      "question": "要は",
      "answer": "ようは",
      "meaning": "in short, the point is, the important thing is, in a word, basically"
    },
    {
      "question": "午前",
      "answer": "ごぜん",
      "meaning": "morning, a.m."
    },
    {
      "question": "乳首",
      "answer": "ちくび,ちちくび",
      "meaning": "nipple, teat"
    },
    {
      "question": "開催",
      "answer": "かいさい",
      "meaning": "holding (a conference, exhibition, etc.), opening, hosting (e.g. the Olympics)"
    },
    {
      "question": "登校",
      "answer": "とうこう",
      "meaning": "attendance (at school), going to school"
    },
    {
      "question": "三度",
      "answer": "さんど,みたび",
      "meaning": "three times, thrice, third (musical interval), many times, over and over again, often, frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "苛立ち",
      "answer": "いらだち",
      "meaning": "irritation, annoyance, frustration"
    },
    {
      "question": "憎悪",
      "answer": "ぞうお",
      "meaning": "hatred, abhorrence, loathing, detestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "概念",
      "answer": "がいねん",
      "meaning": "general idea, concept, notion"
    },
    {
      "question": "主役",
      "answer": "しゅやく",
      "meaning": "leading part, leading actor, leading actress"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り込む",
      "answer": "わりこむ",
      "meaning": "to cut into (a line, conversation, etc.), to force oneself into (e.g. a crowd), to wedge oneself int"
    },
    {
      "question": "懇願",
      "answer": "こんがん",
      "meaning": "entreaty, supplication, petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "運転",
      "answer": "うんてん",
      "meaning": "operation (of a machine, etc.), operating, running, run, driving, working (capital, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "痕跡",
      "answer": "こんせき",
      "meaning": "trace, vestige, mark, sign, evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "雫",
      "answer": "しずく",
      "meaning": "drop (e.g. of water), drip"
    },
    {
      "question": "芯",
      "answer": "しん",
      "meaning": "wick, marrow, staple (for stapler), (pencil) lead, stuffing, pith, core, heart, centre, center, pist"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩み",
      "answer": "あゆみ",
      "meaning": "walking, pace, step, course (of history, one's life, etc.), history, progress, advance, development,"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関",
      "answer": "からくり,きかん",
      "meaning": "mechanism, machinery, contrivance, device, trick, dodge, mechanical doll, string puppet, engine, age"
    },
    {
      "question": "道理",
      "answer": "どうり",
      "meaning": "reason, logic, sense, truth, right"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸惑い",
      "answer": "とまどい",
      "meaning": "being at sea, losing one's bearings, confusion, wonderment"
    },
    {
      "question": "拗ねる",
      "answer": "すねる",
      "meaning": "to be peevish, to sulk, to pout"
    },
    {
      "question": "消え去る",
      "answer": "きえさる",
      "meaning": "to disappear, to vanish"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝突",
      "answer": "しょうとつ",
      "meaning": "collision, crash, running into, conflict, quarrel, clashing"
    },
    {
      "question": "油",
      "answer": "あぶら",
      "meaning": "oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "単位",
      "answer": "たんい",
      "meaning": "unit, denomination, credit (in school), in units of (e.g. 'in thousands'), in amounts of"
    },
    {
      "question": "踵を返す",
      "answer": "きびすをかえす,くびすをかえす",
      "meaning": "to turn on one's heel, to turn back, to return"
    },
    {
      "question": "平穏",
      "answer": "へいおん",
      "meaning": "tranquil, calm, restful, peaceful, quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "余",
      "answer": "よ",
      "meaning": "other, another, remaining, leftover, over, more than, I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "物事",
      "answer": "ものごと",
      "meaning": "things, everything"
    },
    {
      "question": "上品",
      "answer": "じょうひん,じょうぼん",
      "meaning": "elegant, refined, polished, stylish, sophisticated, high-quality goods, first-class article, Buddhis"
    },
    {
      "question": "枠",
      "answer": "わく",
      "meaning": "frame, framework, border, box, limit, restriction, quota, category, bracket, class, (broadcasting) s"
    },
    {
      "question": "菓子",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "confectionery, sweets, candy, cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き継ぐ",
      "answer": "ひきつぐ",
      "meaning": "to take over, to hand over"
    },
    {
      "question": "小僧",
      "answer": "こぞう",
      "meaning": "youngster, boy, kid, brat, young Buddhist monk, young bonze, young shop-boy, errand boy, apprentice"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪能",
      "answer": "たんのう,かんのう",
      "meaning": "proficient, skillful, enjoying, satisfaction, satiation, having one's fill (of), patience, persevera"
    },
    {
      "question": "中断",
      "answer": "ちゅうだん",
      "meaning": "interruption, suspension, break"
    },
    {
      "question": "刹那",
      "answer": "せつな",
      "meaning": "moment, instant, kshana, duration of a single mental event (about 1/75 second), shortest possible in"
    },
    {
      "question": "囚われる",
      "answer": "とらわれる",
      "meaning": "to be caught, to be captured, to be taken prisoner, to be arrested, to be apprehended, to be seized"
    },
    {
      "question": "運営",
      "answer": "うんえい",
      "meaning": "management, administration, operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "指名",
      "answer": "しめい",
      "meaning": "naming, nominating, designating, calling on, asking for, requesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "社",
      "answer": "やしろ,しゃ",
      "meaning": "(Shinto) shrine, company, association, society, regional Chinese god of the earth (or a village buil"
    },
    {
      "question": "散らばる",
      "answer": "ちらばる",
      "meaning": "to be scattered about"
    },
    {
      "question": "拷問",
      "answer": "ごうもん",
      "meaning": "torture"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂らす",
      "answer": "たらす",
      "meaning": "to dribble, to spill, to suspend, to hang down, to slouch, to dangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "一個",
      "answer": "いっこ",
      "meaning": "piece, fragment, one (object)"
    },
    {
      "question": "作成",
      "answer": "さくせい",
      "meaning": "drawing up (e.g. legal document, contract, will, etc.), preparing, writing, framing, making, produci"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆る",
      "answer": "かる",
      "meaning": "to spur on, to urge forward, to impel, to drive at high speed (e.g. a car)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重み",
      "answer": "おもみ",
      "meaning": "weight, weight (e.g. of someone's words), burden, grandeur, dignity, importance, significance"
    },
    {
      "question": "教科書",
      "answer": "きょうかしょ",
      "meaning": "textbook, coursebook, schoolbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "情熱",
      "answer": "じょうねつ",
      "meaning": "passion, enthusiasm, zeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "前髪",
      "answer": "まえがみ",
      "meaning": "forelock, bangs"
    },
    {
      "question": "誇らしい",
      "answer": "ほこらしい",
      "meaning": "proud, haughty, arrogant"
    },
    {
      "question": "呻く",
      "answer": "うめく",
      "meaning": "to moan, to groan"
    },
    {
      "question": "連携",
      "answer": "れんけい",
      "meaning": "cooperation, coordination, link"
    },
    {
      "question": "却下",
      "answer": "きゃっか",
      "meaning": "rejection, dismissal"
    },
    {
      "question": "検討",
      "answer": "けんとう",
      "meaning": "consideration, examination, investigation, study, scrutiny, discussion, analysis, review"
    },
    {
      "question": "微塵",
      "answer": "みじん,びじん",
      "meaning": "particle, atom, little piece, not at all, not the slightest"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛布",
      "answer": "もうふ",
      "meaning": "blanket"
    },
    {
      "question": "進路",
      "answer": "しんろ",
      "meaning": "route, course, path, one's future course (e.g. after graduating high school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "通過",
      "answer": "つうか",
      "meaning": "passing through (a tunnel, station, town, etc.), passing by (e.g. of a typhoon), transit, passage (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "四十",
      "answer": "よんじゅう,しじゅう,よそ",
      "meaning": "forty, 40"
    },
    {
      "question": "成す",
      "answer": "なす",
      "meaning": "to build up, to establish, to form, to become (a state), to accomplish, to achieve, to succeed in, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵",
      "answer": "ちえ",
      "meaning": "wisdom, wit, sagacity, sense, intelligence, prajna (insight leading to enlightenment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後退",
      "answer": "こうたい",
      "meaning": "retreat, falling back, moving backwards, reversing, retrogression, retraction, recession, waning, ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "澄む",
      "answer": "すむ",
      "meaning": "to become clear (water, air, etc.), to become transparent, to resonate clearly (e.g. voice), to beco"
    },
    {
      "question": "何という",
      "answer": "なんという",
      "meaning": "how (beautiful, etc.), what a ..., nothing worth mentioning, nothing special, of what name"
    },
    {
      "question": "特有",
      "answer": "とくゆう",
      "meaning": "characteristic (of), peculiar (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手作り",
      "answer": "てづくり",
      "meaning": "handmade, homegrown, hand-crafted, homemade"
    },
    {
      "question": "可憐",
      "answer": "かれん",
      "meaning": "sweet (e.g. young girls, flowers blooming), touchingly lovely, cute, pitiful, pitiable"
    },
    {
      "question": "工場",
      "answer": "こうじょう,こうば",
      "meaning": "factory, plant, mill, workshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を通す",
      "answer": "めをとおす",
      "meaning": "to scan, to look over"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣き声",
      "answer": "なきごえ",
      "meaning": "cry, crying voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "修理",
      "answer": "しゅうり,しゅり,すり",
      "meaning": "repair, mending, fixing, servicing"
    },
    {
      "question": "同僚",
      "answer": "どうりょう",
      "meaning": "coworker, co-worker, colleague, associate"
    },
    {
      "question": "天国",
      "answer": "てんごく",
      "meaning": "paradise, heaven, Kingdom of Heaven"
    },
    {
      "question": "獲得",
      "answer": "かくとく",
      "meaning": "acquisition, possession"
    },
    {
      "question": "尋常",
      "answer": "じんじょう",
      "meaning": "common, usual"
    },
    {
      "question": "現",
      "answer": "うつつ,げん",
      "meaning": "reality, consciousness, present (e.g. government, administration), current, existing"
    },
    {
      "question": "唾液",
      "answer": "だえき",
      "meaning": "saliva, sputum"
    },
    {
      "question": "躊躇う",
      "answer": "ためらう",
      "meaning": "to hesitate, to waver"
    },
    {
      "question": "実戦",
      "answer": "じっせん",
      "meaning": "combat, battle, action, active service, actual fighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "球",
      "answer": "まり,きゅう,たま",
      "meaning": "ball (for sport, games, etc.), sphere, counter for balls, ball, globe, orb, bead (of sweat, dew, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "物理的",
      "answer": "ぶつりてき",
      "meaning": "physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "階層",
      "answer": "かいそう",
      "meaning": "class, level, stratum, layer, hierarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑丈",
      "answer": "がんじょう",
      "meaning": "solid, firm, stout, burly, strong, sturdy"
    },
    {
      "question": "非難",
      "answer": "ひなん",
      "meaning": "criticism, blame, censure, attack, reproach"
    },
    {
      "question": "祈り",
      "answer": "いのり",
      "meaning": "prayer, supplication"
    },
    {
      "question": "救出",
      "answer": "きゅうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "rescue, extricate, reclaim, deliverance"
    },
    {
      "question": "商会",
      "answer": "しょうかい",
      "meaning": "firm, company"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓",
      "answer": "はか",
      "meaning": "gravesite, tomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "広大",
      "answer": "こうだい",
      "meaning": "vast, extensive, immense, huge, large, grand, magnificent"
    },
    {
      "question": "辿る",
      "answer": "たどる",
      "meaning": "to follow (road), to pursue (course), to follow up, to follow (hyperlink)"
    },
    {
      "question": "的確",
      "answer": "てきかく,てっかく",
      "meaning": "precise, accurate, appropriate, exactly the right"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳に入る",
      "answer": "みみにはいる",
      "meaning": "to reach one's ears, to come to one's knowledge, to hear about, to learn of (by chance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を離す",
      "answer": "めをはなす",
      "meaning": "to take one's eyes off"
    },
    {
      "question": "真顔",
      "answer": "まがお",
      "meaning": "serious look (on one's face), straight face"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き取る",
      "answer": "ききとる",
      "meaning": "to catch (someone's words), to make out, to follow, to understand, to ask about (a situation, circum"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝う",
      "answer": "いわう",
      "meaning": "to celebrate, to congratulate, to observe (a festival), to present (a gift) in celebration, to drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "転生",
      "answer": "てんせい,てんしょう",
      "meaning": "transmigration of souls, reincarnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "再",
      "answer": "さい",
      "meaning": "re-, again, repeated, deutero-, deuto-, deuter-"
    },
    {
      "question": "軌道",
      "answer": "きどう",
      "meaning": "orbit, trajectory, railroad track, (right) track, proper course"
    },
    {
      "question": "大して",
      "answer": "たいして",
      "meaning": "(not so) much, (not) very"
    },
    {
      "question": "感知",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "perception, sensing, noticing"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き返す",
      "answer": "ききかえす",
      "meaning": "to listen repeatedly, to listen again, to ask a question in return, to ask again, to ask for a repea"
    },
    {
      "question": "即答",
      "answer": "そくとう",
      "meaning": "immediate reply"
    },
    {
      "question": "修復",
      "answer": "しゅうふく,しゅふく",
      "meaning": "restoration, repair, mending"
    },
    {
      "question": "検査",
      "answer": "けんさ",
      "meaning": "inspection (e.g. customs, factory), examination, scan (e.g. MRI, PET, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣き出す",
      "answer": "なきだす",
      "meaning": "to burst into tears, to burst out crying, to begin to cry, to be moved to tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧力",
      "answer": "あつりょく",
      "meaning": "pressure, stress, pressure (e.g. political), coercion, arm-twisting"
    },
    {
      "question": "判る",
      "answer": "わかる",
      "meaning": "to understand, to comprehend, to grasp, to see, to get, to follow, to become clear, to be known, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "習得",
      "answer": "しゅうとく",
      "meaning": "learning, acquisition (of a skill, knowledge, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "紐",
      "answer": "ひも",
      "meaning": "string, cord, man who is financially dependent on a woman, gigolo, pimp, restrictions, conditions, m"
    },
    {
      "question": "対面",
      "answer": "たいめん,たいめ,トイメン",
      "meaning": "meeting face-to-face, seeing in person, facing (each other), opposing (traffic, etc.), confronting,"
    },
    {
      "question": "破片",
      "answer": "はへん",
      "meaning": "fragment, broken piece, splinter, chip, shard"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰め寄る",
      "answer": "つめよる",
      "meaning": "to draw near, to draw closer, to press (e.g. for an answer), to hound"
    },
    {
      "question": "手助け",
      "answer": "てだすけ",
      "meaning": "a help, assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "政府",
      "answer": "せいふ",
      "meaning": "government, administration"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾ける",
      "answer": "かたむける",
      "meaning": "to incline, to lean, to tip, to tilt, to slant, to bend, to list, to devote oneself to, to concentra"
    },
    {
      "question": "幹部",
      "answer": "かんぶ",
      "meaning": "management, (executive) staff, leaders, leadership, top brass, upper echelons"
    },
    {
      "question": "片隅",
      "answer": "かたすみ",
      "meaning": "corner, nook"
    },
    {
      "question": "交代",
      "answer": "こうたい",
      "meaning": "alternation, change, relief, relay, shift, substitution (sports, etc.), taking turns"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛おしい",
      "answer": "いとおしい",
      "meaning": "lovely, dear, beloved, darling, dearest, pitiable, pathetic, piteous, poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈴",
      "answer": "すず,りん,れい",
      "meaning": "bell (often globular)"
    },
    {
      "question": "予備",
      "answer": "よび",
      "meaning": "reserve, spare, preparation, preliminaries"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸血鬼",
      "answer": "きゅうけつき",
      "meaning": "vampire, bloodsucker"
    },
    {
      "question": "子爵",
      "answer": "ししゃく",
      "meaning": "viscount"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪化",
      "answer": "あっか",
      "meaning": "(suffer) deterioration, growing worse, aggravation, degeneration, corruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "不在",
      "answer": "ふざい",
      "meaning": "absence, disregard, indifference"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑑定",
      "answer": "かんてい",
      "meaning": "judgement, judgment, expert opinion, appraisal"
    },
    {
      "question": "不穏",
      "answer": "ふおん",
      "meaning": "disquieting, threatening, turbulent, restless, unsettled, disturbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "留まる",
      "answer": "とまる,とどまる",
      "meaning": "to stop (moving), to come to a stop, to stop (doing, working, being supplied), to come to a halt, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "激突",
      "answer": "げきとつ",
      "meaning": "crash into, clash"
    },
    {
      "question": "見下す",
      "answer": "みくだす",
      "meaning": "to look down (on), to condescend (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "身近",
      "answer": "みぢか",
      "meaning": "near oneself, close to one, familiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "次期",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "next term, next period, next version, next release"
    },
    {
      "question": "摘む",
      "answer": "つむ,つまむ",
      "meaning": "to pick, to pluck, to snip, to cut, to nip, to trim, to pinch, to hold (between one's fingers), to p"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶望的",
      "answer": "ぜつぼうてき",
      "meaning": "desperate, hopeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "留守",
      "answer": "るす",
      "meaning": "absence, being away from home, house-sitting, house-sitter, being left unattended to (of one's studi"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻痺",
      "answer": "まひ",
      "meaning": "paralysis, palsy, numbness, stupor"
    },
    {
      "question": "従者",
      "answer": "じゅうしゃ",
      "meaning": "follower, attendant, valet, servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝かせる",
      "answer": "ねかせる",
      "meaning": "to put to bed, to lay down lengthwise, to put a thing on its side, to set something aside unused, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸君",
      "answer": "しょくん",
      "meaning": "you (people), gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, my friends, everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "佇む",
      "answer": "たたずむ",
      "meaning": "to stand (still) a while, to loiter, to stop"
    },
    {
      "question": "古代",
      "answer": "こだい",
      "meaning": "ancient times"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛れる",
      "answer": "まぎれる",
      "meaning": "to disappear into, to be lost in, to slip into, to get mixed in among, to do something under the cov"
    },
    {
      "question": "称号",
      "answer": "しょうごう",
      "meaning": "title, name, degree"
    },
    {
      "question": "小刻み",
      "answer": "こきざみ",
      "meaning": "mincing, chopping finely, short and repeated (movements) (e.g. trembling, stepping quickly), gradual"
    },
    {
      "question": "曰く",
      "answer": "いわく,のたまわく",
      "meaning": "pretext, history, past, story, according to ..., ... says"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭痛",
      "answer": "ずつう",
      "meaning": "headache"
    },
    {
      "question": "握手",
      "answer": "あくしゅ",
      "meaning": "handshake, reconciliation, joining hands, cooperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "間合い",
      "answer": "まあい",
      "meaning": "interval, distance, break, pause, suitable time, appropriate opportunity, distance between opponents"
    },
    {
      "question": "非",
      "answer": "ひ",
      "meaning": "fault, error, mistake, going poorly, being disadvantageous, being unfavorable, un-, non-, an-"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿題",
      "answer": "しゅくだい",
      "meaning": "homework, assignment, pending issue, unresolved problem, open question"
    },
    {
      "question": "現に",
      "answer": "げんに",
      "meaning": "actually, really"
    },
    {
      "question": "紡ぐ",
      "answer": "つむぐ",
      "meaning": "to spin, to make yarn, to spin (a tale), to assemble (e.g. words), to put together"
    },
    {
      "question": "製",
      "answer": "せい",
      "meaning": "-made, make"
    },
    {
      "question": "果物",
      "answer": "くだもの,かぶつ",
      "meaning": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "標的",
      "answer": "ひょうてき",
      "meaning": "target"
    },
    {
      "question": "王城",
      "answer": "おうじょう",
      "meaning": "royal castle, imperial castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "一つ一つ",
      "answer": "ひとつひとつ",
      "meaning": "one-by-one, separately, in detail"
    },
    {
      "question": "結晶",
      "answer": "けっしょう",
      "meaning": "crystal, crystallization, crystallisation, fruits (of labor, union, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "射精",
      "answer": "しゃせい",
      "meaning": "ejaculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "域",
      "answer": "いき",
      "meaning": "region, limits, stage, level"
    },
    {
      "question": "真相",
      "answer": "しんそう",
      "meaning": "truth, real situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤ん坊",
      "answer": "あかんぼう,あかんぼ",
      "meaning": "baby, infant"
    },
    {
      "question": "芝居",
      "answer": "しばい",
      "meaning": "play, drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "外側",
      "answer": "そとがわ,がいそく",
      "meaning": "exterior, outside, outer, external, lateral"
    },
    {
      "question": "頻繁",
      "answer": "ひんぱん",
      "meaning": "frequent, incessant"
    },
    {
      "question": "医師",
      "answer": "いし,くすし",
      "meaning": "doctor, physician"
    },
    {
      "question": "見張り",
      "answer": "みはり",
      "meaning": "watch-keeping, guard, lookout"
    },
    {
      "question": "寿命",
      "answer": "じゅみょう",
      "meaning": "life span"
    },
    {
      "question": "演出",
      "answer": "えんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "production (e.g. play), direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "両者",
      "answer": "りょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "pair, the two, both persons, both things"
    },
    {
      "question": "声音",
      "answer": "せいおん,こわね",
      "meaning": "vocal sound, tone of voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣",
      "answer": "す",
      "meaning": "nest, rookery, breeding place, hive, den, haunt, (spider's) web"
    },
    {
      "question": "段",
      "answer": "たん,だん",
      "meaning": "variable measure of fabric (28.8 cm in width), for kimonos: at least 10 m in length, for haori: at l"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦",
      "answer": "たて,ほしいまま,よし",
      "meaning": "the vertical, height, front-to-back, length, north-to-south, vertical (relationship), hierarchy, (we"
    },
    {
      "question": "理論",
      "answer": "りろん",
      "meaning": "theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "権限",
      "answer": "けんげん",
      "meaning": "power, authority, jurisdiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "包丁",
      "answer": "ほうちょう",
      "meaning": "kitchen knife, carving knife, cooking, food"
    },
    {
      "question": "束",
      "answer": "たば,つか,そく",
      "meaning": "bundle, bunch, sheaf, strut, short vertical post, thickness (of a book minus the cover, a sheaf of p"
    },
    {
      "question": "容易い",
      "answer": "たやすい",
      "meaning": "easy, simple, light"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷や汗",
      "answer": "ひやあせ",
      "meaning": "cold sweat"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本語",
      "answer": "にほんご,にっぽんご",
      "meaning": "Japanese (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿る",
      "answer": "しめる,しとる",
      "meaning": "to become damp, to become moist, to become wet, to lack energy, to be in a slump, to be in low spiri"
    },
    {
      "question": "試しに",
      "answer": "ためしに",
      "meaning": "as a test, as an experiment, by way of experiment, by way of trial, tentatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "触手",
      "answer": "しょくしゅ",
      "meaning": "feeler, tentacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "高価",
      "answer": "こうか",
      "meaning": "highly priced, expensive, valuable, costly"
    },
    {
      "question": "国内",
      "answer": "こくない,こくだい,くぬち",
      "meaning": "internal, domestic"
    },
    {
      "question": "極端",
      "answer": "きょくたん",
      "meaning": "extreme, extremity"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い払う",
      "answer": "おいはらう,おいぱらう",
      "meaning": "to drive away, to clear, to scatter, to disperse"
    },
    {
      "question": "観念",
      "answer": "かんねん",
      "meaning": "idea, notion, concept, conception, sense (e.g. of duty), resignation, preparedness, acceptance, obse"
    },
    {
      "question": "海外",
      "answer": "かいがい",
      "meaning": "foreign, abroad, overseas"
    },
    {
      "question": "空っぽ",
      "answer": "からっぽ",
      "meaning": "empty, vacant, hollow"
    },
    {
      "question": "路地",
      "answer": "ろじ",
      "meaning": "alley, alleyway, lane, teahouse garden, path through a gate (or through a garden, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "明後日",
      "answer": "あさって,みょうごにち",
      "meaning": "day after tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "露骨",
      "answer": "ろこつ",
      "meaning": "open, unconcealed, undisguised, blatant, plain, frank, broad, lewd, indecent, crude"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣術",
      "answer": "けんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "(art of) fencing, swordsmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "翌朝",
      "answer": "よくあさ,よくちょう",
      "meaning": "next morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り切る",
      "answer": "ふりきる",
      "meaning": "to shake off, to shake free from, to swing completely (bat, club, etc.), to take a full swing, to br"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り付く",
      "answer": "はりつく",
      "meaning": "to stick (to), to cling (to), to stay (e.g. in the office)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘惑",
      "answer": "ゆうわく",
      "meaning": "temptation, allurement, lure, enticement, seduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "予算",
      "answer": "よさん",
      "meaning": "estimate, budget"
    },
    {
      "question": "代償",
      "answer": "だいしょう",
      "meaning": "compensation, indemnification, reparation, consideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "決闘",
      "answer": "けっとう",
      "meaning": "duel, shoot-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆転",
      "answer": "ぎゃくてん",
      "meaning": "(sudden) change, reversal, turn-around, coming from behind (baseball)"
    },
    {
      "question": "贈り物",
      "answer": "おくりもの",
      "meaning": "present, gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "守り",
      "answer": "もり,まもり",
      "meaning": "babysitting, babysitter, protecting, keeping, keeper, protection, defense, defence, providence, amul"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾向",
      "answer": "けいこう",
      "meaning": "tendency, trend, inclination"
    },
    {
      "question": "一直線",
      "answer": "いっちょくせん",
      "meaning": "straight line"
    },
    {
      "question": "血液",
      "answer": "けつえき",
      "meaning": "blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り",
      "answer": "かざり",
      "meaning": "decoration, ornament, trimmings"
    },
    {
      "question": "致命的",
      "answer": "ちめいてき",
      "meaning": "fatal, lethal"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥",
      "answer": "はじ",
      "meaning": "shame, embarrassment, disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒場",
      "answer": "さかば",
      "meaning": "bar, pub, tavern"
    },
    {
      "question": "図る",
      "answer": "はかる",
      "meaning": "to plan, to attempt, to devise, to plot, to conspire, to scheme, to aim for, to strive for, to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "給料",
      "answer": "きゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "salary, wages, pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "未熟",
      "answer": "みじゅく",
      "meaning": "unripe, green, inexperienced, immature, unskilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "険しい",
      "answer": "けわしい",
      "meaning": "precipitous, rugged, inaccessible, impregnable, steep, grim, severe, stern"
    },
    {
      "question": "不意打ち",
      "answer": "ふいうち",
      "meaning": "surprise attack, surprise visit, catching a person off guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲する",
      "answer": "ほっする",
      "meaning": "to want, to desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽",
      "answer": "ひ,よう",
      "meaning": "sun, sunshine, sunlight, (the) positive, yang (in Chinese divination), the open, visible place, publ"
    },
    {
      "question": "儚い",
      "answer": "はかない",
      "meaning": "fleeting, transient, short-lived, momentary, ephemeral, fickle, vain, empty (dream, etc.), mere (hop"
    },
    {
      "question": "坂",
      "answer": "さか",
      "meaning": "slope, incline, hill, milestone, (age) mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "学年",
      "answer": "がくねん",
      "meaning": "academic year, school year, year in school, grade in school"
    },
    {
      "question": "根性",
      "answer": "こんじょう",
      "meaning": "willpower, guts, determination, grit, spirit, character, nature, disposition, personality"
    },
    {
      "question": "基礎",
      "answer": "きそ",
      "meaning": "foundation, basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "充実",
      "answer": "じゅうじつ",
      "meaning": "fullness, completion, perfection, substantiality, enhancement, improvement, enrichment, upgrading, r"
    },
    {
      "question": "拡大",
      "answer": "かくだい",
      "meaning": "magnification, enlargement, expansion, amplification"
    },
    {
      "question": "早朝",
      "answer": "そうちょう",
      "meaning": "early morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "自力",
      "answer": "じりき,じりょく",
      "meaning": "one's own strength, one's own efforts, self-salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "反動",
      "answer": "はんどう",
      "meaning": "reaction, recoil, kick, backlash"
    },
    {
      "question": "断つ",
      "answer": "たつ",
      "meaning": "to sever, to cut off, to suppress, to eradicate, to exterminate, to abstain (from), to give up"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂漠",
      "answer": "さばく",
      "meaning": "desert"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き出す",
      "answer": "ふきだす",
      "meaning": "to spout out, to spurt out, to gush out, to jet out, to sprout, to bud, to burst into laughter, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "練る",
      "answer": "ねる",
      "meaning": "to knead, to thicken into a paste (stirring over a flame), to polish (a plan, etc.), to refine, to e"
    },
    {
      "question": "見返す",
      "answer": "みかえす",
      "meaning": "to look (stare) back at (somebody), to look at again, to re-examine, to prove oneself superior (to s"
    },
    {
      "question": "切断",
      "answer": "せつだん",
      "meaning": "cutting, severance, section, amputation, disconnection"
    },
    {
      "question": "道路",
      "answer": "どうろ",
      "meaning": "road, highway"
    },
    {
      "question": "五分",
      "answer": "ごぶ,ごぶん,ごふん",
      "meaning": "half, 50%, tie, evenness, 5 parts, 5%, to divide into five parts, five minutes"
    },
    {
      "question": "尾",
      "answer": "お,び",
      "meaning": "tail (animal, kite, comet, etc.), tail end, slope at the foot of a mountain, Chinese 'Tail' constell"
    },
    {
      "question": "装飾",
      "answer": "そうしょく",
      "meaning": "ornament, decoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "本棚",
      "answer": "ほんだな",
      "meaning": "bookshelves, bookshelf, bookcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡める",
      "answer": "からめる",
      "meaning": "to entwine, to twine around, to mix together, to coordinate (with), to arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "担う",
      "answer": "になう",
      "meaning": "to carry on one's shoulder, to shoulder, to bear, to bear (burden, responsibility, etc.), to take up"
    },
    {
      "question": "他人事",
      "answer": "ひとごと,たにんごと",
      "meaning": "other people's affairs, somebody else's problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "設ける",
      "answer": "もうける",
      "meaning": "to prepare, to provide, to set up, to establish, to organize, to lay down (rules), to make (an excus"
    },
    {
      "question": "庭園",
      "answer": "ていえん",
      "meaning": "garden, park"
    },
    {
      "question": "部室",
      "answer": "ぶしつ",
      "meaning": "clubroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "同",
      "answer": "どう",
      "meaning": "the same, the said, ibid."
    },
    {
      "question": "解き放つ",
      "answer": "ときはなつ",
      "meaning": "to release"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚れ",
      "answer": "けがれ,よごれ",
      "meaning": "uncleanness, impurity, defilement, disgrace, shame, stain, blot, corruption, depravity, uncleanlines"
    },
    {
      "question": "過剰",
      "answer": "かじょう",
      "meaning": "excess, surplus, superabundance, overabundance"
    },
    {
      "question": "有する",
      "answer": "ゆうする",
      "meaning": "to have, to possess, to own, to be endowed with"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭を振る",
      "answer": "かぶりをふる",
      "meaning": "to shake one's head (in denial)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶頂",
      "answer": "ぜっちょう",
      "meaning": "top (of a mountain), summit, peak, height, zenith, climax, orgasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "溜める",
      "answer": "ためる",
      "meaning": "to amass, to accumulate, to store, to leave unpaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘やかす",
      "answer": "あまやかす",
      "meaning": "to pamper, to spoil"
    },
    {
      "question": "過程",
      "answer": "かてい",
      "meaning": "process, course, mechanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞘",
      "answer": "さや",
      "meaning": "scabbard, sheath, cap (on pen, brush, etc.), case, sleeve, margin (between two prices), spread, mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "障害",
      "answer": "しょうがい",
      "meaning": "obstacle, impediment, hindrance, difficulty, barrier, handicap, impairment, disability, disorder, ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "上機嫌",
      "answer": "じょうきげん",
      "meaning": "good humour (humor), good mood"
    },
    {
      "question": "核",
      "answer": "かく,さね",
      "meaning": "stone (of a fruit), pit, pip, core (of an organization, team, etc.), nucleus, heart, nuclear weapons"
    },
    {
      "question": "回答",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "reply, answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "直感",
      "answer": "ちょっかん",
      "meaning": "intuition, instinct, insight, hunch, immediacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿す",
      "answer": "やどす,しゅくす",
      "meaning": "to house, to contain, to harbour (a feeling), to hold (e.g. dew on leaves), to carry (a baby), to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "提示",
      "answer": "ていじ",
      "meaning": "presentation, exhibit, suggest, citation"
    },
    {
      "question": "見極める",
      "answer": "みきわめる",
      "meaning": "to ascertain, to make sure of, to determine, to probe, to get to the bottom (of something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "空ける",
      "answer": "あける,うつける",
      "meaning": "to empty, to remove, to make space, to make room, to move out, to clear out, to be away from (e.g. o"
    },
    {
      "question": "症状",
      "answer": "しょうじょう",
      "meaning": "symptoms, condition (of a patient)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲良し",
      "answer": "なかよし",
      "meaning": "intimate friend, close friend, bosom buddy, chum"
    },
    {
      "question": "工房",
      "answer": "こうぼう",
      "meaning": "workshop, studio, atelier"
    },
    {
      "question": "努める",
      "answer": "つとめる",
      "meaning": "to endeavor (endeavour), to try, to strive, to make an effort, to exert oneself, to be diligent, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "流石",
      "answer": "さすが",
      "meaning": "as one would expect, just as you'd expect (from), just like (someone), still, all the same, after al"
    },
    {
      "question": "国境",
      "answer": "こっきょう,くにざかい",
      "meaning": "national border, provincial border"
    },
    {
      "question": "援護",
      "answer": "えんご",
      "meaning": "covering, protection, backing, relief"
    },
    {
      "question": "道中",
      "answer": "どうちゅう,みちなか",
      "meaning": "journey, trip, travels, during the journey, on the way, while travelling, middle of the road, on the"
    },
    {
      "question": "十数",
      "answer": "じゅうすう",
      "meaning": "ten-odd, a dozen or so"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制的",
      "answer": "きょうせいてき",
      "meaning": "forced, compulsory"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸める",
      "answer": "まるめる",
      "meaning": "to make round, to roll up, to curl up, to seduce, to cajole, to explain away, to round off (a fracti"
    },
    {
      "question": "温もり",
      "answer": "ぬくもり",
      "meaning": "warmth"
    },
    {
      "question": "手遅れ",
      "answer": "ておくれ",
      "meaning": "being too late, losing one's final chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を打つ",
      "answer": "てをうつ",
      "meaning": "to take measures (in face of events being anticipated), to come to an agreement (in bargaining, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み干す",
      "answer": "のみほす",
      "meaning": "to drink up, to drain (cup)"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝物",
      "answer": "たからもの,ほうもつ",
      "meaning": "treasure, treasured item, prized possession"
    },
    {
      "question": "保管",
      "answer": "ほかん",
      "meaning": "charge, custody, safekeeping, deposit, storage"
    },
    {
      "question": "不良",
      "answer": "ふりょう",
      "meaning": "bad, poor, inferior, delinquent, hoodlum, hooligan"
    },
    {
      "question": "定期的",
      "answer": "ていきてき",
      "meaning": "periodic, regular, routine"
    },
    {
      "question": "降り立つ",
      "answer": "おりたつ",
      "meaning": "to go down and stand, to alight, to get down"
    },
    {
      "question": "一流",
      "answer": "いちりゅう",
      "meaning": "first-class, top grade, foremost, top-notch, leading, characteristic, peculiar, unique, school (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "小型",
      "answer": "こがた",
      "meaning": "small, small-sized, small-scale, miniature"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い切り",
      "answer": "おもいきり",
      "meaning": "with all one's strength, with all one's heart, to the utmost, resolution, decisiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈辱",
      "answer": "くつじょく",
      "meaning": "disgrace, humiliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "金貨",
      "answer": "きんか",
      "meaning": "gold coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き離す",
      "answer": "ひきはなす",
      "meaning": "to pull apart, to separate, to have a lead over, to pull ahead of, to outdistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "政治",
      "answer": "せいじ",
      "meaning": "politics, government"
    },
    {
      "question": "咆哮",
      "answer": "ほうこう",
      "meaning": "roar, howl, yell, bellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "独立",
      "answer": "どくりつ",
      "meaning": "independence, self-reliance, supporting oneself, being on one's own, independence (e.g. of a nation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "両足",
      "answer": "りょうそく,りょうあし,もろあし",
      "meaning": "both feet, both legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯気",
      "answer": "ゆげ",
      "meaning": "steam, vapour, vapor"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ越す",
      "answer": "ひっこす",
      "meaning": "to move (house), to change residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "土下座",
      "answer": "どげざ",
      "meaning": "kneeling down on the ground, prostrate oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "最大限",
      "answer": "さいだいげん",
      "meaning": "maximum, to the maximum degree, to the full"
    },
    {
      "question": "着せる",
      "answer": "きせる",
      "meaning": "to put clothes on (someone), to plate, to gild, to veneer, to accuse (of some crime), to give (a bad"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓喜",
      "answer": "かんき",
      "meaning": "delight, great joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "手袋",
      "answer": "てぶくろ",
      "meaning": "glove, mitten, mitt"
    },
    {
      "question": "崖",
      "answer": "がけ",
      "meaning": "cliff, precipice, brink of a dangerous situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ青",
      "answer": "まっさお",
      "meaning": "deep blue, bright blue, ghastly pale, pallid, white as a sheet"
    },
    {
      "question": "水晶",
      "answer": "すいしょう",
      "meaning": "(rock) crystal, high purity quartz"
    },
    {
      "question": "市場",
      "answer": "いちば,しじょう",
      "meaning": "(town) market, (street) market, marketplace, market (financial, stock, domestic, etc.), exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "傲慢",
      "answer": "ごうまん",
      "meaning": "haughty, arrogant, insolent, proud, overbearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "青白い",
      "answer": "あおじろい",
      "meaning": "pale, pallid, bluish-white"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲高い",
      "answer": "かんだかい",
      "meaning": "high-pitched, shrill"
    },
    {
      "question": "稽古",
      "answer": "けいこ",
      "meaning": "practice, practising, training, study"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が国",
      "answer": "わがくに",
      "meaning": "our country, our land, one's own country"
    },
    {
      "question": "特訓",
      "answer": "とっくん",
      "meaning": "special training, intensive training, crash course"
    },
    {
      "question": "回数",
      "answer": "かいすう",
      "meaning": "number of times, frequency, count"
    },
    {
      "question": "何日",
      "answer": "なんにち",
      "meaning": "what day, how many days"
    },
    {
      "question": "一段",
      "answer": "いちだん,いったん",
      "meaning": "more, much more, still more, all the more, step, rung, level, rank, paragraph, passage, ichidan (ver"
    },
    {
      "question": "駒",
      "answer": "こま",
      "meaning": "piece (in shogi, chess, etc.), horse, foal, bridge (of a violin, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "異性",
      "answer": "いせい",
      "meaning": "the opposite sex, isomerism"
    },
    {
      "question": "殲滅",
      "answer": "せんめつ",
      "meaning": "extermination, annihilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰め込む",
      "answer": "つめこむ",
      "meaning": "to cram, to stuff, to jam, to squeeze, to compress, to pack, to crowd"
    },
    {
      "question": "箸",
      "answer": "はし",
      "meaning": "chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦術",
      "answer": "せんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷やす",
      "answer": "ひやす",
      "meaning": "to cool (from room temperature), to chill, to refrigerate, to calm down, to cool off, to regain one'"
    },
    {
      "question": "殆ど",
      "answer": "ほとんど",
      "meaning": "mostly, nearly, practically, well-nigh, almost invariably, all but, just about, almost"
    },
    {
      "question": "送り出す",
      "answer": "おくりだす",
      "meaning": "to send out, to forward, to show (a person) out"
    },
    {
      "question": "怯む",
      "answer": "ひるむ",
      "meaning": "to falter, to flinch (from), to recoil (from), to quail (at)"
    },
    {
      "question": "測る",
      "answer": "はかる",
      "meaning": "to measure, to weigh, to survey, to time (sound, gauge, estimate), to conjecture, to infer, to surmi"
    },
    {
      "question": "制止",
      "answer": "せいし",
      "meaning": "control, check, restraint, inhibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "気を抜く",
      "answer": "きをぬく",
      "meaning": "to lose focus, to let one's mind wander, to relax one's attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠢く",
      "answer": "うごめく",
      "meaning": "to wriggle, to squirm, to crawl like a worm"
    },
    {
      "question": "加工",
      "answer": "かこう",
      "meaning": "manufacturing, processing, treatment, machining"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆無",
      "answer": "かいむ",
      "meaning": "nonexistent, nil, none, nothing (at all), bugger-all"
    },
    {
      "question": "功績",
      "answer": "こうせき",
      "meaning": "achievement, meritorious deed, distinguished service, contribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "内臓",
      "answer": "ないぞう",
      "meaning": "internal organs, intestines, viscera"
    },
    {
      "question": "無傷",
      "answer": "むきず",
      "meaning": "unhurt, uninjured, unwounded, unscathed, unharmed, flawless (e.g. gem), unblemished, undamaged, perf"
    },
    {
      "question": "露出",
      "answer": "ろしゅつ",
      "meaning": "exposure, laying bare, baring (e.g. skin), (photographic) exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "食器",
      "answer": "しょっき",
      "meaning": "tableware"
    },
    {
      "question": "存じる",
      "answer": "ぞんじる",
      "meaning": "to think, feel, consider, know, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "家具",
      "answer": "かぐ",
      "meaning": "furniture"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽織る",
      "answer": "はおる",
      "meaning": "to put on (coat, gown, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "討つ",
      "answer": "うつ",
      "meaning": "to shoot (at), to attack, to defeat, to destroy, to avenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "執着",
      "answer": "しゅうちゃく,しゅうじゃく",
      "meaning": "attachment, adhesion, tenacity, fixation, obsession"
    },
    {
      "question": "番組",
      "answer": "ばんぐみ",
      "meaning": "program (e.g. TV), programme"
    },
    {
      "question": "脅かす",
      "answer": "おどかす,おびやかす",
      "meaning": "to threaten, to menace, to intimidate, to startle, to frighten, to scare, to threaten (e.g. peace),"
    },
    {
      "question": "密か",
      "answer": "ひそか",
      "meaning": "secret, private, surreptitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ合う",
      "answer": "ふれあう",
      "meaning": "to come into contact with, to touch (each other), to have a brush with"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ黒",
      "answer": "まっくろ",
      "meaning": "pitch black"
    },
    {
      "question": "向かい",
      "answer": "むかい",
      "meaning": "facing, opposite, across the street, other side"
    },
    {
      "question": "予約",
      "answer": "よやく",
      "meaning": "reservation, appointment, booking, advance order, contract, subscription, pledge, programming (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "絞り出す",
      "answer": "しぼりだす",
      "meaning": "to squeeze out, to wring out"
    },
    {
      "question": "動画",
      "answer": "どうが",
      "meaning": "video, movie, moving picture, animation, animated cartoon, in-betweens (animation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪悪",
      "answer": "じゃあく",
      "meaning": "wicked, evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜入",
      "answer": "せんにゅう",
      "meaning": "infiltration, sneaking in, going undercover"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き",
      "answer": "いき,ゆき",
      "meaning": "the way there, outbound leg, outbound trip, departing leg, bound for ..., outbound ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍人",
      "answer": "ぐんじん",
      "meaning": "military personnel, soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "足を運ぶ",
      "answer": "あしをはこぶ",
      "meaning": "to go, to come, to turn out (at a meeting, event, etc.), to show up, to make your way to"
    },
    {
      "question": "幻想",
      "answer": "げんそう",
      "meaning": "fantasy, illusion, vision, dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "万全",
      "answer": "ばんぜん",
      "meaning": "perfection, flawlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り札",
      "answer": "きりふだ",
      "meaning": "trump card, ace up one's sleeve, secret weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "浴びせる",
      "answer": "あびせる",
      "meaning": "to pour on"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し倒す",
      "answer": "おしたおす",
      "meaning": "to pin down, to knock down, to push (and hold) somebody down (esp. with sexual connotations)"
    },
    {
      "question": "浄化",
      "answer": "じょうか",
      "meaning": "purification, cleanup (e.g. of politics), purge"
    },
    {
      "question": "華奢",
      "answer": "きゃしゃ,かしゃ",
      "meaning": "dainty, delicate, slender, slim and elegant, fragile (e.g. furniture), frail, lavish, luxurious, sho"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養",
      "answer": "えいよう",
      "meaning": "nutrition, nourishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲直り",
      "answer": "なかなおり",
      "meaning": "reconciliation, make peace with"
    },
    {
      "question": "大嫌い",
      "answer": "だいきらい",
      "meaning": "detestable, abhorrent, loathsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "流れ込む",
      "answer": "ながれこむ",
      "meaning": "to flow into, to pour into, to stream into"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い分",
      "answer": "いいぶん",
      "meaning": "one's say, one's point, complaint, grievance, objection, excuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠実",
      "answer": "ちゅうじつ,まめ",
      "meaning": "faithful, devoted, loyal, honest, true, diligent, hardworking, conscientious, sincere, healthy, fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺跡",
      "answer": "いせき",
      "meaning": "historic ruins (remains, relics), archeological site"
    },
    {
      "question": "取材",
      "answer": "しゅざい",
      "meaning": "news coverage, collecting data (e.g. for an article), covering (something for media), interview"
    },
    {
      "question": "前進",
      "answer": "ぜんしん",
      "meaning": "advance, moving forward, progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "素",
      "answer": "もと,そ,す",
      "meaning": "origin, source, base, basis, foundation, root, cause, ingredient, material, original cost (or capita"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹っ飛ぶ",
      "answer": "ふっとぶ",
      "meaning": "to blow off, to be blown off"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り返す",
      "answer": "とりかえす",
      "meaning": "to get back, to regain, to recover, to make up (for), to catch up on"
    },
    {
      "question": "強いる",
      "answer": "しいる",
      "meaning": "to force, to compel, to coerce, to press, to impose"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛る",
      "answer": "さかる,もる",
      "meaning": "to prosper, to flourish, to copulate (animals), to serve (in a bowl, on a plate, etc.), to dish out,"
    },
    {
      "question": "目元",
      "answer": "めもと",
      "meaning": "eyes, expression of the eyes, area around the eyes, skin round one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "委員長",
      "answer": "いいんちょう",
      "meaning": "(committee) chairman, president"
    },
    {
      "question": "不自由",
      "answer": "ふじゆう",
      "meaning": "discomfort, inconvenience, poverty, want, destitution, disability, impairment (physical, mental, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴く",
      "answer": "あばく",
      "meaning": "to disclose, to divulge, to expose, to open (and rob) a grave"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏側",
      "answer": "うらがわ",
      "meaning": "the reverse, other side, lining"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝言",
      "answer": "でんごん,つてこと",
      "meaning": "verbal message, word (from someone), rumour, rumor"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿",
      "answer": "さる,ましら,まし",
      "meaning": "monkey (esp. the Japanese macaque, Macaca fuscata), ape, non-human primate, sly person, idiot, hick,"
    },
    {
      "question": "放出",
      "answer": "ほうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "release, emission, ejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己",
      "answer": "じこ",
      "meaning": "self, oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔道",
      "answer": "まどう",
      "meaning": "heresy, evil ways, path of evil, sorcery, black magic, netherworld, world outside the six realms whe"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄色",
      "answer": "きいろ,こうしょく,おうしょく",
      "meaning": "yellow, amber"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳房",
      "answer": "ちぶさ,にゅうぼう",
      "meaning": "breast, udder"
    },
    {
      "question": "決心",
      "answer": "けっしん",
      "meaning": "determination, resolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "無様",
      "answer": "ぶざま",
      "meaning": "unshapely, unsightly, clumsy, unpresentable, uncouth, awkward, ungainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "失望",
      "answer": "しつぼう",
      "meaning": "disappointment, despair"
    },
    {
      "question": "独自",
      "answer": "どくじ",
      "meaning": "original, unique, distinctive, characteristic, peculiar, independent, one's own, personal"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き先",
      "answer": "いきさき,ゆきさき",
      "meaning": "destination, whereabouts, future, prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "説得力",
      "answer": "せっとくりょく",
      "meaning": "persuasiveness, powers of persuasion, cogency"
    },
    {
      "question": "延々",
      "answer": "えんえん",
      "meaning": "forever, endlessly, on and on, meandering, wandering, winding, sinuous, serpentine, zigzagging"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り絞る",
      "answer": "ふりしぼる",
      "meaning": "to use to the full (one's voice, energy, etc.), to muster all of (one's strength, courage, etc.), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "部員",
      "answer": "ぶいん",
      "meaning": "staff, member (club, society, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "補給",
      "answer": "ほきゅう",
      "meaning": "supply, supplying, replenishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "家事",
      "answer": "かじ",
      "meaning": "housework, domestic chores, family affairs, household matters"
    },
    {
      "question": "封筒",
      "answer": "ふうとう",
      "meaning": "envelope"
    },
    {
      "question": "週",
      "answer": "しゅう",
      "meaning": "week"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠ざける",
      "answer": "とおざける",
      "meaning": "to keep away, to keep at a distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "募る",
      "answer": "つのる",
      "meaning": "to become stronger, to grow in intensity, to grow violent, to become worse, to invite contributions,"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃走",
      "answer": "とうそう",
      "meaning": "flight, desertion, escape"
    },
    {
      "question": "日差し",
      "answer": "ひざし",
      "meaning": "sunlight, rays of the Sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "喫茶店",
      "answer": "きっさてん,きっちゃてん",
      "meaning": "coffee shop, tearoom, coffee lounge, coffeehouse, cafe"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰",
      "answer": "はい",
      "meaning": "ash, ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "企画",
      "answer": "きかく",
      "meaning": "planning, project, plan, design"
    },
    {
      "question": "宰相",
      "answer": "さいしょう",
      "meaning": "prime minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し出る",
      "answer": "もうしでる",
      "meaning": "to report to, to tell, to suggest, to submit, to request, to make an offer, to come forward with inf"
    },
    {
      "question": "紳士",
      "answer": "しんし",
      "meaning": "gentleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "本質",
      "answer": "ほんしつ",
      "meaning": "essence, true nature, substance, reality"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞭",
      "answer": "むち,ぶち",
      "meaning": "whip, lash, scourge, stick, cane, rod, pointer"
    },
    {
      "question": "兄上",
      "answer": "あにうえ",
      "meaning": "older brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "包帯",
      "answer": "ほうたい",
      "meaning": "bandage, dressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "正常",
      "answer": "せいじょう",
      "meaning": "normalcy, normality, normal"
    },
    {
      "question": "細める",
      "answer": "ほそめる",
      "meaning": "to make narrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "見直す",
      "answer": "みなおす",
      "meaning": "to look at again, to re-examine (policy, estimate, plan, etc.), to review, to get a better opinion o"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れる",
      "answer": "かれる",
      "meaning": "to wither (of a plant), to be blasted, to die, to mature (of one's personality, abilities, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "解説",
      "answer": "かいせつ",
      "meaning": "explanation, commentary, exposition, elucidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "大物",
      "answer": "おおもの",
      "meaning": "important person, influential figure, big shot, big name, bigwig, heavyweight, big game, big catch,"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫁ぐ",
      "answer": "とつぐ",
      "meaning": "to marry (of a woman), to become a bride, to marry into (a family), to have sexual intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "無し",
      "answer": "なし",
      "meaning": "without, unacceptable, not alright, unsatisfactory"
    },
    {
      "question": "砦",
      "answer": "とりで",
      "meaning": "fort, fortress, stronghold, fortification"
    },
    {
      "question": "青春",
      "answer": "せいしゅん",
      "meaning": "youth, springtime of life, adolescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き続く",
      "answer": "ひきつづく",
      "meaning": "to continue (for a long time), to occur in succession, to come next (e.g. on TV)"
    },
    {
      "question": "動機",
      "answer": "どうき",
      "meaning": "motive, incentive, motif"
    },
    {
      "question": "刃物",
      "answer": "はもの",
      "meaning": "edged tool, cutlery"
    },
    {
      "question": "不敵",
      "answer": "ふてき",
      "meaning": "daring, fearless, intrepid, bold, tough"
    },
    {
      "question": "改善",
      "answer": "かいぜん",
      "meaning": "betterment, improvement, kaizen (Japanese business philosophy of continuous improvement)"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣服",
      "answer": "いふく",
      "meaning": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "記念",
      "answer": "きねん",
      "meaning": "commemoration, celebration, honoring the memory of something, turning something into a memento, memo"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽り",
      "answer": "いつわり",
      "meaning": "lie, falsehood, fiction, fabrication"
    },
    {
      "question": "後頭部",
      "answer": "こうとうぶ",
      "meaning": "back of head"
    },
    {
      "question": "身動き",
      "answer": "みうごき",
      "meaning": "moving about, stirring about"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸",
      "answer": "と,こ",
      "meaning": "door (esp. Japanese-style), shutter, window shutter, entrance (to a home), narrows, counter for hous"
    },
    {
      "question": "一連",
      "answer": "いちれん",
      "meaning": "series, chain, sequence, two reams (i.e. 1000 sheets of paper), verse, stanza"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶える",
      "answer": "たえる",
      "meaning": "to die out, to peter out, to become extinct, to cease, to be stopped, to be discontinued, to be cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "大通り",
      "answer": "おおどおり",
      "meaning": "main street"
    },
    {
      "question": "根元",
      "answer": "こんげん,ねもと",
      "meaning": "root, source, origin, foundation, base, principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "配下",
      "answer": "はいか",
      "meaning": "followers, subordinates, being under someone's command"
    },
    {
      "question": "迂闊",
      "answer": "うかつ",
      "meaning": "careless, stupid, thoughtless, heedless, unobservant, inadvertent, incautious"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て直す",
      "answer": "たてなおす",
      "meaning": "to put back up, to stand back up, to restore (to former strength), to revive (e.g. the economy), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶民",
      "answer": "しょみん",
      "meaning": "common people, ordinary people, masses"
    },
    {
      "question": "激痛",
      "answer": "げきつう",
      "meaning": "sharp pain, acute pain, intense pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "感嘆",
      "answer": "かんたん",
      "meaning": "admiration, wonder, astonishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸念",
      "answer": "けねん",
      "meaning": "worry, fear, anxiety, concern"
    },
    {
      "question": "採用",
      "answer": "さいよう",
      "meaning": "use, adoption, acceptance, appointment, employment, engagement, recruitment"
    },
    {
      "question": "居間",
      "answer": "いま",
      "meaning": "living room (Western style), sitting room"
    },
    {
      "question": "後日",
      "answer": "ごじつ,ごにち",
      "meaning": "in the future, another day, later"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕",
      "answer": "まく",
      "meaning": "curtain, bunting, act (in play)"
    },
    {
      "question": "引退",
      "answer": "いんたい",
      "meaning": "retirement"
    },
    {
      "question": "情",
      "answer": "じょう",
      "meaning": "feelings, emotion, sentiment, compassion, sympathy, passion, affection, love, the way things really"
    },
    {
      "question": "営業",
      "answer": "えいぎょう",
      "meaning": "business, trade, operations, sales"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥棒",
      "answer": "どろぼう",
      "meaning": "thief, burglar, robber, theft, burglary, robbery"
    },
    {
      "question": "励む",
      "answer": "はげむ",
      "meaning": "to strive, to endeavour, to endeavor, to make an effort, to be zealous"
    },
    {
      "question": "無能",
      "answer": "むのう",
      "meaning": "incompetence, inefficiency, inability, incapacity, incompetent person"
    },
    {
      "question": "上目遣い",
      "answer": "うわめづかい",
      "meaning": "upturned eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "収納",
      "answer": "しゅうのう",
      "meaning": "storage, putting or stowing away, receipt (of funds, payment, etc.), harvesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "保存",
      "answer": "ほぞん",
      "meaning": "preservation, conservation, storage, maintenance, saving (e.g. to disk)"
    },
    {
      "question": "四つ",
      "answer": "よっつ,よつ",
      "meaning": "four, four years of age, ten o'clock (old time system), cross grips"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護者",
      "answer": "ほごしゃ",
      "meaning": "guardian, protector, patron, parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "視点",
      "answer": "してん",
      "meaning": "opinion, point of view, visual point"
    },
    {
      "question": "短剣",
      "answer": "たんけん",
      "meaning": "short sword, dagger, stiletto, hour hand (of a clock)"
    },
    {
      "question": "照明",
      "answer": "しょうめい",
      "meaning": "illumination, lighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "侮る",
      "answer": "あなどる,あなずる",
      "meaning": "to disdain, to look down on, to make light of, to hold in contempt, to scorn, to despise"
    },
    {
      "question": "港",
      "answer": "みなと,こう",
      "meaning": "harbour, harbor, port"
    },
    {
      "question": "未練",
      "answer": "みれん",
      "meaning": "lingering attachment, lingering affection, regret, reluctance, ruefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "棟",
      "answer": "とう,むね",
      "meaning": "large building, building with a long roof, counter for buildings, apartments, etc., ridge (of roof),"
    },
    {
      "question": "明白",
      "answer": "めいはく,あからさま",
      "meaning": "obvious, clear, plain, evident, apparent, explicit, overt, frank, candid, open, direct, straightforw"
    },
    {
      "question": "構え",
      "answer": "かまえ",
      "meaning": "structure, construction, appearance, posture (e.g. in martial arts), pose, stance, readiness, determ"
    },
    {
      "question": "真正面",
      "answer": "ましょうめん",
      "meaning": "directly opposite, right in front"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち直る",
      "answer": "たちなおる",
      "meaning": "to regain one's footing, to get back on one's feet, to recover, (of the market) to improve"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き返る",
      "answer": "いきかえる",
      "meaning": "to revive, to come to oneself, to be restored to life"
    },
    {
      "question": "信仰",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "(religious) faith, belief, creed"
    },
    {
      "question": "折角",
      "answer": "せっかく",
      "meaning": "with trouble, at great pains, rare, valuable, precious, long-awaited, kind, generous, specially, esp"
    },
    {
      "question": "成り立つ",
      "answer": "なりたつ",
      "meaning": "to consist of, to be made up of, to be composed of, to be concluded (e.g. of an agreement), to hold"
    },
    {
      "question": "映し出す",
      "answer": "うつしだす",
      "meaning": "to project, to show, to portray, to depict, to describe, to reflect"
    },
    {
      "question": "重",
      "answer": "おも,え,じゅう",
      "meaning": "chief, main, principal, important, main secondary or supporting role (in kyogen), -fold, -ply, jūbak"
    },
    {
      "question": "重たい",
      "answer": "おもたい",
      "meaning": "heavy, weighty, heavy (feeling, atmosphere, etc.), serious, gloomy, depressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "率",
      "answer": "りつ",
      "meaning": "rate, ratio, proportion, percentage"
    },
    {
      "question": "調理",
      "answer": "ちょうり",
      "meaning": "cooking, food preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "必殺",
      "answer": "ひっさつ",
      "meaning": "bringing certain death, deadly, knockout (blow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金持ち",
      "answer": "かねもち",
      "meaning": "rich person"
    },
    {
      "question": "料理人",
      "answer": "りょうりにん",
      "meaning": "cook, chef"
    },
    {
      "question": "相応",
      "answer": "そうおう",
      "meaning": "suitable, appropriate, befitting, becoming, adequate, reasonable, proper, conjoining, association, s"
    },
    {
      "question": "真",
      "answer": "しん,ま,まな",
      "meaning": "truth, reality, genuineness, seriousness, logical truth, printed style writing, star performer, just"
    },
    {
      "question": "苛立つ",
      "answer": "いらだつ",
      "meaning": "to be irritated, to get annoyed, to lose one's patience"
    },
    {
      "question": "足止め",
      "answer": "あしどめ",
      "meaning": "preventing (someone) from leaving, confinement, keeping indoors, inducement to stay, being stranded,"
    },
    {
      "question": "真意",
      "answer": "しんい",
      "meaning": "real intention, true motive, true meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え事",
      "answer": "かんがえごと",
      "meaning": "something to think about, one's thoughts, concern, worry, thinking about something, being absorbed i"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ込む",
      "answer": "ひっこむ",
      "meaning": "to draw back, to sink, to cave in, to be set back (e.g. from a road), to withdraw (e.g. from the pub"
    },
    {
      "question": "振る舞い",
      "answer": "ふるまい",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour, conduct, entertainment, treat, feast, banquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄",
      "answer": "なわ",
      "meaning": "rope, cord, policeman's rope"
    },
    {
      "question": "一家",
      "answer": "いっか,いっけ",
      "meaning": "a family, a household, a home, one's family, whole family, (one's own) style, school, gang, (yakuza)"
    },
    {
      "question": "世代",
      "answer": "せだい",
      "meaning": "generation, the world, the age"
    },
    {
      "question": "性別",
      "answer": "せいべつ",
      "meaning": "gender, distinction of sex, sex"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜜",
      "answer": "みつ,みち",
      "meaning": "nectar, honey, honeydew, treacle, molasses, sorbitol (when visible as dark patches inside an apple)"
    },
    {
      "question": "現実的",
      "answer": "げんじつてき",
      "meaning": "realistic, pragmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "訪問",
      "answer": "ほうもん",
      "meaning": "call, visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "関心",
      "answer": "かんしん",
      "meaning": "concern, interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "自業自得",
      "answer": "じごうじとく",
      "meaning": "paying for one's mistakes, getting one's just deserts, suffering the consequences (of one's own acti"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂気",
      "answer": "きょうき",
      "meaning": "madness, insanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "思案",
      "answer": "しあん",
      "meaning": "careful thought, consideration, deliberation, reflection, rumination, pondering"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩き回る",
      "answer": "あるきまわる",
      "meaning": "to walk about, to walk to and fro, to pace around"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳重",
      "answer": "げんじゅう,げんじょう,げんちょう",
      "meaning": "strict, severe, stringent, rigorous, rigid, firm, strong, secure"
    },
    {
      "question": "吠える",
      "answer": "ほえる",
      "meaning": "to bark, to howl, to bay, to bellow, to howl (e.g. of the wind), to roar, to yell, to cry, to moan,"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が済む",
      "answer": "きがすむ",
      "meaning": "to be satisfied, to find peace of mind, to feel good"
    },
    {
      "question": "中年",
      "answer": "ちゅうねん",
      "meaning": "middle-age, middle age, midlife, one's middle years"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅立つ",
      "answer": "たびだつ",
      "meaning": "to begin a trip, to depart, to embark, to die, to pass away, to depart this life"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽",
      "answer": "にせ,ぎ",
      "meaning": "imitation, fake, phony, counterfeit, forged, bogus, sham, pseudo-, falseness (logic), falsehood"
    },
    {
      "question": "一室",
      "answer": "いっしつ",
      "meaning": "one room"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳躍",
      "answer": "ちょうやく",
      "meaning": "jump, leap, skip, bound"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶悪",
      "answer": "きょうあく",
      "meaning": "atrocious, fiendish, brutal, villainous"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅前",
      "answer": "えきまえ",
      "meaning": "in front of a station"
    },
    {
      "question": "合間",
      "answer": "あいま",
      "meaning": "interval, break, pause, spare moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "出向く",
      "answer": "でむく",
      "meaning": "to go to, to proceed to, to leave for"
    },
    {
      "question": "使者",
      "answer": "ししゃ",
      "meaning": "messenger, envoy, emissary"
    },
    {
      "question": "高鳴る",
      "answer": "たかなる",
      "meaning": "to throb, to beat fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "零れる",
      "answer": "こぼれる",
      "meaning": "to spill, to fall out of, to overflow, to peek through, to become visible (although normally not), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を回す",
      "answer": "てをまわす",
      "meaning": "to use one's influence, to pull strings, to take measures, to make the necessary preparations"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪型",
      "answer": "かみがた",
      "meaning": "hair style, coiffure, hairdo"
    },
    {
      "question": "命中",
      "answer": "めいちゅう",
      "meaning": "(direct) hit, hitting the mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り繕う",
      "answer": "とりつくろう",
      "meaning": "to keep up (appearances), to smooth over (an error, etc.), to gloss over, to varnish over, to pallia"
    },
    {
      "question": "復帰",
      "answer": "ふっき",
      "meaning": "return, comeback, reinstatement, carriage return, CR"
    },
    {
      "question": "拳銃",
      "answer": "けんじゅう",
      "meaning": "pistol, handgun, revolver"
    },
    {
      "question": "壊滅",
      "answer": "かいめつ",
      "meaning": "destruction, annihilation, devastation, catastrophe"
    },
    {
      "question": "存在感",
      "answer": "そんざいかん",
      "meaning": "presence (impressive quality)"
    },
    {
      "question": "販売",
      "answer": "はんばい",
      "meaning": "sales, selling, marketing"
    },
    {
      "question": "流し込む",
      "answer": "ながしこむ",
      "meaning": "to pour into, to wash down, to insert (e.g. into a data stream)"
    },
    {
      "question": "要塞",
      "answer": "ようさい",
      "meaning": "fort, stronghold, fortification"
    },
    {
      "question": "無敵",
      "answer": "むてき",
      "meaning": "invincible, unrivaled, unrivalled, matchless, unbeatable, undefeatable"
    },
    {
      "question": "修正",
      "answer": "しゅうせい",
      "meaning": "amendment, correction, revision, modification, alteration, retouching, update, fix"
    },
    {
      "question": "妖怪",
      "answer": "ようかい",
      "meaning": "ghost, apparition, phantom, spectre, specter, demon, monster, goblin"
    },
    {
      "question": "背景",
      "answer": "はいけい",
      "meaning": "background, scenery, backdrop, setting, background (of an incident, situation, etc.), circumstances,"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛行機",
      "answer": "ひこうき",
      "meaning": "aeroplane, airplane, aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩",
      "answer": "おん",
      "meaning": "favour, favor, obligation, debt of gratitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "改造",
      "answer": "かいぞう",
      "meaning": "remodeling, remodelling, restructuring, reconstruction, reshuffling (e.g. cabinet), modding"
    },
    {
      "question": "区",
      "answer": "く",
      "meaning": "ward, borough, city (in Tokyo), district (e.g. electoral), section, zone (e.g. postal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前日",
      "answer": "ぜんじつ,まえび",
      "meaning": "previous day, day before, eve, prior day, preceding day"
    },
    {
      "question": "最善",
      "answer": "さいぜん",
      "meaning": "the very best, utmost"
    },
    {
      "question": "双方",
      "answer": "そうほう",
      "meaning": "both parties, both sides"
    },
    {
      "question": "要望",
      "answer": "ようぼう",
      "meaning": "demand for, request"
    },
    {
      "question": "軋む",
      "answer": "きしむ",
      "meaning": "to jar, to creak, to grate"
    },
    {
      "question": "動き回る",
      "answer": "うごきまわる",
      "meaning": "to move around"
    },
    {
      "question": "牽制",
      "answer": "けんせい",
      "meaning": "check, keeping in check, restraint, curbing, reining in, discouraging (from doing), containment (of"
    },
    {
      "question": "訂正",
      "answer": "ていせい",
      "meaning": "correction, revision, amendment"
    },
    {
      "question": "地区",
      "answer": "ちく",
      "meaning": "district, section, sector"
    },
    {
      "question": "同盟",
      "answer": "どうめい",
      "meaning": "alliance, union, league"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐縮",
      "answer": "きょうしゅく",
      "meaning": "feeling obliged, being grateful, being thankful, being sorry, being ashamed, shrinking back in fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "推理",
      "answer": "すいり",
      "meaning": "reasoning, inference, deduction, mystery or detective genre"
    },
    {
      "question": "紋章",
      "answer": "もんしょう",
      "meaning": "crest, coat of arms"
    },
    {
      "question": "形成",
      "answer": "けいせい",
      "meaning": "formation, molding, making up, taking form, giving form to, repair (e.g. plastic surgery), replaceme"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い込む",
      "answer": "くいこむ",
      "meaning": "to bite into (e.g. rope into skin), to cut into, to dig into (e.g. of fingernails), to eat into, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉",
      "answer": "こな,こ",
      "meaning": "flour, meal, powder, dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫う",
      "answer": "ぬう",
      "meaning": "to sew, to stitch, to weave one's way (e.g. through a crowd)"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴体",
      "answer": "どうたい",
      "meaning": "body, trunk, torso, hull (boat), fuselage (aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "林",
      "answer": "はやし",
      "meaning": "woods, forest, copse, thicket, bunch, line (of something), collection"
    },
    {
      "question": "追撃",
      "answer": "ついげき",
      "meaning": "pursuit (of a fleeing enemy), chase"
    },
    {
      "question": "流行る",
      "answer": "はやる",
      "meaning": "to be popular, to come into fashion, to be prevalent, to spread widely (e.g. disease), to be endemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動",
      "answer": "じどう",
      "meaning": "automatic, intransitive verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "妊娠",
      "answer": "にんしん",
      "meaning": "conception, pregnancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "究極",
      "answer": "きゅうきょく",
      "meaning": "ultimate, final, last, eventual"
    },
    {
      "question": "気合",
      "answer": "きあい",
      "meaning": "(fighting) spirit, motivation, effort, shout (for getting in the right mood to deal with something,"
    },
    {
      "question": "設備",
      "answer": "せつび",
      "meaning": "equipment, facilities, installation, accommodations, conveniences, arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "汁",
      "answer": "しる",
      "meaning": "juice, sap, soup, broth"
    },
    {
      "question": "失格",
      "answer": "しっかく",
      "meaning": "disqualification, elimination, incapacity, being unfit for one's role, being a failure"
    },
    {
      "question": "関わり",
      "answer": "かかわり",
      "meaning": "relation, connection"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠気",
      "answer": "ねむけ",
      "meaning": "sleepiness, drowsiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "採取",
      "answer": "さいしゅ",
      "meaning": "picking, collecting, harvesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "走り回る",
      "answer": "はしりまわる",
      "meaning": "to run around"
    },
    {
      "question": "対照的",
      "answer": "たいしょうてき",
      "meaning": "contrastive"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵本",
      "answer": "えほん",
      "meaning": "picture book"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び込む",
      "answer": "しのびこむ",
      "meaning": "to creep in, to steal in"
    },
    {
      "question": "総",
      "answer": "そう,ふさ",
      "meaning": "whole, all, general, gross, entire, overall, tuft (of hair, threads, etc.), fringe, tassel, bunch (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "見透かす",
      "answer": "みすかす",
      "meaning": "to see through, to see the true nature of something"
    },
    {
      "question": "気取る",
      "answer": "きどる,けどる",
      "meaning": "to be affected, to put on airs, to act like (something one isn't), to pretend to be, to suspect, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "通話",
      "answer": "つうわ",
      "meaning": "telephone call, speaking over the telephone, (Internet) voice call, counter for telephone calls of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "助言",
      "answer": "じょげん,じょごん",
      "meaning": "advice, suggestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "断ち切る",
      "answer": "たちきる",
      "meaning": "to cut apart (cloth, paper, etc.), to sever (ties), to break off (relationship), to overcome (habit,"
    },
    {
      "question": "職場",
      "answer": "しょくば",
      "meaning": "one's post, place of work, workplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕入れる",
      "answer": "しいれる",
      "meaning": "to lay in stock, to replenish stock, to procure, to learn, to find out, to take in"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫色",
      "answer": "むらさきいろ,ししょく",
      "meaning": "purple, violet"
    },
    {
      "question": "天然",
      "answer": "てんねん",
      "meaning": "nature, spontaneity, natural airhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "無造作",
      "answer": "むぞうさ",
      "meaning": "easy, simple, ready, casual, off-hand, easy-going, careless, artless"
    },
    {
      "question": "日記",
      "answer": "にっき",
      "meaning": "diary, journal"
    },
    {
      "question": "往復",
      "answer": "おうふく",
      "meaning": "making a round trip, going and returning, coming and going, round-trip ticket, return ticket, corres"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り乱す",
      "answer": "とりみだす",
      "meaning": "to be upset, to lose one's composure, to lose self-control, to go to pieces, to be shaken up, to bre"
    },
    {
      "question": "有能",
      "answer": "ゆうのう",
      "meaning": "able, capable, competent, talented, efficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "色気",
      "answer": "いろけ",
      "meaning": "colouring, coloring, shade of colour (color), sex appeal (esp. of women), sexiness, sexual allure, s"
    },
    {
      "question": "写る",
      "answer": "うつる",
      "meaning": "to be photographed, to be projected"
    },
    {
      "question": "反発",
      "answer": "はんぱつ",
      "meaning": "opposition, rebellion, revolt, resistance, backlash, refusal, rebounding, recoiling, repulsion, rall"
    },
    {
      "question": "頰",
      "answer": "ほお,ほほ",
      "meaning": "cheek (of face)"
    },
    {
      "question": "商店街",
      "answer": "しょうてんがい",
      "meaning": "shopping district, shopping street, downtown"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆頭",
      "answer": "ひっとう,ふでがしら",
      "meaning": "brush tip, first on a list, head, chief"
    },
    {
      "question": "幅",
      "answer": "はば,の,ふく",
      "meaning": "width, breadth, freedom (e.g. of thought), latitude, gap, difference (e.g. in price), range (e.g. of"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚痴",
      "answer": "ぐち",
      "meaning": "idle complaint, grumble, moha (ignorance, folly)"
    },
    {
      "question": "行使",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "use, exercise (of one's right, authority, power, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "比較",
      "answer": "ひかく",
      "meaning": "comparison"
    },
    {
      "question": "講義",
      "answer": "こうぎ",
      "meaning": "lecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "神妙",
      "answer": "しんみょう,しんびょう",
      "meaning": "meek, quiet, docile, humble, faithful, obedient, mysterious, marvelous, marvellous"
    },
    {
      "question": "と言うと",
      "answer": "というと",
      "meaning": "when it comes to ..., if one were to speak of ..., when one hears ..., by ... you mean ..., when you"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬語",
      "answer": "けいご",
      "meaning": "honorific, term of respect, polite expression, honorific language"
    },
    {
      "question": "泉",
      "answer": "いずみ",
      "meaning": "spring, fountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "並み",
      "answer": "なみ",
      "meaning": "average, medium, common, ordinary, mid-grade (item), regular grade, same level as, equal to, equival"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊富",
      "answer": "ほうふ",
      "meaning": "abundant, plentiful, rich, ample"
    },
    {
      "question": "弄ぶ",
      "answer": "もてあそぶ",
      "meaning": "to play with (a toy, one's hair, etc.), to fiddle with, to toy with (one's emotions, etc.), to trifl"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼儀",
      "answer": "れいぎ",
      "meaning": "manners, courtesy, etiquette"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎",
      "answer": "とら",
      "meaning": "tiger (Panthera tigris), drunkard, drunk, sot"
    },
    {
      "question": "日頃",
      "answer": "ひごろ",
      "meaning": "normally, habitually"
    },
    {
      "question": "面会",
      "answer": "めんかい",
      "meaning": "meeting (face-to-face), seeing, visit, interview"
    },
    {
      "question": "称する",
      "answer": "しょうする",
      "meaning": "to take the name of, to call oneself, to pretend, to feign, to purport"
    },
    {
      "question": "担ぐ",
      "answer": "かつぐ",
      "meaning": "to shoulder, to carry on one's shoulder, to nominate for a position, to choose as a representative,"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑らか",
      "answer": "なめらか,すべらか",
      "meaning": "smooth (of a surface), glassy, velvety, soft, smooth (of an action, proceedings, etc.), fluent (spee"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き来",
      "answer": "ゆきき,いきき",
      "meaning": "coming and going, keeping in touch, visiting each other, street traffic, highway"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁じる",
      "answer": "きんじる",
      "meaning": "to prohibit"
    },
    {
      "question": "咎める",
      "answer": "とがめる",
      "meaning": "to blame, to reproach, to censure, to rebuke, to reprove, to find fault, to take to task, to critici"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り",
      "answer": "つり",
      "meaning": "fishing, angling, change (for a purchase), trolling, writing deliberately inflammatory posts online"
    },
    {
      "question": "迎撃",
      "answer": "げいげき",
      "meaning": "intercept, interception, counter-attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "誓い",
      "answer": "ちかい",
      "meaning": "oath, vow"
    },
    {
      "question": "追跡",
      "answer": "ついせき",
      "meaning": "chase, pursuit, tracking, stalking, following up, tracing"
    },
    {
      "question": "広間",
      "answer": "ひろま",
      "meaning": "hall, saloon, spacious room, reception room"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁度",
      "answer": "ちょうど",
      "meaning": "exactly, precisely, just, right, as if, as though, quite"
    },
    {
      "question": "離脱",
      "answer": "りだつ",
      "meaning": "withdrawal, secession, separation, breakaway"
    },
    {
      "question": "閃光",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "flash (of light), glint, schiller"
    },
    {
      "question": "装甲",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "armoring, armouring, armor, armour"
    },
    {
      "question": "全国",
      "answer": "ぜんこく",
      "meaning": "the whole country"
    },
    {
      "question": "足下",
      "answer": "あしもと,そっか",
      "meaning": "at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in 'watch your step'), gait, pace, step, most recent, curre"
    },
    {
      "question": "埃",
      "answer": "ほこり,あい",
      "meaning": "dust, one ten-billionth"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り切る",
      "answer": "わりきる",
      "meaning": "to find a clear solution, to come to a clean decision, to give a clear explanation, to divide exactl"
    },
    {
      "question": "跪く",
      "answer": "ひざまずく,ひざまづく",
      "meaning": "to kneel"
    },
    {
      "question": "格",
      "answer": "かく,きゃく",
      "meaning": "status, position, rank, method, way, style, rule, regulation, law, grammatical case, figure (syllogi"
    },
    {
      "question": "息苦しい",
      "answer": "いきぐるしい",
      "meaning": "choking, oppressive, suffocating"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛烈",
      "answer": "もうれつ",
      "meaning": "fierce, intense, severe, violent, strong, vehement, terrific, terrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "包囲",
      "answer": "ほうい",
      "meaning": "siege, encirclement, envelopment, surrounding, besiegement"
    },
    {
      "question": "側面",
      "answer": "そくめん",
      "meaning": "side, flank, profile, sidelight, lateral, aspect, dimension"
    },
    {
      "question": "有様",
      "answer": "ありさま,ありよう",
      "meaning": "state, condition, circumstances, sight, spectacle, the way things should be, ideal state, truth"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥じる",
      "answer": "はじる",
      "meaning": "to feel ashamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘れ物",
      "answer": "わすれもの",
      "meaning": "lost article, something forgotten"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り残す",
      "answer": "とりのこす",
      "meaning": "to leave behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪役",
      "answer": "あくやく",
      "meaning": "villain, baddie, the villain's part"
    },
    {
      "question": "察し",
      "answer": "さっし",
      "meaning": "consideration, guess, conjecture, judgment, judgement"
    },
    {
      "question": "宴",
      "answer": "うたげ,えん",
      "meaning": "party, banquet, feast"
    },
    {
      "question": "愕然",
      "answer": "がくぜん",
      "meaning": "astonished, shocked, amazed, astounded, aghast"
    },
    {
      "question": "最適",
      "answer": "さいてき",
      "meaning": "most suitable, optimum, optimal, best"
    },
    {
      "question": "青空",
      "answer": "あおぞら",
      "meaning": "blue sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い残す",
      "answer": "いいのこす",
      "meaning": "to leave word with (a person), to state in one's will, to leave (something) unsaid, to forget to men"
    },
    {
      "question": "一秒",
      "answer": "いちびょう",
      "meaning": "one second"
    },
    {
      "question": "干す",
      "answer": "ほす",
      "meaning": "to air, to dry, to desiccate, to drain (off), to drink up, to deprive of a role, job, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "一筋",
      "answer": "ひとすじ",
      "meaning": "one long straight object (e.g. strand of hair, beam of light, wisp of smoke), a single bloodline, ea"
    },
    {
      "question": "先代",
      "answer": "せんだい",
      "meaning": "previous generation (e.g. one's parents), family predecessor, predecessor, previous age"
    },
    {
      "question": "共にする",
      "answer": "ともにする",
      "meaning": "to do together, to share, to participate in"
    },
    {
      "question": "以後",
      "answer": "いご",
      "meaning": "after this, from now on, hereafter, thereafter, since (then), after"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇",
      "answer": "げき",
      "meaning": "drama, play, powerful drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "代々",
      "answer": "だいだい,よよ",
      "meaning": "for generations, hereditary, generation after generation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍛錬",
      "answer": "たんれん",
      "meaning": "tempering (metal), annealing, forging, toughening, disciplining, training"
    },
    {
      "question": "初心者",
      "answer": "しょしんしゃ",
      "meaning": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "離婚",
      "answer": "りこん",
      "meaning": "divorce"
    },
    {
      "question": "制圧",
      "answer": "せいあつ",
      "meaning": "gaining total control (of people or counties), suppression, oppression, control, mastery, ascendancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "外国",
      "answer": "がいこく,そとぐに",
      "meaning": "foreign country"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟音",
      "answer": "ごうおん",
      "meaning": "thunderous roar, roaring sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "一目",
      "answer": "ひとめ,いちもく",
      "meaning": "glance, look, glimpse, complete view, bird's-eye view, stone (in the game of go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "足場",
      "answer": "あしば",
      "meaning": "scaffold, scaffolding, foothold, footing, foothold (e.g. in business), foundation, base, convenience"
    },
    {
      "question": "姫様",
      "answer": "ひめさま",
      "meaning": "princess, daughter of a nobleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐘",
      "answer": "かね",
      "meaning": "bell (often a large hanging bell), chime"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮める",
      "answer": "ちぢめる",
      "meaning": "to shorten, to reduce, to condense, to shrink, to crumple (fabric), to wrinkle, to make (one's body)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風情",
      "answer": "ふぜい,ふうじょう",
      "meaning": "taste, elegance, charm, appearance, air, the likes of ..., lowly people such as ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "決戦",
      "answer": "けっせん",
      "meaning": "decisive battle, deciding match, play-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "調べ",
      "answer": "しらべ",
      "meaning": "investigation, inspection, examination, tune, note, melody"
    },
    {
      "question": "並",
      "answer": "なみ",
      "meaning": "average, medium, common, ordinary, mid-grade (item), regular grade, same level as, equal to, equival"
    },
    {
      "question": "半日",
      "answer": "はんにち,はんじつ",
      "meaning": "half day"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻先",
      "answer": "はなさき",
      "meaning": "tip of nose, before one's eyes, under one's nose, in front of, tip (of something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一層",
      "answer": "いっそう",
      "meaning": "much more, still more, all the more, more than ever, single layer (or storey, etc.), rather, sooner,"
    },
    {
      "question": "調達",
      "answer": "ちょうたつ",
      "meaning": "supply, provision, raising, procurement"
    },
    {
      "question": "犯行",
      "answer": "はんこう",
      "meaning": "crime, criminal act, offence, offense"
    },
    {
      "question": "企業",
      "answer": "きぎょう",
      "meaning": "enterprise, business, company, corporation"
    },
    {
      "question": "君達",
      "answer": "きみたち,きんだち",
      "meaning": "you (plural), all of you, you all, kings, children of nobles, young nobleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "絨毯",
      "answer": "じゅうたん",
      "meaning": "carpet, rug, runner"
    },
    {
      "question": "代理",
      "answer": "だいり",
      "meaning": "representation, agency, proxy, deputy, agent, attorney, substitute, alternate, acting (principal, et"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝顔",
      "answer": "ねがお",
      "meaning": "sleeping face"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽やか",
      "answer": "かろやか,かるやか",
      "meaning": "light, easy, non-serious, minor"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌々しい",
      "answer": "いまいましい",
      "meaning": "annoying, provoking"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け流す",
      "answer": "うけながす",
      "meaning": "to ward off (e.g. an attack), to fend off (e.g. a question), to elude, to evade, to dodge, to turn a"
    },
    {
      "question": "身体能力",
      "answer": "しんたいのうりょく",
      "meaning": "physical ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "最優先",
      "answer": "さいゆうせん",
      "meaning": "maximum preference, maximum priority, priority handling"
    },
    {
      "question": "切",
      "answer": "せつ,きり",
      "meaning": "eager, earnest, ardent, kind, keen, acute, OFF (on switch), end, finish, stop, bounds, limits, deliv"
    },
    {
      "question": "価値観",
      "answer": "かちかん",
      "meaning": "sense of values, values, value system"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝶",
      "answer": "ちょう",
      "meaning": "butterfly"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛乳",
      "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう",
      "meaning": "(cow's) milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "構築",
      "answer": "こうちく",
      "meaning": "construction, building, putting up, erecting, creation, formulation, architecture (systems, agreemen"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰向け",
      "answer": "あおむけ",
      "meaning": "facing upward"
    },
    {
      "question": "集う",
      "answer": "つどう",
      "meaning": "to meet, to assemble, to congregate"
    },
    {
      "question": "従える",
      "answer": "したがえる",
      "meaning": "to be accompanied by, to be attended by, to take along (someone), to conquer, to subjugate, to subdu"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰に",
      "answer": "いんに",
      "meaning": "invisibly, secretly, privately"
    },
    {
      "question": "財産",
      "answer": "ざいさん",
      "meaning": "property, fortune, assets"
    },
    {
      "question": "覆す",
      "answer": "くつがえす",
      "meaning": "to overturn, to capsize, to upset, to overthrow (government etc.), to reverse (decision etc.), to di"
    },
    {
      "question": "睡眠",
      "answer": "すいみん",
      "meaning": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "渋々",
      "answer": "しぶしぶ",
      "meaning": "reluctantly, unwillingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "華",
      "answer": "はな,か",
      "meaning": "flower, blossom, bloom, petal, cherry blossom, beauty, blooming (esp. of cherry blossoms), ikebana,"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り込む",
      "answer": "まわりこむ",
      "meaning": "to go round and cut in, to take a roundabout path"
    },
    {
      "question": "見出す",
      "answer": "みいだす,みだす",
      "meaning": "to find out, to discover, to notice, to detect, to select, to pick out, to look out (from the inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦略",
      "answer": "せんりゃく",
      "meaning": "strategy, tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "暫く",
      "answer": "しばらく",
      "meaning": "for a moment, for a minute, for a while, for some time, for the time being, for now, it's been a lon"
    },
    {
      "question": "極める",
      "answer": "きめる,きわめる",
      "meaning": "to decide, to choose, to determine, to make up one's mind, to resolve, to set one's heart on, to set"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹂躙",
      "answer": "じゅうりん",
      "meaning": "trampling down, overrunning, infringement, violation"
    },
    {
      "question": "対等",
      "answer": "たいとう",
      "meaning": "equality (esp. of status, on equal terms), equivalence, equivalent, equal"
    },
    {
      "question": "投入",
      "answer": "とうにゅう",
      "meaning": "throwing in, inserting, depositing (e.g. a ballot), investment, commitment (of funds, personnel, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "知らせ",
      "answer": "しらせ",
      "meaning": "news, word, tidings, notice, notification, information, omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "強調",
      "answer": "きょうちょう",
      "meaning": "emphasis, highlight, stress, stressed point"
    },
    {
      "question": "見習い",
      "answer": "みならい",
      "meaning": "apprenticeship, probation, learning by observation, apprentice, trainee, probationer"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦戦",
      "answer": "くせん",
      "meaning": "hard fight, close game, struggle, tight contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "平凡",
      "answer": "へいぼん",
      "meaning": "ordinary, common, commonplace, mediocre, unremarkable, undistinguished, uneventful"
    },
    {
      "question": "草原",
      "answer": "そうげん,くさはら,くさわら",
      "meaning": "grassy field, grassland, meadow, grass-covered plain, savannah, prairie, steppe"
    },
    {
      "question": "弄る",
      "answer": "いじる,まさぐる,いじくる",
      "meaning": "to finger, to touch, to play with, to fiddle with, to toy with, to make changes to, to tinker with,"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮遊",
      "answer": "ふゆう",
      "meaning": "floating, drifting, suspension, wandering (about)"
    },
    {
      "question": "処置",
      "answer": "しょち",
      "meaning": "measure, step, dealing with, medical treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "足早",
      "answer": "あしばや",
      "meaning": "fast (walking), quick, brisk, quick (passing of time), rapid, swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "探偵",
      "answer": "たんてい",
      "meaning": "detective, sleuth, investigator"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤める",
      "answer": "つとめる",
      "meaning": "to work (for), to be employed (at), to serve (in), to serve (as), to act (as), to fill (the position"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑談",
      "answer": "ざつだん",
      "meaning": "chatting, idle talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍隊",
      "answer": "ぐんたい",
      "meaning": "armed forces, military, troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "急ぎ",
      "answer": "いそぎ",
      "meaning": "haste, hurry, expedition, speed, dispatch"
    },
    {
      "question": "説",
      "answer": "せつ",
      "meaning": "theory, doctrine, opinion, view, rumour, rumor, gossip, hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "不吉",
      "answer": "ふきつ",
      "meaning": "ominous, sinister, unlucky, inauspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "臆病",
      "answer": "おくびょう",
      "meaning": "cowardly, timid, easily frightened"
    },
    {
      "question": "交える",
      "answer": "まじえる",
      "meaning": "to mix, to combine, to include, to exchange (words, fire, etc.), to cross (e.g. swords), to join tog"
    },
    {
      "question": "活かす",
      "answer": "いかす",
      "meaning": "to make (the best) use of, to put to good use, to leverage (skills, attributes, experience, etc.), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "言語",
      "answer": "げんご,ごんご,げんきょ",
      "meaning": "language"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪",
      "answer": "じゅ,かしり",
      "meaning": "spell, curse, dharani, mantra"
    },
    {
      "question": "対決",
      "answer": "たいけつ",
      "meaning": "confrontation, showdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "成人",
      "answer": "せいじん",
      "meaning": "adult (esp. person 20 years old or over), grownup, becoming an adult, coming of age, growing up (to"
    },
    {
      "question": "留守番",
      "answer": "るすばん",
      "meaning": "care-taking, house-sitting, house-watching, staying at home, caretaker, house-sitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き去り",
      "answer": "おきざり",
      "meaning": "leaving behind, desertion, abandonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏切り者",
      "answer": "うらぎりもの",
      "meaning": "betrayer, traitor, turncoat, informer"
    },
    {
      "question": "病室",
      "answer": "びょうしつ",
      "meaning": "sickroom, hospital room"
    },
    {
      "question": "科学",
      "answer": "かがく",
      "meaning": "science"
    },
    {
      "question": "魅了",
      "answer": "みりょう",
      "meaning": "fascination, to charm, to fascinate, to mesmerize"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉座",
      "answer": "ぎょくざ",
      "meaning": "throne"
    },
    {
      "question": "日曜日",
      "answer": "にちようび",
      "meaning": "Sunday"
    },
    {
      "question": "威嚇",
      "answer": "いかく",
      "meaning": "threat, intimidation, menace"
    },
    {
      "question": "従業員",
      "answer": "じゅうぎょういん",
      "meaning": "employee, worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅ぶ",
      "answer": "ほろぶ",
      "meaning": "to be ruined, to go under, to perish, to be destroyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "追及",
      "answer": "ついきゅう",
      "meaning": "investigation (e.g. into someone's guilt), questioning, pressing, hounding, pinning down, catching u"
    },
    {
      "question": "空腹",
      "answer": "くうふく",
      "meaning": "empty stomach, hunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "大将",
      "answer": "たいしょう,だいしょう",
      "meaning": "general, admiral, head, chief, leader, boss, kingpin, old chap, mate, man, athlete who competes in t"
    },
    {
      "question": "個体",
      "answer": "こたい",
      "meaning": "individual, specimen"
    },
    {
      "question": "特性",
      "answer": "とくせい",
      "meaning": "special characteristic, special quality, trait, idiosyncrasy, peculiarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "交互",
      "answer": "こうご",
      "meaning": "alternate, alternating, mutual, reciprocal"
    },
    {
      "question": "知らす",
      "answer": "しらす",
      "meaning": "to inform, to notify, to know, to reign"
    },
    {
      "question": "惜しむ",
      "answer": "おしむ",
      "meaning": "to be frugal, to be sparing, to value, to hold dear, to regret (e.g. a loss), to feel sorry (for), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱き合う",
      "answer": "だきあう",
      "meaning": "to embrace each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "物資",
      "answer": "ぶっし",
      "meaning": "goods, materials, commodities, resources, supplies"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍る",
      "answer": "にぶる,なまる",
      "meaning": "to become blunt, to grow dull, to become less capable, to weaken, to falter"
    },
    {
      "question": "本題",
      "answer": "ほんだい",
      "meaning": "main question, real issue at hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "不味い",
      "answer": "まずい",
      "meaning": "bad (taste), unpalatable, unsavoury, unsavory, awful, terrible, unpleasant, poor, unskillful, unskil"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙々",
      "answer": "もくもく",
      "meaning": "silent, mute, dumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "願望",
      "answer": "がんぼう,がんもう",
      "meaning": "desire, wish, aspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "誠実",
      "answer": "せいじつ",
      "meaning": "sincere, honest, faithful"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏切り",
      "answer": "うらぎり",
      "meaning": "treachery, betrayal, perfidy"
    },
    {
      "question": "彷徨う",
      "answer": "さまよう",
      "meaning": "to loiter, to putter, to prowl, to wander about, to roam about, to knock around"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝",
      "answer": "みかど",
      "meaning": "emperor (of Japan), mikado"
    },
    {
      "question": "透き通る",
      "answer": "すきとおる",
      "meaning": "to be transparent, to be see-through, to be clear (voice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "別々",
      "answer": "べつべつ",
      "meaning": "separate, respective"
    },
    {
      "question": "重視",
      "answer": "じゅうし",
      "meaning": "regarding as important, attaching importance to, taking a serious view of, putting emphasis on"
    },
    {
      "question": "習慣",
      "answer": "しゅうかん",
      "meaning": "habit, (social) custom, practice, convention"
    },
    {
      "question": "側近",
      "answer": "そっきん",
      "meaning": "close associate, close aide, brains-truster"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い手",
      "answer": "つかいて",
      "meaning": "user, consumer, employer, master (e.g. of swordsmanship), prodigal, spendthrift"
    },
    {
      "question": "個室",
      "answer": "こしつ",
      "meaning": "private room, single (room), room for one, one's own room, (toilet) stall"
    },
    {
      "question": "教え",
      "answer": "おしえ",
      "meaning": "teaching, instruction, teachings, precept, lesson, doctrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "継続",
      "answer": "けいぞく",
      "meaning": "continuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し殺す",
      "answer": "おしころす",
      "meaning": "to crush to death, to stifle to death, to squeeze to death, to stifle (a laugh, etc.), to muffle (on"
    },
    {
      "question": "片付け",
      "answer": "かたづけ",
      "meaning": "tidying up, finishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "統一",
      "answer": "とういつ",
      "meaning": "unity, consolidation, uniformity, unification, compatible"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪しむ",
      "answer": "あやしむ",
      "meaning": "to suspect"
    },
    {
      "question": "何せ",
      "answer": "なにせ,なんせ",
      "meaning": "at any rate, anyhow"
    },
    {
      "question": "液",
      "answer": "えき,しる,つゆ",
      "meaning": "liquid, fluid, juice, sap, soup, broth, (dipping) sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇襲",
      "answer": "きしゅう",
      "meaning": "surprise attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "檻",
      "answer": "おり",
      "meaning": "cage, pen, (jail) cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "文明",
      "answer": "ぶんめい",
      "meaning": "civilization, civilisation, culture, Bunmei era (1469.4.28-1487.7.20)"
    },
    {
      "question": "火傷",
      "answer": "やけど,かしょう",
      "meaning": "burn, scald"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮",
      "answer": "け,かり",
      "meaning": "lacking substance and existing in name only, something without substance, temporary, provisional, in"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化祭",
      "answer": "ぶんかさい",
      "meaning": "school festival, cultural festival, annual open day school event showcasing student talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "手術",
      "answer": "しゅじゅつ,しゅずつ",
      "meaning": "surgery, operation, procedure"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐れ",
      "answer": "おそれ",
      "meaning": "fear, horror, anxiety, concern, uneasiness, reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "侮辱",
      "answer": "ぶじょく",
      "meaning": "insult, affront, slight, contempt (e.g. of court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不便",
      "answer": "ふべん,ふびん",
      "meaning": "inconvenience, inexpediency, unhandiness, poor, pitiful, piteous, pitiable"
    },
    {
      "question": "基地",
      "answer": "きち",
      "meaning": "base (military, expedition, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "担任",
      "answer": "たんにん",
      "meaning": "being in charge of (esp. a class or subject), taking charge of, class teacher, homeroom teacher, for"
    },
    {
      "question": "全開",
      "answer": "ぜんかい",
      "meaning": "opening fully, full throttle, full power"
    },
    {
      "question": "段々",
      "answer": "だんだん",
      "meaning": "gradually, by degrees, little by little, more and more, increasingly, steps, stairs, staircase, terr"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き込む",
      "answer": "ふきこむ",
      "meaning": "to blow into, to breathe into, to inspire, to indoctrinate, to record (music, video, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "目前",
      "answer": "めさき,もくぜん",
      "meaning": "before one's eyes, under one's nose, immediate (e.g. interests), present, at hand, short-run, foresi"
    },
    {
      "question": "手柄",
      "answer": "てがら",
      "meaning": "achievement, feat, meritorious deed, distinguished service"
    },
    {
      "question": "物理",
      "answer": "ぶつり",
      "meaning": "physics, law of nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "自嘲",
      "answer": "じちょう",
      "meaning": "self-deprecation, self-derision, self-mockery, laughing at oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "散らす",
      "answer": "ちらす",
      "meaning": "to scatter, to cause a shower of, to disperse, to distribute, to spread, to resolve (a symptom, cond"
    },
    {
      "question": "滝",
      "answer": "たき",
      "meaning": "waterfall, rapids"
    },
    {
      "question": "消失",
      "answer": "しょうしつ",
      "meaning": "disappearance, vanishing, loss, dying away, wearing off"
    },
    {
      "question": "謁見",
      "answer": "えっけん",
      "meaning": "audience (with a superior, e.g. nobility)"
    },
    {
      "question": "議論",
      "answer": "ぎろん",
      "meaning": "argument, discussion, dispute, controversy"
    },
    {
      "question": "零す",
      "answer": "こぼす",
      "meaning": "to spill, to drop, to shed (tears), to grumble, to complain, to let one's feelings show"
    },
    {
      "question": "日付",
      "answer": "ひづけ",
      "meaning": "date, dating"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い取る",
      "answer": "かいとる",
      "meaning": "to buy, to purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶対的",
      "answer": "ぜったいてき",
      "meaning": "absolute"
    },
    {
      "question": "許し",
      "answer": "ゆるし,ばかし,ばっかし",
      "meaning": "pardon, forgiveness, exemption, permission, approximately, about, only, nothing but, just (finished,"
    },
    {
      "question": "細工",
      "answer": "さいく",
      "meaning": "work, workmanship, craftsmanship, handiwork, artifice, trick, device, tampering, doctoring"
    },
    {
      "question": "精",
      "answer": "せい",
      "meaning": "spirit, sprite, nymph, energy, vigor (vigour), strength, fine details, semen"
    },
    {
      "question": "同感",
      "answer": "どうかん",
      "meaning": "same feeling, same sentiment, same opinion, sympathy, agreement, concurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "驚かす",
      "answer": "おどろかす",
      "meaning": "to surprise, to frighten, to create a stir"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨晩",
      "answer": "さくばん",
      "meaning": "last night"
    },
    {
      "question": "手際",
      "answer": "てぎわ",
      "meaning": "performance, execution, skill, dexterity, tact"
    },
    {
      "question": "訊ねる",
      "answer": "たずねる",
      "meaning": "to ask, to enquire, to inquire, to search, to look for, to look into, to investigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "惨め",
      "answer": "みじめ",
      "meaning": "miserable, wretched, unhappy, sad, pitiable"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鳥",
      "answer": "ことり",
      "meaning": "small bird, little bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せる",
      "answer": "やせる",
      "meaning": "to become thin, to lose weight, to reduce (one's) weight, to slim, to be barren, to be infertile, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教",
      "answer": "しゅうきょう",
      "meaning": "religion, religious affiliation, belief, faith, creed, religious activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "過酷",
      "answer": "かこく",
      "meaning": "severe, harsh, hard, cruel, rigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇腹",
      "answer": "わきばら",
      "meaning": "side (of the torso), flank, illegitimate child, child born by someone other than one's wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "付与",
      "answer": "ふよ",
      "meaning": "grant, allowance, endowment, bestowal, assignment, conferment"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼",
      "answer": "けん",
      "meaning": "cum (e.g. bedroom-cum-study), holding both roles (e.g. Prime Minister and Minister of Foreign Affair"
    },
    {
      "question": "大幅",
      "answer": "おおはば",
      "meaning": "big, large, drastic, substantial, full-width cloth (approx. 72 cm wide for traditional Japanese clot"
    },
    {
      "question": "坊",
      "answer": "ぼう,ぼん",
      "meaning": "bonze, monk, monk's dwelling, boy, son, sonny, I, me, little, person who is ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "見習う",
      "answer": "みならう",
      "meaning": "to follow another's example"
    },
    {
      "question": "お約束",
      "answer": "おやくそく",
      "meaning": "promise, agreement, arrangement, one's word, contract, pact, appointment, engagement, date, somethin"
    },
    {
      "question": "受験",
      "answer": "じゅけん",
      "meaning": "taking an examination (esp. school and university entrance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "致命傷",
      "answer": "ちめいしょう",
      "meaning": "fatal wound"
    },
    {
      "question": "貢献",
      "answer": "こうけん",
      "meaning": "contribution (furthering a goal or cause), services (to a cause)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最",
      "answer": "さい",
      "meaning": "the most, the extreme, prime, conspicuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "電波",
      "answer": "でんぱ",
      "meaning": "radio wave, reception, signal, saying strange things"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃げ込む",
      "answer": "にげこむ",
      "meaning": "to take refuge in, to succeed in running away"
    },
    {
      "question": "補充",
      "answer": "ほじゅう",
      "meaning": "replenishment, supplementation, supplement, replacement, refilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊重",
      "answer": "そんちょう",
      "meaning": "respect, esteem, regard"
    },
    {
      "question": "平静",
      "answer": "へいせい",
      "meaning": "calm, serenity, tranquillity, tranquility"
    },
    {
      "question": "体育館",
      "answer": "たいいくかん,たいくかん",
      "meaning": "gymnasium"
    },
    {
      "question": "後者",
      "answer": "こうしゃ",
      "meaning": "the latter"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶色",
      "answer": "ちゃいろ",
      "meaning": "light brown, tawny"
    },
    {
      "question": "果実",
      "answer": "かじつ",
      "meaning": "fruit, nut, berry, fruits, profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "住所",
      "answer": "じゅうしょ",
      "meaning": "address (e.g. of house), residence, domicile"
    },
    {
      "question": "列車",
      "answer": "れっしゃ",
      "meaning": "train, railway train"
    },
    {
      "question": "免れる",
      "answer": "まぬがれる,まぬかれる",
      "meaning": "to escape (disaster, death, etc.), to be saved from, to be rescued from, to avoid (e.g. punishment),"
    },
    {
      "question": "名付ける",
      "answer": "なづける",
      "meaning": "to name, to call, to christen, to term"
    },
    {
      "question": "訝しい",
      "answer": "いぶかしい",
      "meaning": "suspicious, doubtful"
    },
    {
      "question": "院",
      "answer": "いん",
      "meaning": "house of parliament (congress, diet, etc.), graduate school, postgraduate school, institution (often"
    },
    {
      "question": "身を隠す",
      "answer": "みをかくす",
      "meaning": "to hide oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "画像",
      "answer": "がぞう",
      "meaning": "image, picture, portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "専念",
      "answer": "せんねん",
      "meaning": "absorption, giving undivided attention, devoting oneself (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶妙",
      "answer": "ぜつみょう",
      "meaning": "exquisite, superb, perfect, miraculous"
    },
    {
      "question": "即",
      "answer": "そく",
      "meaning": "instantly, immediately, at once, equals, means, is, oneness (of two opposing things), inseparability"
    },
    {
      "question": "通報",
      "answer": "つうほう",
      "meaning": "report, notification, tip, bulletin, message (in information and communication theory)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手早い",
      "answer": "てばやい",
      "meaning": "nimble, quick, agile"
    },
    {
      "question": "心得る",
      "answer": "こころえる",
      "meaning": "to know, to understand, to be aware of, to regard as, to take for, to consent, to agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "活用",
      "answer": "かつよう",
      "meaning": "practical use, application, conjugation, inflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "指揮官",
      "answer": "しきかん",
      "meaning": "commander, commanding officer, CO"
    },
    {
      "question": "形状",
      "answer": "けいじょう",
      "meaning": "shape, form"
    },
    {
      "question": "破棄",
      "answer": "はき",
      "meaning": "tearing up and discarding (e.g. documents), disposal (e.g. weaponry), destruction, annulment, cancel"
    },
    {
      "question": "濁る",
      "answer": "にごる",
      "meaning": "to become muddy, to become cloudy, to get impure (of a liquid, gas, etc.), to become dull (of a soun"
    },
    {
      "question": "人種",
      "answer": "じんしゅ",
      "meaning": "race (of people), type of person"
    },
    {
      "question": "最新",
      "answer": "さいしん",
      "meaning": "latest, newest, late-breaking (news)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣国",
      "answer": "りんごく,りんこく",
      "meaning": "neighbouring country, neighboring country, adjacent country"
    },
    {
      "question": "快適",
      "answer": "かいてき",
      "meaning": "pleasant, agreeable, comfortable"
    },
    {
      "question": "物質",
      "answer": "ぶっしつ",
      "meaning": "material, substance, matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "追放",
      "answer": "ついほう",
      "meaning": "exile, banishment, eviction, deportation, purge, expulsion, ousting, elimination (e.g. of poverty),"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃亡",
      "answer": "とうぼう",
      "meaning": "escape, flight, running away, elopement, fleeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き進む",
      "answer": "つきすすむ",
      "meaning": "to push on, to plunge forward, to push one's way to"
    },
    {
      "question": "手の甲",
      "answer": "てのこう",
      "meaning": "back of the hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐い",
      "answer": "こわい",
      "meaning": "scary, frightening, eerie, dreadful"
    },
    {
      "question": "大きめ",
      "answer": "おおきめ",
      "meaning": "largish, biggish, a little bit larger"
    },
    {
      "question": "変装",
      "answer": "へんそう",
      "meaning": "disguise, masquerade"
    },
    {
      "question": "兎",
      "answer": "うさぎ,う",
      "meaning": "rabbit, hare, coney, cony, lagomorph (esp. leporids)"
    },
    {
      "question": "申請",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "application, request, petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "躱す",
      "answer": "かわす",
      "meaning": "to dodge, to evade, to avoid, to sidestep"
    },
    {
      "question": "罵る",
      "answer": "ののしる",
      "meaning": "to abuse (verbally), to curse at, to shout abuse at, to speak ill of"
    },
    {
      "question": "難易度",
      "answer": "なんいど",
      "meaning": "degree of difficulty, difficulty level"
    },
    {
      "question": "体制",
      "answer": "たいせい",
      "meaning": "order, system, structure, set-up, organization, organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "亀裂",
      "answer": "きれつ",
      "meaning": "crack, crevice, fissure, chap, rift"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤る",
      "answer": "あやまる",
      "meaning": "to make a mistake (in), to commit an error, to do incorrectly, to err, to be wrong, to be incorrect,"
    },
    {
      "question": "時間帯",
      "answer": "じかんたい",
      "meaning": "period of time, time slot, time zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "渾身",
      "answer": "こんしん",
      "meaning": "one's whole body, all of one's might"
    }
  ]
}
